id,cleaned_text,favorites,retweets,date,date_new,date_part,time_part,hour,year,month,sentiment_score,tweet_length,compound,entity,entity_type,cleaned_text2
9.38423e+17,make america great again!,157963,37189,2017-06-12 15:00:00,2017-06-12 23:00:00,2017-06-12,23:00:00,23,2017,6,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.406, 'pos': 0.594, 'compound': 0.6588}",25,0.6588,[],[],make america great again!
9.39189e+17,make america great again! ,56596,11433,2017-08-12 17:46:00,2017-08-13 01:46:00,2017-08-13,01:46:00,1,2017,8,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.406, 'pos': 0.594, 'compound': 0.6588}",26,0.6588,[],[],make america great again! 
9.3534e+17,thank you rand! ,42793,9125,2017-11-28 02:50:00,2017-11-28 10:50:00,2017-11-28,10:50:00,10,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.417, 'pos': 0.583, 'compound': 0.4199}",16,0.4199,['Rand'],['ORG'],thank you rand! 
9.25389e+17,thank you @luisriveramarin! ,23521,4574,2017-10-31 15:48:00,2017-10-31 23:48:00,2017-10-31,23:48:00,23,2017,10,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.417, 'pos': 0.583, 'compound': 0.4199}",28,0.4199,[],[],thank you ! 
8.99798e+17,"join me live from fort myer in arlington, virginia. ➡️",36009,4891,2017-08-22 01:00:00,2017-08-22 09:00:00,2017-08-22,09:00:00,9,2017,8,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.804, 'pos': 0.196, 'compound': 0.296}",54,0.29600000000000004,"['Fort Myer', 'Arlington', 'Virginia', '➡']","['GPE', 'GPE', 'GPE', 'ORG']","join me live from fort myer in arlington, virginia. "
8.9397e+17,thank you nicole! ,43367,8275,2017-05-08 23:01:00,2017-05-09 07:01:00,2017-05-09,07:01:00,7,2017,5,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.417, 'pos': 0.583, 'compound': 0.4199}",18,0.4199,['Nicole'],['PERSON'],thank you nicole! 
8.91344e+17,u.s. stock market up almost 20% since election!,88855,17565,2017-07-29 17:04:00,2017-07-30 01:04:00,2017-07-30,01:04:00,1,2017,7,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",47,0.0,"['U.S.', 'almost 20%']","['GPE', 'PERCENT']",u.s. stock market up almost 20% since election!
8.81977e+17,thank you to shawn steel for the nice words on @foxnews.,50956,7465,2017-03-07 20:44:00,2017-03-08 04:44:00,2017-03-08,04:44:00,4,2017,3,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.629, 'pos': 0.371, 'compound': 0.6486}",56,0.6486,['Shawn Steel'],['PERSON'],thank you to shawn steel for the nice words on .
8.77846e+17,great night in iowa - special people. thank you!,56446,8039,2017-06-22 11:11:00,2017-06-22 19:11:00,2017-06-22,19:11:00,19,2017,6,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.343, 'pos': 0.657, 'compound': 0.8622}",48,0.8622,"['night', 'Iowa']","['TIME', 'GPE']",great night in iowa - special people. thank you!
8.78725e+17,make america great again!,134210,36346,2017-06-24 21:23:00,2017-06-25 05:23:00,2017-06-25,05:23:00,5,2017,6,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.406, 'pos': 0.594, 'compound': 0.6588}",25,0.6588,[],[],make america great again!
8.74084e+17,"my daughter, ivanka, will be on @foxandfriends tomorrow morning. enjoy!",50169,6877,2017-12-06 02:02:00,2017-12-06 10:02:00,2017-12-06,10:02:00,10,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.72, 'pos': 0.28, 'compound': 0.5411}",71,0.5411,['Ivanka'],['PERSON'],"my daughter, ivanka, will be on  tomorrow morning. enjoy!"
8.60581e+17,#weeklyaddress🇺🇸 ,32928,7962,2017-05-05 19:43:00,2017-05-06 03:43:00,2017-05-06,03:43:00,3,2017,5,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",17,0.0,"['#', 'WeeklyAddress', '🇸']","['CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'ORG']",#weeklyaddress 
8.62999e+17,the fake media is working overtime today!,65939,15809,2017-12-05 11:53:00,2017-12-05 19:53:00,2017-12-05,19:53:00,19,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.361, 'neu': 0.639, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5255}",41,-0.5255,['today'],['DATE'],the fake media is working overtime today!
8.56148e+17,"thank you lake worth, florida. @foxandfriends",29218,3842,2017-04-23 14:07:00,2017-04-23 22:07:00,2017-04-23,22:07:00,22,2017,4,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.476, 'pos': 0.524, 'compound': 0.5267}",45,0.5267,"['Lake Worth', 'Florida']","['GPE', 'GPE']","thank you lake worth, florida. "
8.60089e+17,congratulations to @foxandfriends on its unbelievable ratings hike.,31683,5238,2017-04-05 11:07:00,2017-04-05 19:07:00,2017-04-05,19:07:00,19,2017,4,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.513, 'pos': 0.487, 'compound': 0.6908}",67,0.6908,[],[],congratulations to  on its unbelievable ratings hike.
8.52985e+17,weekly address-  ,28250,5616,2017-04-14 20:41:00,2017-04-15 04:41:00,2017-04-15,04:41:00,4,2017,4,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",17,0.0,['Weekly'],['DATE'],weekly address-  
8.41665e+17,"jobs, jobs, jobs! ",83629,19677,2017-03-14 15:00:00,2017-03-14 23:00:00,2017-03-14,23:00:00,23,2017,3,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",18,0.0,['JOBS'],['ORG'],"jobs, jobs, jobs! "
8.32375e+17,'trump signs bill undoing obama coal mining rule' ,79427,15157,2017-02-16 23:44:00,2017-02-17 07:44:00,2017-02-17,07:44:00,7,2017,2,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",50,0.0,['Obama'],['ORG'],'trump signs bill undoing obama coal mining rule' 
1.07755e+18,merry christmas!,447174,72055,2018-12-25 12:59:00,2018-12-25 20:59:00,2018-12-25,20:59:00,20,2018,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.209, 'pos': 0.791, 'compound': 0.5848}",16,0.5848,['Merry Christmas'],['PERSON'],merry christmas!
1.07325e+18,witch hunt!,88440,18748,2018-12-13 16:08:00,2018-12-14 00:08:00,2018-12-14,00:08:00,0,2018,12,"{'neg': 0.736, 'neu': 0.264, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4199}",11,-0.4199,[],[],witch hunt!
1.07103e+18,china talks are going very well!,77764,11947,2018-07-12 13:13:00,2018-07-12 21:13:00,2018-07-12,21:13:00,21,2018,7,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.651, 'pos': 0.349, 'compound': 0.3989}",32,0.3989,['China'],['GPE'],china talks are going very well!
1.0651e+18,america first!,157446,34373,2018-11-21 04:40:00,2018-11-21 12:40:00,2018-11-21,12:40:00,12,2018,11,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",14,0.0,[],[],america first!
1.05987e+18,polling locations: ,31596,7863,2018-06-11 17:58:00,2018-06-12 01:58:00,2018-06-12,01:58:00,1,2018,6,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",19,0.0,[],[],polling locations: 
1.05848e+18,"jobs, jobs, jobs! #maga ",50814,12836,2018-02-11 22:14:00,2018-02-12 06:14:00,2018-02-12,06:14:00,6,2018,2,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",24,0.0,"['JOBS', 'JOBS', 'JOBS', '#']","['ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'CARDINAL']","jobs, jobs, jobs! #maga "
1.04106e+18,thank you @nycemergencymgt! ,30020,5917,2018-09-15 20:26:00,2018-09-16 04:26:00,2018-09-16,04:26:00,4,2018,9,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.417, 'pos': 0.583, 'compound': 0.4199}",28,0.4199,[],[],thank you ! 
1.04043e+18,gina is great! ,35481,7208,2018-09-14 02:37:00,2018-09-14 10:37:00,2018-09-14,10:37:00,10,2018,9,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.313, 'pos': 0.687, 'compound': 0.6588}",15,0.6588,['Gina'],['PERSON'],gina is great! 
1.03789e+18,make america great again! ,57264,13708,2018-07-09 02:38:00,2018-07-09 10:38:00,2018-07-09,10:38:00,10,2018,7,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.406, 'pos': 0.594, 'compound': 0.6588}",26,0.6588,[],[],make america great again! 
1.03491e+18,#stopthebias ,90355,31460,2018-08-29 20:55:00,2018-08-30 04:55:00,2018-08-30,04:55:00,4,2018,8,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",13,0.0,[],[],#stopthebias 
1.01991e+18,really big jobs meeting today at the white house! 3 p.m.,52570,8804,2018-07-19 11:37:00,2018-07-19 19:37:00,2018-07-19,19:37:00,19,2018,7,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",56,0.0,"['today', 'the White House', '3']","['DATE', 'FAC', 'CARDINAL']",really big jobs meeting today at the white house! 3 p.m.
1.01527e+18,"jobs, jobs, jobs! ",77760,17348,2018-06-07 16:12:00,2018-06-08 00:12:00,2018-06-08,00:12:00,0,2018,6,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",18,0.0,['JOBS'],['ORG'],"jobs, jobs, jobs! "
9.88106e+17,a complete witch hunt!,80665,15518,2018-04-22 17:23:00,2018-04-23 01:23:00,2018-04-23,01:23:00,1,2018,4,"{'neg': 0.583, 'neu': 0.417, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4199}",22,-0.4199,[],[],a complete witch hunt!
9.68468e+17,witch hunt!,78352,18267,2018-02-27 12:49:00,2018-02-27 20:49:00,2018-02-27,20:49:00,20,2018,2,"{'neg': 0.736, 'neu': 0.264, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4199}",11,-0.4199,[],[],witch hunt!
9.71009e+17,we will see what happens! ,32543,7586,2018-06-03 13:05:00,2018-06-03 21:05:00,2018-06-03,21:05:00,21,2018,6,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",26,0.0,[],[],we will see what happens! 
9.66119e+17,"so true, thank you! ",82845,17050,2018-02-21 01:14:00,2018-02-21 09:14:00,2018-02-21,09:14:00,9,2018,2,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.245, 'pos': 0.755, 'compound': 0.7322}",20,0.7322,[],[],"so true, thank you! "
9.67389e+17,"so true wayne, and lowest black unemployment in history! ",67985,15985,2018-02-24 13:21:00,2018-02-24 21:21:00,2018-02-24,21:21:00,21,2018,2,"{'neg': 0.389, 'neu': 0.403, 'pos': 0.208, 'compound': -0.4017}",57,-0.4017,"['Wayne', 'Lowest']","['PERSON', 'ORG']","so true wayne, and lowest black unemployment in history! "
1.01994e+18,“trump recognized russian meddling many times.” ,2539,809,2018-07-19 01:27:00,2018-07-19 09:27:00,2018-07-19,09:27:00,9,2018,7,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",48,0.0,['Russian Meddling MANY TIMES'],['ORG'],“trump recognized russian meddling many times.” 
9.47803e+17,"the united states has foolishly given pakistan more than 33 billion dollars in aid over the last 15 years, and they have given us nothing but lies &amp, deceit, thinking of our leaders as fools. they give safe haven to the terrorists we hunt in afghanistan, with little help. no more!",264772,84892,2018-01-01 12:12:00,2018-01-01 20:12:00,2018-01-01,20:12:00,20,2018,1,"{'neg': 0.256, 'neu': 0.58, 'pos': 0.164, 'compound': -0.8256}",284,-0.8256,"['The United States', 'Pakistan', 'more than 33 billion dollars', 'the last 15 years', 'Afghanistan']","['GPE', 'GPE', 'MONEY', 'DATE', 'GPE']","the united states has foolishly given pakistan more than 33 billion dollars in aid over the last 15 years, and they have given us nothing but lies &amp, deceit, thinking of our leaders as fools. they give safe haven to the terrorists we hunt in afghanistan, with little help. no more!"
9.47811e+17,"iran is failing at every level despite the terrible deal made with them by the obama administration. the great iranian people have been repressed for many years. they are hungry for food &amp, for freedom. along with human rights, the wealth of iran is being looted. time for change!",93842,22577,2018-01-01 12:44:00,2018-01-01 20:44:00,2018-01-01,20:44:00,20,2018,1,"{'neg': 0.089, 'neu': 0.683, 'pos': 0.228, 'compound': 0.8672}",283,0.8672,"['Iran', 'the Obama Administration', 'Iranian', 'food &amp', 'Iran', 'TIME']","['GPE', 'ORG', 'NORP', 'ORG', 'GPE', 'ORG']","iran is failing at every level despite the terrible deal made with them by the obama administration. the great iranian people have been repressed for many years. they are hungry for food &amp, for freedom. along with human rights, the wealth of iran is being looted. time for change!"
9.48164e+17,"the people of iran are finally acting against the brutal and corrupt iranian regime. all of the money that president obama so foolishly gave them went into terrorism and into their “pockets.” the people have little food, big inflation and no human rights. the u.s. is watching!",88918,21894,2018-02-01 12:09:00,2018-02-01 20:09:00,2018-02-01,20:09:00,20,2018,2,"{'neg': 0.256, 'neu': 0.744, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.9414}",277,-0.9414,"['Iran', 'Iranian', 'Obama', 'U.S.']","['GPE', 'NORP', 'PERSON', 'GPE']","the people of iran are finally acting against the brutal and corrupt iranian regime. all of the money that president obama so foolishly gave them went into terrorism and into their “pockets.” the people have little food, big inflation and no human rights. the u.s. is watching!"
9.48174e+17,"crooked hillary clinton’s top aid, huma abedin, has been accused of disregarding basic security protocols. she put classified passwords into the hands of foreign agents. remember sailors pictures on submarine? jail! deep state justice dept must finally act? also on comey &amp, others",110587,29611,2018-02-01 12:48:00,2018-02-01 20:48:00,2018-02-01,20:48:00,20,2018,2,"{'neg': 0.081, 'neu': 0.755, 'pos': 0.164, 'compound': 0.6312}",284,0.6312,"['Crooked Hillary Clinton’s', 'Huma Abedin', 'Classified Passwords', 'Comey &amp']","['PERSON', 'PERSON', 'ORG', 'ORG']","crooked hillary clinton’s top aid, huma abedin, has been accused of disregarding basic security protocols. she put classified passwords into the hands of foreign agents. remember sailors pictures on submarine? jail! deep state justice dept must finally act? also on comey &amp, others"
9.48188e+17,"thank you to brandon judd of the national border patrol council for your kind words on how well we are doing at the border. we will be bringing in more &amp, more of your great folks and will build the desperately needed wall! @foxandfriends",58684,11221,2018-02-01 13:44:00,2018-02-01 21:44:00,2018-02-01,21:44:00,21,2018,2,"{'neg': 0.048, 'neu': 0.719, 'pos': 0.233, 'compound': 0.8766}",241,0.8766,"['Brandon Judd', 'the National Border Patrol Council']","['PERSON', 'ORG']","thank you to brandon judd of the national border patrol council for your kind words on how well we are doing at the border. we will be bringing in more &amp, more of your great folks and will build the desperately needed wall! "
9.48189e+17,companies are giving big bonuses to their workers because of the tax cut bill. really great!,73282,12077,2018-02-01 13:49:00,2018-02-01 21:49:00,2018-02-01,21:49:00,21,2018,2,"{'neg': 0.085, 'neu': 0.484, 'pos': 0.431, 'compound': 0.862}",92,0.862,['the Tax Cut Bill'],['LAW'],companies are giving big bonuses to their workers because of the tax cut bill. really great!
9.48194e+17,"sanctions and “other” pressures are beginning to have a big impact on north korea. soldiers are dangerously fleeing to south korea. rocket man now wants to talk to south korea for first time. perhaps that is good news, perhaps not - we will see!",65372,13491,2018-02-01 14:08:00,2018-02-01 22:08:00,2018-02-01,22:08:00,22,2018,2,"{'neg': 0.118, 'neu': 0.821, 'pos': 0.061, 'compound': -0.4003}",245,-0.4003,"['North Korea', 'South Korea', 'South Korea', 'first']","['GPE', 'GPE', 'GPE', 'ORDINAL']","sanctions and “other” pressures are beginning to have a big impact on north korea. soldiers are dangerously fleeing to south korea. rocket man now wants to talk to south korea for first time. perhaps that is good news, perhaps not - we will see!"
9.48195e+17,"since taking office i have been very strict on commercial aviation. good news - it was just reported that there were zero deaths in 2017, the best and safest year on record!",75197,12828,2018-02-01 14:13:00,2018-02-01 22:13:00,2018-02-01,22:13:00,22,2018,2,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.728, 'pos': 0.272, 'compound': 0.8777}",173,0.8777,"['Commercial Aviation', 'Zero', '2017']","['ORG', 'CARDINAL', 'DATE']","since taking office i have been very strict on commercial aviation. good news - it was just reported that there were zero deaths in 2017, the best and safest year on record!"
9.48202e+17,"the failing new york times has a new publisher, a.g. sulzberger. congratulations! here is a last chance for the times to fulfill the vision of its founder, adolph ochs, “to give the news impartially, without fear or favor, regardless of party, sect, or interests involved.” get...",66457,13909,2018-02-01 14:39:00,2018-02-01 22:39:00,2018-02-01,22:39:00,22,2018,2,"{'neg': 0.102, 'neu': 0.588, 'pos': 0.309, 'compound': 0.8839}",280,0.8839,"['Times', 'Adolph Ochs']","['ORG', 'PERSON']","the failing new york times has a new publisher, a.g. sulzberger. congratulations! here is a last chance for the times to fulfill the vision of its founder, adolph ochs, “to give the news impartially, without fear or favor, regardless of party, sect, or interests involved.” get..."
9.48206e+17,"....impartial journalists of a much higher standard, lose all of your phony and non-existent “sources,” and treat the president of the united states fairly, so that the next time i (and the people) win, you won’t have to write an apology to your readers for a job poorly done! gl",64938,12704,2018-02-01 14:53:00,2018-02-01 22:53:00,2018-02-01,22:53:00,22,2018,2,"{'neg': 0.047, 'neu': 0.713, 'pos': 0.24, 'compound': 0.8786}",279,0.8786,"['the United States', 'GL']","['GPE', 'PERSON']","....impartial journalists of a much higher standard, lose all of your phony and non-existent “sources,” and treat the president of the united states fairly, so that the next time i (and the people) win, you won’t have to write an apology to your readers for a job poorly done! gl"
9.48211e+17,"democrats are doing nothing for daca - just interested in politics.  daca activists and hispanics will go hard against dems, will start “falling in love” with republicans and their president! we are about results.",73566,14383,2018-02-01 15:16:00,2018-02-01 23:16:00,2018-02-01,23:16:00,23,2018,2,"{'neg': 0.04, 'neu': 0.876, 'pos': 0.085, 'compound': 0.3802}",213,0.3802,"['Democrats', 'Hispanics', 'Dems', 'Republicans', 'RESULTS']","['NORP', 'NORP', 'NORP', 'NORP', 'ORG']","democrats are doing nothing for daca - just interested in politics.  daca activists and hispanics will go hard against dems, will start “falling in love” with republicans and their president! we are about results."
9.48255e+17,we will not rest until all of america’s great veterans can receive the care they so richly deserve. tremendous progress has been made in a short period of time. keep up the great work @secshulkin @deptvetaffairs!  ,59356,12689,2018-02-01 18:11:00,2018-02-02 02:11:00,2018-02-02,02:11:00,2,2018,2,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.62, 'pos': 0.38, 'compound': 0.9608}",214,0.9608,"['America', '@SecShulkin']","['GPE', 'NORP']",we will not rest until all of america’s great veterans can receive the care they so richly deserve. tremendous progress has been made in a short period of time. keep up the great work  !  
9.48319e+17,"congratulations to senator orrin hatch on an absolutely incredible career. he has been a tremendous supporter, and i will never forget the (beyond kind) statements he has made about me as president. he is my friend and he will be greatly missed in the u.s. senate! ",53678,9691,2018-02-01 22:23:00,2018-02-02 06:23:00,2018-02-02,06:23:00,6,2018,2,"{'neg': 0.047, 'neu': 0.741, 'pos': 0.212, 'compound': 0.8255}",265,0.8255,"['Orrin Hatch', 'the U.S. Senate']","['PERSON', 'ORG']","congratulations to senator orrin hatch on an absolutely incredible career. he has been a tremendous supporter, and i will never forget the (beyond kind) statements he has made about me as president. he is my friend and he will be greatly missed in the u.s. senate! "
9.4836e+17,"i will be announcing the most dishonest &amp, corrupt media awards of the year on monday at 5:00 o’clock. subjects will cover dishonesty &amp, bad reporting in various categories from the fake news media. stay tuned!",164894,39474,2018-03-01 01:05:00,2018-03-01 09:05:00,2018-03-01,09:05:00,9,2018,3,"{'neg': 0.262, 'neu': 0.658, 'pos': 0.079, 'compound': -0.8631}",216,-0.8631,"['THE MOST DISHONEST &amp', 'CORRUPT', 'THE YEAR on Monday', '5:00 o’clock', 'Dishonesty &amp', 'Bad Reporting', 'the Fake News Media']","['ORG', 'ORG', 'EVENT', 'TIME', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG']","i will be announcing the most dishonest &amp, corrupt media awards of the year on monday at 5:00 o’clock. subjects will cover dishonesty &amp, bad reporting in various categories from the fake news media. stay tuned!"
9.48404e+17,"“president trump has something now he didn’t have a year ago, that is a set of accomplishments that nobody can deny. the accomplishments are there, look at his record, he has had a very significant first year.” @loudobbs show,david asman &amp, ed rollins",82534,16495,2018-03-01 04:03:00,2018-03-01 12:03:00,2018-03-01,12:03:00,12,2018,3,"{'neg': 0.056, 'neu': 0.894, 'pos': 0.049, 'compound': -0.079}",254,-0.079,"['Trump', 'a year ago', 'first', 'David Asman &amp', 'Ed Rollins']","['PERSON', 'DATE', 'ORDINAL', 'ORG', 'PERSON']","“president trump has something now he didn’t have a year ago, that is a set of accomplishments that nobody can deny. the accomplishments are there, look at his record, he has had a very significant first year.”  show,david asman &amp, ed rollins"
9.48549e+17,such respect for the people of iran as they try to take back their corrupt government. you will see great support from the united states at the appropriate time!,126089,24423,2018-03-01 13:37:00,2018-03-01 21:37:00,2018-03-01,21:37:00,21,2018,3,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.658, 'pos': 0.342, 'compound': 0.9184}",161,0.9184,"['Iran', 'the United States']","['GPE', 'GPE']",such respect for the people of iran as they try to take back their corrupt government. you will see great support from the united states at the appropriate time!
9.48738e+17,"“some 40 u.s. companies have responded to president trump’s tax cut and reform victory in congress last year by handing out bonuses up to $2,000, increases in 401k matches and spending on charity, a much higher number than previously known.” ",57755,13178,2018-04-01 02:07:00,2018-04-01 10:07:00,2018-04-01,10:07:00,10,2018,4,"{'neg': 0.047, 'neu': 0.781, 'pos': 0.172, 'compound': 0.6808}",242,0.6808,"['Some 40', 'U.S.', 'Trump', 'Congress', 'last year', 'up to $2,000', '401k']","['CARDINAL', 'GPE', 'PERSON', 'ORG', 'DATE', 'MONEY', 'NORP']","“some 40 u.s. companies have responded to president trump’s tax cut and reform victory in congress last year by handing out bonuses up to $2,000, increases in 401k matches and spending on charity, a much higher number than previously known.” "
9.48739e+17,"stock market had another good day but, now that the tax cut bill has passed, we have tremendous upward potential. dow just short of 25,000, a number that few thought would be possible this soon into my administration. also, unemployment went down to 4.1%. only getting better!",90710,15696,2018-04-01 02:11:00,2018-04-01 10:11:00,2018-04-01,10:11:00,10,2018,4,"{'neg': 0.118, 'neu': 0.745, 'pos': 0.137, 'compound': -0.1386}",276,-0.1386,"['another good day', 'the Tax Cut Bill', '25,000', '4.1%']","['DATE', 'LAW', 'CARDINAL', 'PERCENT']","stock market had another good day but, now that the tax cut bill has passed, we have tremendous upward potential. dow just short of 25,000, a number that few thought would be possible this soon into my administration. also, unemployment went down to 4.1%. only getting better!"
9.48872e+17,"many mostly democrat states refused to hand over data from the 2016 election to the commission on voter fraud. they fought hard that the commission not see their records or methods because they know that many people are voting illegally. system is rigged, must go to voter i.d.",93479,24611,2018-04-01 11:02:00,2018-04-01 19:02:00,2018-04-01,19:02:00,19,2018,4,"{'neg': 0.213, 'neu': 0.732, 'pos': 0.056, 'compound': -0.7906}",277,-0.7906,"['Democrat', '2016', 'the Commission On Voter Fraud', 'Commission', 'Voter I.D.']","['NORP', 'DATE', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG']","many mostly democrat states refused to hand over data from the 2016 election to the commission on voter fraud. they fought hard that the commission not see their records or methods because they know that many people are voting illegally. system is rigged, must go to voter i.d."
9.48875e+17,"as americans, you need identification, sometimes in a very strong and accurate form, for almost everything you do.....except when it comes to the most important thing, voting for the people that run your country. push hard for voter identification!",131113,31942,2018-04-01 11:11:00,2018-04-01 19:11:00,2018-04-01,19:11:00,19,2018,4,"{'neg': 0.033, 'neu': 0.826, 'pos': 0.141, 'compound': 0.6786}",248,0.6786,"['Americans', 'Voter Identification']","['NORP', 'ORG']","as americans, you need identification, sometimes in a very strong and accurate form, for almost everything you do.....except when it comes to the most important thing, voting for the people that run your country. push hard for voter identification!"
9.4888e+17,"with all of the failed “experts” weighing in, does anybody really believe that talks and dialogue would be going on between north and south korea right now if i wasn’t firm, strong and willing to commit our total “might” against the north. fools, but talks are a good thing!",79155,15366,2018-04-01 11:32:00,2018-04-01 19:32:00,2018-04-01,19:32:00,19,2018,4,"{'neg': 0.078, 'neu': 0.776, 'pos': 0.146, 'compound': 0.5635}",274,0.5635,"['North', 'South Korea', 'North']","['GPE', 'GPE', 'LOC']","with all of the failed “experts” weighing in, does anybody really believe that talks and dialogue would be going on between north and south korea right now if i wasn’t firm, strong and willing to commit our total “might” against the north. fools, but talks are a good thing!"
9.48881e+17,so beautiful....show this picture to the nfl players who still kneel! ,100807,26681,2018-04-01 11:37:00,2018-04-01 19:37:00,2018-04-01,19:37:00,19,2018,4,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",70,0.0,['NFL'],['ORG'],so beautiful....show this picture to the nfl players who still kneel! 
9.48944e+17,"dow just crashes through 25,000. congrats! big cuts in unnecessary regulations continuing.",99915,18325,2018-04-01 15:48:00,2018-04-01 23:48:00,2018-04-01,23:48:00,23,2018,4,"{'neg': 0.138, 'neu': 0.629, 'pos': 0.232, 'compound': 0.3595}",90,0.3595,"['25,000']",['CARDINAL'],"dow just crashes through 25,000. congrats! big cuts in unnecessary regulations continuing."
9.49066e+17,"thank you to the great republican senators who showed up to our mtg on immigration reform. we must build the wall, stop illegal immigration, end chain migration &amp, cancel the visa lottery. the current system is unsafe &amp, unfair to the great people of our country - time for change!",116304,23628,2018-04-01 23:53:00,2018-04-02 07:53:00,2018-04-02,07:53:00,7,2018,4,"{'neg': 0.175, 'neu': 0.657, 'pos': 0.167, 'compound': 0.2714}",287,0.2714,"['Republican', 'WALL']","['NORP', 'ORG']","thank you to the great republican senators who showed up to our mtg on immigration reform. we must build the wall, stop illegal immigration, end chain migration &amp, cancel the visa lottery. the current system is unsafe &amp, unfair to the great people of our country - time for change!"
9.49071e+17,making america great again! ,79061,17547,2018-05-01 00:11:00,2018-05-01 08:11:00,2018-05-01,08:11:00,8,2018,5,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.406, 'pos': 0.594, 'compound': 0.6588}",28,0.6588,[],[],making america great again! 
9.49127e+17,"i authorized zero access to white house (actually turned him down many times) for author of phony book! i never spoke to him for book. full of lies, misrepresentations and sources that don’t exist. look at this guy’s past and watch what happens to him and sloppy steve!",84431,18374,2018-05-01 03:52:00,2018-05-01 11:52:00,2018-05-01,11:52:00,11,2018,5,"{'neg': 0.07, 'neu': 0.93, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5242}",269,-0.5242,"['White House', 'Sloppy Steve']","['ORG', 'PERSON']","i authorized zero access to white house (actually turned him down many times) for author of phony book! i never spoke to him for book. full of lies, misrepresentations and sources that don’t exist. look at this guy’s past and watch what happens to him and sloppy steve!"
9.49129e+17,"the fake news media barely mentions the fact that the stock market just hit another new record and that business in the u.s. is booming...but the people know! can you imagine if “o” was president and had these numbers - would be biggest story on earth! dow now over 25,000.",109266,21941,2018-05-01 04:04:00,2018-05-01 12:04:00,2018-05-01,12:04:00,12,2018,5,"{'neg': 0.071, 'neu': 0.929, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5696}",273,-0.5696,"['U.S.', '25,000']","['GPE', 'CARDINAL']","the fake news media barely mentions the fact that the stock market just hit another new record and that business in the u.s. is booming...but the people know! can you imagine if “o” was president and had these numbers - would be biggest story on earth! dow now over 25,000."
9.49243e+17,"dow goes from 18,589 on november 9, 2016, to 25,075 today, for a new all-time record. jumped 1000 points in last 5 weeks, record fastest 1000 point move in history. this is all about the make america great again agenda! jobs, jobs, jobs. six trillion dollars in value created!",104714,21478,2018-05-01 11:35:00,2018-05-01 19:35:00,2018-05-01,19:35:00,19,2018,5,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.829, 'pos': 0.171, 'compound': 0.8436}",276,0.8436,"['18,589', 'November 9, 2016', '25,075', 'today', '1000', 'last 5 weeks', '1000', 'the Make America Great', 'Six trillion dollars']","['CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'CARDINAL', 'LOC', 'MONEY']","dow goes from 18,589 on november 9, 2016, to 25,075 today, for a new all-time record. jumped 1000 points in last 5 weeks, record fastest 1000 point move in history. this is all about the make america great again agenda! jobs, jobs, jobs. six trillion dollars in value created!"
9.49288e+17,"well, now that collusion with russia is proving to be a total hoax and the only collusion is with hillary clinton and the fbi/russia, the fake news media (mainstream) and this phony new book are hitting out at every new front imaginable. they should try winning an election. sad!",123001,25324,2018-05-01 14:32:00,2018-05-01 22:32:00,2018-05-01,22:32:00,22,2018,5,"{'neg': 0.15, 'neu': 0.753, 'pos': 0.096, 'compound': -0.4753}",279,-0.4753,"['Russia', 'Hillary Clinton', 'FBI', 'Russia', 'the Fake News Media']","['GPE', 'PERSON', 'ORG', 'GPE', 'ORG']","well, now that collusion with russia is proving to be a total hoax and the only collusion is with hillary clinton and the fbi/russia, the fake news media (mainstream) and this phony new book are hitting out at every new front imaginable. they should try winning an election. sad!"
9.49303e+17,the mercer family recently dumped the leaker known as sloppy steve bannon. smart!,66381,12265,2018-05-01 15:34:00,2018-05-01 23:34:00,2018-05-01,23:34:00,23,2018,5,"{'neg': 0.165, 'neu': 0.671, 'pos': 0.165, 'compound': 0.0}",81,0.0,['Steve Bannon'],['PERSON'],the mercer family recently dumped the leaker known as sloppy steve bannon. smart!
9.49496e+17,good idea rand! ,100976,23528,2018-06-01 04:19:00,2018-06-01 12:19:00,2018-06-01,12:19:00,12,2018,6,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.385, 'pos': 0.615, 'compound': 0.4926}",16,0.4926,['Rand'],['ORG'],good idea rand! 
9.49499e+17,"michael wolff is a total loser who made up stories in order to sell this really boring and untruthful book. he used sloppy steve bannon, who cried when he got fired and begged for his job. now sloppy steve has been dumped like a dog by almost everyone. too bad! ",73499,18306,2018-06-01 04:32:00,2018-06-01 12:32:00,2018-06-01,12:32:00,12,2018,6,"{'neg': 0.297, 'neu': 0.662, 'pos': 0.04, 'compound': -0.9425}",262,-0.9425,"['Michael Wolff', 'Steve Bannon', 'Sloppy Steve']","['PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON']","michael wolff is a total loser who made up stories in order to sell this really boring and untruthful book. he used sloppy steve bannon, who cried when he got fired and begged for his job. now sloppy steve has been dumped like a dog by almost everyone. too bad! "
9.49609e+17,"the african american unemployment rate fell to 6.8%, the lowest rate in 45 years. i am so happy about this news! and, in the washington post (of all places), headline states, “trumps first year jobs numbers were very, very good.”",122595,25626,2018-06-01 11:49:00,2018-06-01 19:49:00,2018-06-01,19:49:00,19,2018,6,"{'neg': 0.124, 'neu': 0.774, 'pos': 0.102, 'compound': 0.1364}",229,0.1364,"['African American', '6.8%', '45 years', 'the Washington Post', 'Trumps', 'first year']","['NORP', 'PERCENT', 'DATE', 'ORG', 'PERSON', 'DATE']","the african american unemployment rate fell to 6.8%, the lowest rate in 45 years. i am so happy about this news! and, in the washington post (of all places), headline states, “trumps first year jobs numbers were very, very good.”"
9.49611e+17,"brian ross, the reporter who made a fraudulent live newscast about me that drove the stock market down 350 points (billions of dollars), was suspended for a month but is now back at abc news in a lower capacity. he is no longer allowed to report on trump. should have been fired!",100329,18049,2018-06-01 11:57:00,2018-06-01 19:57:00,2018-06-01,19:57:00,19,2018,6,"{'neg': 0.254, 'neu': 0.746, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.9318}",279,-0.9318,"['Brian Ross', '350', 'billions of dollars', 'a month', 'ABC NEWS', 'Trump']","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL', 'MONEY', 'DATE', 'ORG', 'ORG']","brian ross, the reporter who made a fraudulent live newscast about me that drove the stock market down 350 points (billions of dollars), was suspended for a month but is now back at abc news in a lower capacity. he is no longer allowed to report on trump. should have been fired!"
9.49616e+17,"now that russian collusion, after one year of intense study, has proven to be a total hoax on the american public, the democrats and their lapdogs, the fake news mainstream media, are taking out the old ronald reagan playbook and screaming mental stability and intelligence.....",124638,27214,2018-06-01 12:19:00,2018-06-01 20:19:00,2018-06-01,20:19:00,20,2018,6,"{'neg': 0.159, 'neu': 0.815, 'pos': 0.026, 'compound': -0.7579}",278,-0.7579,"['Russian', 'one year', 'American', 'Democrats', 'the Fake News Mainstream Media', 'Ronald Reagan']","['NORP', 'DATE', 'NORP', 'NORP', 'ORG', 'PERSON']","now that russian collusion, after one year of intense study, has proven to be a total hoax on the american public, the democrats and their lapdogs, the fake news mainstream media, are taking out the old ronald reagan playbook and screaming mental stability and intelligence....."
9.49618e+17,"....actually, throughout my life, my two greatest assets have been mental stability and being, like, really smart. crooked hillary clinton also played these cards very hard and, as everyone knows, went down in flames. i went from very successful businessman, to top t.v. star.....",113501,28326,2018-06-01 12:27:00,2018-06-01 20:27:00,2018-06-01,20:27:00,20,2018,6,"{'neg': 0.03, 'neu': 0.613, 'pos': 0.358, 'compound': 0.9567}",280,0.9567,"['two', 'Hillary Clinton', 'T.V. Star']","['CARDINAL', 'PERSON', 'ORG']","....actually, throughout my life, my two greatest assets have been mental stability and being, like, really smart. crooked hillary clinton also played these cards very hard and, as everyone knows, went down in flames. i went from very successful businessman, to top t.v. star....."
9.49619e+17,"....to president of the united states (on my first try). i think that would qualify as not smart, but genius....and a very stable genius at that!",119593,26632,2018-06-01 12:30:00,2018-06-01 20:30:00,2018-06-01,20:30:00,20,2018,6,"{'neg': 0.058, 'neu': 0.748, 'pos': 0.194, 'compound': 0.5862}",145,0.5862,"['the United States', 'first']","['GPE', 'ORDINAL']","....to president of the united states (on my first try). i think that would qualify as not smart, but genius....and a very stable genius at that!"
9.50012e+17,"leaving camp david for the white house. great meetings with the cabinet and military on many very important subjects including border security &amp, the desperately needed wall, the ever increasing drug and opioid problem, infrastructure, military, budget, trade and daca.",68901,12216,2018-07-01 14:33:00,2018-07-01 22:33:00,2018-07-01,22:33:00,22,2018,7,"{'neg': 0.108, 'neu': 0.716, 'pos': 0.176, 'compound': 0.5095}",272,0.5095,"['the White House', 'Cabinet', 'Border Security &amp', 'Drug', 'Opioid Problem', 'Infrastructure', 'DACA']","['ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'GPE', 'GPE', 'ORG']","leaving camp david for the white house. great meetings with the cabinet and military on many very important subjects including border security &amp, the desperately needed wall, the ever increasing drug and opioid problem, infrastructure, military, budget, trade and daca."
9.50014e+17,"i’ve had to put up with the fake news from the first day i announced that i would be running for president. now i have to put up with a fake book, written by a totally discredited author. ronald reagan had the same problem and handled it well. so will i!",129890,24634,2018-07-01 14:40:00,2018-07-01 22:40:00,2018-07-01,22:40:00,22,2018,7,"{'neg': 0.223, 'neu': 0.739, 'pos': 0.038, 'compound': -0.883}",254,-0.883,"['the Fake News', 'the first day', 'Ronald Reagan']","['ORG', 'DATE', 'PERSON']","i’ve had to put up with the fake news from the first day i announced that i would be running for president. now i have to put up with a fake book, written by a totally discredited author. ronald reagan had the same problem and handled it well. so will i!"
9.50023e+17,jake tapper of fake news cnn just got destroyed in his interview with stephen miller of the trump administration. watch the hatred and unfairness of this cnn flunky!,102009,22489,2018-07-01 15:15:00,2018-07-01 23:15:00,2018-07-01,23:15:00,23,2018,7,"{'neg': 0.362, 'neu': 0.638, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.9273}",165,-0.9273,"['Jake Tapper', 'Fake News', 'CNN', 'Stephen Miller', 'the Trump Administration', 'CNN']","['PERSON', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'PERSON', 'ORG', 'ORG']",jake tapper of fake news cnn just got destroyed in his interview with stephen miller of the trump administration. watch the hatred and unfairness of this cnn flunky!
9.50104e+17,"the fake news awards, those going to the most corrupt &amp, biased of the mainstream media, will be presented to the losers on wednesday, january 17th, rather than this coming monday. the interest in, and importance of, these awards is far greater than anyone could have anticipated!",126448,28946,2018-07-01 20:35:00,2018-07-02 04:35:00,2018-07-02,04:35:00,4,2018,7,"{'neg': 0.143, 'neu': 0.627, 'pos': 0.23, 'compound': 0.6628}",283,0.6628,"['the Mainstream Media', 'Wednesday, January 17th', 'this coming Monday']","['ORG', 'DATE', 'DATE']","the fake news awards, those going to the most corrupt &amp, biased of the mainstream media, will be presented to the losers on wednesday, january 17th, rather than this coming monday. the interest in, and importance of, these awards is far greater than anyone could have anticipated!"
9.50105e+17,"the stock market has been creating tremendous benefits for our country in the form of not only record setting stock prices, but present and future jobs, jobs, jobs. seven trillion dollars of value created since our big election win!",84850,15850,2018-07-01 20:42:00,2018-07-02 04:42:00,2018-07-02,04:42:00,4,2018,7,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.701, 'pos': 0.299, 'compound': 0.9259}",232,0.9259,['Seven TRILLION dollars'],['MONEY'],"the stock market has been creating tremendous benefits for our country in the form of not only record setting stock prices, but present and future jobs, jobs, jobs. seven trillion dollars of value created since our big election win!"
9.50206e+17,"“his is turning out to be an enormously consequential presidency. so much so that, despite my own frustration over his missteps, there has never been a day when i wished hillary clinton were president. not one. indeed, as trump’s accomplishments accumulate, the mere thought of...",70013,13215,2018-08-01 03:23:00,2018-08-01 11:23:00,2018-08-01,11:23:00,11,2018,8,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.943, 'pos': 0.057, 'compound': 0.3724}",280,0.3724,"['a day', 'Hillary Clinton', 'Trump']","['DATE', 'PERSON', 'ORG']","“his is turning out to be an enormously consequential presidency. so much so that, despite my own frustration over his missteps, there has never been a day when i wished hillary clinton were president. not one. indeed, as trump’s accomplishments accumulate, the mere thought of..."
9.50207e+17,"...clinton in the wh, doubling down on barack obama’s failed policies, washes away any doubts that america made the right choice. this was truly a change election — and the changes trump is bringing are far-reaching &amp, necessary.” thank you michael goodwin! ",70174,14702,2018-08-01 03:24:00,2018-08-01 11:24:00,2018-08-01,11:24:00,11,2018,8,"{'neg': 0.123, 'neu': 0.763, 'pos': 0.114, 'compound': -0.1007}",261,-0.1007,"['Clinton', 'Barack Obama', 'America', 'Michael Goodwin']","['PERSON', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'GPE', 'PERSON']","...clinton in the wh, doubling down on barack obama’s failed policies, washes away any doubts that america made the right choice. this was truly a change election — and the changes trump is bringing are far-reaching &amp, necessary.” thank you michael goodwin! "
9.50444e+17,can’t wait to be back in the amazing state of tennessee to address the 99th american @farmbureau federation’s annual convention in nashville! #afbf18on my way now - join me live at 4:00pme:  ,45911,7989,2018-08-01 19:06:00,2018-08-02 03:06:00,2018-08-02,03:06:00,3,2018,8,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.822, 'pos': 0.178, 'compound': 0.7424}",191,0.7424,"['Tennessee', '99th', 'American @FarmBureau Federation', 'Annual Convention', 'Nashville']","['GPE', 'ORDINAL', 'ORG', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'GPE']",can’t wait to be back in the amazing state of tennessee to address the 99th american  federation’s annual convention in nashville! #afbf18on my way now - join me live at 4:00pme:  
9.50502e+17,we have been working every day to deliver for america’s farmers just as they work every day to deliver for us. #afbf18 ,49232,9116,2018-08-01 22:58:00,2018-08-02 06:58:00,2018-08-02,06:58:00,6,2018,8,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",119,0.0,"['DELIVER for America', 'every day', 'US']","['ORG', 'DATE', 'GPE']",we have been working every day to deliver for america’s farmers just as they work every day to deliver for us. #afbf18 
9.50502e+17,"in every decision we make, we are honoring america’s proud farming legacy. years of crushing taxes, crippling regs, &amp, corrupt politics left our communities hurting, our economy stagnant, &amp, millions of hardworking americans completely forgotten. but they are not forgotten anymore! ",69129,14128,2018-08-01 22:59:00,2018-08-02 06:59:00,2018-08-02,06:59:00,6,2018,8,"{'neg': 0.173, 'neu': 0.661, 'pos': 0.166, 'compound': -0.0905}",289,-0.0905,"['America', 'millions', 'Americans']","['GPE', 'CARDINAL', 'NORP']","in every decision we make, we are honoring america’s proud farming legacy. years of crushing taxes, crippling regs, &amp, corrupt politics left our communities hurting, our economy stagnant, &amp, millions of hardworking americans completely forgotten. but they are not forgotten anymore! "
9.50507e+17,"we are fighting for our farmers, for our country, and for our great american flag. we want our flag respected - and we want our national anthem respected also! ",89774,17493,2018-08-01 23:19:00,2018-08-02 07:19:00,2018-08-02,07:19:00,7,2018,8,"{'neg': 0.065, 'neu': 0.573, 'pos': 0.362, 'compound': 0.8866}",160,0.8866,[],[],"we are fighting for our farmers, for our country, and for our great american flag. we want our flag respected - and we want our national anthem respected also! "
9.50777e+17,"on behalf of the american people, thank you to our incredible law enforcement officers. as president of the united states - i will fight for you, and i will never, ever let you down. now, more than ever, we must support the men and women in blue! #lawenforcementappreciationday ",96590,21627,2018-09-01 17:11:00,2018-09-02 01:11:00,2018-09-02,01:11:00,1,2018,9,"{'neg': 0.049, 'neu': 0.779, 'pos': 0.171, 'compound': 0.7525}",278,0.7525,"['American', 'the United States']","['NORP', 'GPE']","on behalf of the american people, thank you to our incredible law enforcement officers. as president of the united states - i will fight for you, and i will never, ever let you down. now, more than ever, we must support the men and women in blue! #lawenforcementappreciationday "
9.50824e+17,"it was my great honor to sign h.r. 267, the “martin luther king, jr. national historical park act,” which redesignates the martin luther king, junior, national historic site in the state of georgia as the martin luther king, jr. national historical park.  ",62081,13524,2018-09-01 20:17:00,2018-09-02 04:17:00,2018-09-02,04:17:00,4,2018,9,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.846, 'pos': 0.154, 'compound': 0.8074}",256,0.8074,"['H.R. 267', 'Martin Luther King', 'National Historical Park Act', 'Martin Luther King', 'Junior', 'the State of Georgia', 'Martin Luther King', 'National Historical Park']","['FAC', 'PERSON', 'LAW', 'PERSON', 'GPE', 'GPE', 'PERSON', 'FAC']","it was my great honor to sign h.r. 267, the “martin luther king, jr. national historical park act,” which redesignates the martin luther king, junior, national historic site in the state of georgia as the martin luther king, jr. national historical park.  "
9.33721e+17,happy thanksgiving! ,85109,18998,2017-11-23 15:35:00,2017-11-23 23:35:00,2017-11-23,23:35:00,23,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.2, 'pos': 0.8, 'compound': 0.6114}",20,0.6114,[],[],happy thanksgiving! 
9.27523e+17,#usa🇺🇸 #japan🇯🇵 ,61192,14328,2017-06-11 13:09:00,2017-06-11 21:09:00,2017-06-11,21:09:00,21,2017,6,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",16,0.0,"['#', 'USA', '🇸', 'Japan']","['CARDINAL', 'GPE', 'ORG', 'GPE']",#usa #japan 
8.81503e+17,#fraudnewscnn #fnn ,503063,293109,2017-02-07 13:21:00,2017-02-07 21:21:00,2017-02-07,21:21:00,21,2017,2,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",19,0.0,['FNN'],['ORG'],#fraudnewscnn #fnn 
9.23546e+17,will be another sean success! ,33921,7270,2017-10-26 13:45:00,2017-10-26 21:45:00,2017-10-26,21:45:00,21,2017,10,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.501, 'pos': 0.499, 'compound': 0.6114}",30,0.6114,[],[],will be another sean success! 
8.86262e+17,will be at the women's u.s. open today!,46130,5310,2017-07-15 16:33:00,2017-07-16 00:33:00,2017-07-16,00:33:00,0,2017,7,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",39,0.0,"[""the Women's U.S. Open""]",['FAC'],will be at the women's u.s. open today!
8.8475e+17,big wins against isis!,106595,22414,2017-11-07 12:23:00,2017-11-07 20:23:00,2017-11-07,20:23:00,20,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.429, 'pos': 0.571, 'compound': 0.6114}",22,0.6114,[],[],big wins against isis!
1.04749e+18,"blowout numbers on new jobs and, separately, services. market up!",53623,10546,2018-03-10 14:05:00,2018-03-10 22:05:00,2018-03-10,22:05:00,22,2018,3,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",65,0.0,['New Jobs'],['GPE'],"blowout numbers on new jobs and, separately, services. market up!"
9.45287e+17,merry christmas!!! ,180277,40084,2017-12-25 13:36:00,2017-12-25 21:36:00,2017-12-25,21:36:00,21,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.186, 'pos': 0.814, 'compound': 0.6571}",19,0.6571,[],[],merry christmas!!! 
9.4514e+17,merry christmas!! ,128584,26247,2017-12-25 03:51:00,2017-12-25 11:51:00,2017-12-25,11:51:00,11,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.197, 'pos': 0.803, 'compound': 0.6229}",18,0.6229,[],[],merry christmas!! 
9.47614e+17,"happy new year! we are making america great again, and much faster than anyone thought possible!",166739,32589,2017-12-31 23:43:00,2018-01-01 07:43:00,2018-01-01,07:43:00,7,2018,1,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.587, 'pos': 0.413, 'compound': 0.8968}",96,0.8968,['HAPPY NEW YEAR'],['EVENT'],"happy new year! we are making america great again, and much faster than anyone thought possible!"
9.47593e+17,"as our country rapidly grows stronger and smarter, i want to wish all of my friends, supporters, enemies, haters, and even the very dishonest fake news media, a happy and healthy new year. 2018 will be a great year for america!",169966,36017,2017-12-31 22:18:00,2018-01-01 06:18:00,2018-01-01,06:18:00,6,2018,1,"{'neg': 0.211, 'neu': 0.384, 'pos': 0.405, 'compound': 0.8915}",227,0.8915,"['Fake News Media', 'Healthy New Year', '2018', 'a great year', 'America']","['PERSON', 'EVENT', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'GPE']","as our country rapidly grows stronger and smarter, i want to wish all of my friends, supporters, enemies, haters, and even the very dishonest fake news media, a happy and healthy new year. 2018 will be a great year for america!"
9.47588e+17,"iran, the number one state of sponsored terror with numerous violations of human rights occurring on an hourly basis, has now closed down the internet so that peaceful demonstrators cannot communicate. not good!",93121,25822,2017-12-31 22:00:00,2018-01-01 06:00:00,2018-01-01,06:00:00,6,2018,1,"{'neg': 0.162, 'neu': 0.668, 'pos': 0.17, 'compound': -0.3123}",211,-0.3123,"['Iran', 'One', 'hourly']","['GPE', 'CARDINAL', 'TIME']","iran, the number one state of sponsored terror with numerous violations of human rights occurring on an hourly basis, has now closed down the internet so that peaceful demonstrators cannot communicate. not good!"
9.47545e+17,"what a year it’s been, and we're just getting started. together, we are making america great again! happy new year!! ",117478,26486,2017-12-31 19:06:00,2018-01-01 03:06:00,2018-01-01,03:06:00,3,2018,1,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.644, 'pos': 0.356, 'compound': 0.8862}",117,0.8862,"['a year', 'New Year']","['DATE', 'EVENT']","what a year it’s been, and we're just getting started. together, we are making america great again! happy new year!! "
9.47537e+17,"my deepest condolences to the victims of the terrible shooting in douglas county @dcsheriff, and their families. we love our police and law enforcement - god bless them all! #lesm",75389,14746,2017-12-31 18:36:00,2018-01-01 02:36:00,2018-01-01,02:36:00,2,2018,1,"{'neg': 0.139, 'neu': 0.619, 'pos': 0.242, 'compound': 0.6114}",179,0.6114,"['Douglas County', '#']","['GPE', 'CARDINAL']","my deepest condolences to the victims of the terrible shooting in douglas county , and their families. we love our police and law enforcement - god bless them all! #lesm"
9.47461e+17,"why would smart voters want to put democrats in congress in 2018 election when their policies will totally kill the great wealth created during the months since the election. people are much better off now not to mention isis, va, judges, strong border, 2nd a, tax cuts &amp, more?",101848,22672,2017-12-31 13:36:00,2017-12-31 21:36:00,2017-12-31,21:36:00,21,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.107, 'neu': 0.597, 'pos': 0.295, 'compound': 0.8903}",281,0.8903,"['Democrats', 'Congress', '2018', 'the months', 'ISIS', 'VA', 'Judges', 'Strong Border', ', 2nd', 'A, Tax Cuts &amp']","['NORP', 'ORG', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'GPE', 'GPE', 'GPE', 'PERSON', 'DATE', 'ORG']","why would smart voters want to put democrats in congress in 2018 election when their policies will totally kill the great wealth created during the months since the election. people are much better off now not to mention isis, va, judges, strong border, 2nd a, tax cuts &amp, more?"
9.47459e+17,"if the dems (crooked hillary) got elected, your stocks would be down 50% from values on election day. now they have a great future - and just beginning! ",60300,12123,2017-12-31 13:26:00,2017-12-31 21:26:00,2017-12-31,21:26:00,21,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.772, 'pos': 0.228, 'compound': 0.7959}",153,0.7959,"['Dems', 'Crooked Hillary', '50%', 'Election Day']","['NORP', 'PERSON', 'PERCENT', 'DATE']","if the dems (crooked hillary) got elected, your stocks would be down 50% from values on election day. now they have a great future - and just beginning! "
9.47453e+17,big protests in iran. the people are finally getting wise as to how their money and wealth is being stolen and squandered on terrorism. looks like they will not take it any longer. the usa is watching very closely for human rights violations!,100447,24828,2017-12-31 13:03:00,2017-12-31 21:03:00,2017-12-31,21:03:00,21,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.23, 'neu': 0.619, 'pos': 0.151, 'compound': -0.68}",242,-0.68,"['Iran', 'USA']","['GPE', 'GPE']",big protests in iran. the people are finally getting wise as to how their money and wealth is being stolen and squandered on terrorism. looks like they will not take it any longer. the usa is watching very closely for human rights violations!
9.47328e+17,“trump rally: stocks put 2017 in the record books” ,55336,10928,2017-12-31 04:46:00,2017-12-31 12:46:00,2017-12-31,12:46:00,12,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",51,0.0,"['Trump Rally: Stocks', '2017']","['WORK_OF_ART', 'DATE']",“trump rally: stocks put 2017 in the record books” 
9.47236e+17,"jobs are kicking in and companies are coming back to the u.s. unnecessary regulations and high taxes are being dramatically cut, and it will only get better. much more to come!",106921,20115,2017-12-30 22:42:00,2017-12-31 06:42:00,2017-12-31,06:42:00,6,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.061, 'neu': 0.846, 'pos': 0.093, 'compound': 0.2714}",176,0.2714,['U.S.'],['GPE'],"jobs are kicking in and companies are coming back to the u.s. unnecessary regulations and high taxes are being dramatically cut, and it will only get better. much more to come!"
9.47235e+17,"i use social media not because i like to, but because it is the only way to fight a very dishonest and unfair “press,” now often referred to as fake news media. phony and non-existent “sources” are being used more often than ever. many stories &amp, reports a pure fiction!",179632,42893,2017-12-30 22:36:00,2017-12-31 06:36:00,2017-12-31,06:36:00,6,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.344, 'neu': 0.656, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.9736}",273,-0.9736,"['Social Media', 'Fake News Media']","['ORG', 'ORG']","i use social media not because i like to, but because it is the only way to fight a very dishonest and unfair “press,” now often referred to as fake news media. phony and non-existent “sources” are being used more often than ever. many stories &amp, reports a pure fiction!"
9.47214e+17,"on taxes: “this is the biggest corporate rate cut ever, going back to the corporate income tax rate of roughly 80 years ago.this is a huge pro-growth stimulus for the economy. every year the obama wh overstated how the economy would grow. now real economics and jobs.” @wsj report",66759,13561,2017-12-30 21:12:00,2017-12-31 05:12:00,2017-12-31,05:12:00,5,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.042, 'neu': 0.913, 'pos': 0.046, 'compound': 0.0516}",280,0.0516,"['roughly 80 years ago', 'the Obama WH']","['DATE', 'FAC']","on taxes: “this is the biggest corporate rate cut ever, going back to the corporate income tax rate of roughly 80 years ago.this is a huge pro-growth stimulus for the economy. every year the obama wh overstated how the economy would grow. now real economics and jobs.”  report"
9.47181e+17,"oppressive regimes cannot endure forever, and the day will come when the iranian people will face a choice. the world is watching! ",72000,18952,2017-12-30 19:02:00,2017-12-31 03:02:00,2017-12-31,03:02:00,3,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.13, 'neu': 0.87, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.4574}",131,-0.4574,"['the day', 'Iranian']","['DATE', 'NORP']","oppressive regimes cannot endure forever, and the day will come when the iranian people will face a choice. the world is watching! "
9.47181e+17,"the entire world understands that the good people of iran want change, and, other than the vast military power of the united states, that iran’s people are what their leaders fear the most.... ",70367,18727,2017-12-30 19:00:00,2017-12-31 03:00:00,2017-12-31,03:00:00,3,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.082, 'neu': 0.74, 'pos': 0.179, 'compound': 0.4215}",193,0.4215,"['Iran', 'the United States', 'Iran']","['GPE', 'GPE', 'GPE']","the entire world understands that the good people of iran want change, and, other than the vast military power of the united states, that iran’s people are what their leaders fear the most.... "
9.4695e+17,"many reports of peaceful protests by iranian citizens fed up with regime’s corruption &amp, its squandering of the nation’s wealth to fund terrorism abroad. iranian govt should respect their people’s rights, including right to express themselves. the world is watching! #iranprotests",119278,33702,2017-12-30 03:42:00,2017-12-30 11:42:00,2017-12-30,11:42:00,11,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.124, 'neu': 0.688, 'pos': 0.187, 'compound': 0.5093}",283,0.5093,"['Iranian', 'corruption &amp', 'Iranian', '#']","['NORP', 'ORG', 'NORP', 'CARDINAL']","many reports of peaceful protests by iranian citizens fed up with regime’s corruption &amp, its squandering of the nation’s wealth to fund terrorism abroad. iranian govt should respect their people’s rights, including right to express themselves. the world is watching! #iranprotests"
9.46732e+17,"the democrats have been told, and fully understand, that there can be no daca without the desperately needed wall at the southern border and an end to the horrible chain migration &amp, ridiculous lottery system of immigration etc. we must protect our country at all cost!",123329,27879,2017-12-29 13:16:00,2017-12-29 21:16:00,2017-12-29,21:16:00,21,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.156, 'neu': 0.755, 'pos': 0.088, 'compound': -0.573}",272,-0.573,"['Democrats', 'Chain Migration &amp', 'Lottery System of Immigration']","['NORP', 'ORG', 'ORG']","the democrats have been told, and fully understand, that there can be no daca without the desperately needed wall at the southern border and an end to the horrible chain migration &amp, ridiculous lottery system of immigration etc. we must protect our country at all cost!"
9.46729e+17,"why is the united states post office, which is losing many billions of dollars a year, while charging amazon and others so little to deliver their packages, making amazon richer and the post office dumber and poorer? should be charging much more!",103195,22167,2017-12-29 13:04:00,2017-12-29 21:04:00,2017-12-29,21:04:00,21,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.148, 'neu': 0.66, 'pos': 0.192, 'compound': 0.3164}",246,0.3164,"['the United States Post Office', 'billions of dollars', 'Amazon', 'Amazon', 'Post Office']","['ORG', 'MONEY', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG']","why is the united states post office, which is losing many billions of dollars a year, while charging amazon and others so little to deliver their packages, making amazon richer and the post office dumber and poorer? should be charging much more!"
9.46724e+17,"while the fake news loves to talk about my so-called low approval rating, @foxandfriends just showed that my rating on dec. 28, 2017, was approximately the same as president obama on dec. 28, 2009, which was 47%...and this despite massive negative trump coverage &amp, russia hoax!",85189,18358,2017-12-29 12:46:00,2017-12-29 20:46:00,2017-12-29,20:46:00,20,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.127, 'neu': 0.697, 'pos': 0.176, 'compound': 0.5845}",281,0.5845,"['the Fake News', 'Dec. 28, 2017', 'Obama', 'Dec. 28, 2009', '47%', 'Trump coverage &amp', 'Russia']","['ORG', 'DATE', 'PERSON', 'DATE', 'CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'GPE']","while the fake news loves to talk about my so-called low approval rating,  just showed that my rating on dec. 28, 2017, was approximately the same as president obama on dec. 28, 2009, which was 47%...and this despite massive negative trump coverage &amp, russia hoax!"
9.46532e+17,"in the east, it could be the coldest new year’s eve on record. perhaps we could use a little bit of that good old global warming that our country, but not other countries, was going to pay trillions of dollars to protect against. bundle up!",174817,51213,2017-12-29 00:01:00,2017-12-29 08:01:00,2017-12-29,08:01:00,8,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.033, 'neu': 0.824, 'pos': 0.143, 'compound': 0.6533}",240,0.6533,"['East', 'the COLDEST New Year', 'Global Warming']","['LOC', 'EVENT', 'ORG']","in the east, it could be the coldest new year’s eve on record. perhaps we could use a little bit of that good old global warming that our country, but not other countries, was going to pay trillions of dollars to protect against. bundle up!"
9.4652e+17,"together, we are making america great again!  ",58339,12232,2017-12-28 23:14:00,2017-12-29 07:14:00,2017-12-29,07:14:00,7,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.539, 'pos': 0.461, 'compound': 0.729}",46,0.7290000000000001,[],[],"together, we are making america great again!  "
9.46461e+17,"i've been saying it for a long, long time. #noko ",63172,21232,2017-12-28 19:20:00,2017-12-29 03:20:00,2017-12-29,03:20:00,3,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",49,0.0,[],[],"i've been saying it for a long, long time. #noko "
9.46416e+17,caught red handed - very disappointed that china is allowing oil to go into north korea. there will never be a friendly solution to the north korea problem if this continues to happen!,106943,24926,2017-12-28 16:24:00,2017-12-29 00:24:00,2017-12-29,00:24:00,0,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.289, 'neu': 0.711, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8743}",184,-0.8743,"['China', 'North Korea', 'North Korea']","['GPE', 'GPE', 'GPE']",caught red handed - very disappointed that china is allowing oil to go into north korea. there will never be a friendly solution to the north korea problem if this continues to happen!
9.46415e+17,retail sales are at record numbers. we’ve got the economy going better than anyone ever dreamt - and you haven’t seen anything yet!,93802,16926,2017-12-28 16:18:00,2017-12-29 00:18:00,2017-12-29,00:18:00,0,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.868, 'pos': 0.132, 'compound': 0.4926}",131,0.4926,[],[],retail sales are at record numbers. we’ve got the economy going better than anyone ever dreamt - and you haven’t seen anything yet!
9.46402e+17,"vanity fair, which looks like it is on its last legs, is bending over backwards in apologizing for the minor hit they took at crooked h. anna wintour, who was all set to be amb to court of st james’s &amp, a big fundraiser for ch, is beside herself in grief &amp, begging for forgiveness!",55601,10992,2017-12-28 15:24:00,2017-12-28 23:24:00,2017-12-28,23:24:00,23,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.104, 'neu': 0.779, 'pos': 0.117, 'compound': 0.2003}",288,0.2003,"['Vanity Fair', 'Crooked H. Anna Wintour', 'Amb to Court of St James’s &amp', 'grief &amp']","['ORG', 'PERSON', 'ORG', 'ORG']","vanity fair, which looks like it is on its last legs, is bending over backwards in apologizing for the minor hit they took at crooked h. anna wintour, who was all set to be amb to court of st james’s &amp, a big fundraiser for ch, is beside herself in grief &amp, begging for forgiveness!"
9.46211e+17,"“arrests of ms-13 members, associates up 83% under trump” ",71955,16355,2017-12-28 02:46:00,2017-12-28 10:46:00,2017-12-28,10:46:00,10,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",58,0.0,"['Arrests of MS-13 Members, Associates Up 83% Under Trump']",['WORK_OF_ART'],"“arrests of ms-13 members, associates up 83% under trump” "
9.46201e+17,"“on 1/20 - the day trump was inaugurated - an estimated 35,000 isis fighters held approx 17,500 square miles of territory in both iraq and syria. as of 12/21, the u.s. military est the remaining 1,000 or so fighters occupy roughly 1,900 square miles..” @jamiejmcintyre @dcexaminer ",58623,15449,2017-12-28 02:09:00,2017-12-28 10:09:00,2017-12-28,10:09:00,10,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.054, 'neu': 0.946, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.1027}",281,-0.1027,"['1/20 - the day', 'Trump', 'an estimated 35,000', '17,500 square miles', 'Iraq', 'Syria', '12/21', 'U.S.', '1,000 or so', 'roughly 1,900 square miles']","['DATE', 'PERSON', 'CARDINAL', 'QUANTITY', 'GPE', 'GPE', 'CARDINAL', 'GPE', 'CARDINAL', 'QUANTITY']","“on 1/20 - the day trump was inaugurated - an estimated 35,000 isis fighters held approx 17,500 square miles of territory in both iraq and syria. as of 12/21, the u.s. military est the remaining 1,000 or so fighters occupy roughly 1,900 square miles..”   "
9.46157e+17,"just left west palm beach fire &amp, rescue #2. met with great men and women as representatives of those who do so much for all of us. firefighters, paramedics, first responders - what amazing people they are!",93854,14495,2017-12-27 23:11:00,2017-12-28 07:11:00,2017-12-28,07:11:00,7,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.052, 'neu': 0.697, 'pos': 0.25, 'compound': 0.8777}",209,0.8777,"['West Palm Beach Fire &amp', '2', 'first']","['ORG', 'MONEY', 'ORDINAL']","just left west palm beach fire &amp, rescue #2. met with great men and women as representatives of those who do so much for all of us. firefighters, paramedics, first responders - what amazing people they are!"
9.46151e+17,"“on 1/20 - the day trump was inaugurated - an estimated 35,000 isis fighters held approx 17,500 square miles of territory in both iraq and syria. as of 12/21, the u.s. military estimates the remaining 1,000 or so fighters occupy roughly 1,900 square miles...” via @jamiejmcintyre ",38520,12128,2017-12-27 10:49:00,2017-12-27 18:49:00,2017-12-27,18:49:00,18,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.054, 'neu': 0.946, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.1027}",280,-0.1027,"['1/20 - the day', 'Trump', 'an estimated 35,000', '17,500 square miles', 'Iraq', 'Syria', '12/21', 'U.S.', '1,000 or so', 'roughly 1,900 square miles']","['DATE', 'PERSON', 'CARDINAL', 'QUANTITY', 'GPE', 'GPE', 'CARDINAL', 'GPE', 'CARDINAL', 'QUANTITY']","“on 1/20 - the day trump was inaugurated - an estimated 35,000 isis fighters held approx 17,500 square miles of territory in both iraq and syria. as of 12/21, the u.s. military estimates the remaining 1,000 or so fighters occupy roughly 1,900 square miles...” via  "
9.45781e+17,"all signs are that business is looking really good for next year, only to be helped further by our tax cut bill. will be a great year for companies and jobs! stock market is poised for another year of success!",111975,20029,2017-12-26 22:17:00,2017-12-27 06:17:00,2017-12-27,06:17:00,6,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.042, 'neu': 0.674, 'pos': 0.284, 'compound': 0.9218}",209,0.9218,"['next year', 'a great year', 'Stock Market', 'another year', 'SUCCESS']","['DATE', 'DATE', 'PERSON', 'DATE', 'ORG']","all signs are that business is looking really good for next year, only to be helped further by our tax cut bill. will be a great year for companies and jobs! stock market is poised for another year of success!"
9.45646e+17,"wow, @foxandfrlends  “dossier is bogus. clinton campaign, dnc funded dossier. fbi cannot (after all of this time) verify claims in dossier of russia/trump collusion. fbi tainted.” and they used this crooked hillary pile of garbage as the basis for going after the trump campaign!",99848,27379,2017-12-26 13:24:00,2017-12-26 21:24:00,2017-12-26,21:24:00,21,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.899, 'pos': 0.101, 'compound': 0.7027}",279,0.7027,"['WOW', '@foxandfrlends', 'Dossier', 'Clinton Campaign', 'DNC', 'Dossier', 'FBI CANNOT', 'RUSSIA', 'FBI', 'this Crooked Hillary']","['ORG', 'ORG', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'PERSON', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'PERSON']","wow,   “dossier is bogus. clinton campaign, dnc funded dossier. fbi cannot (after all of this time) verify claims in dossier of russia/trump collusion. fbi tainted.” and they used this crooked hillary pile of garbage as the basis for going after the trump campaign!"
9.45625e+17,"based on the fact that the very unfair and unpopular individual mandate has been terminated as part of our tax cut bill, which essentially repeals (over time) obamacare, the democrats &amp, republicans will eventually come together and develop a great new healthcare plan!",93839,16116,2017-12-26 11:58:00,2017-12-26 19:58:00,2017-12-26,19:58:00,19,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.118, 'neu': 0.798, 'pos': 0.084, 'compound': -0.1742}",272,-0.1742,"['Repeals', 'ObamaCare', 'the Democrats &amp', 'Republicans', 'HealthCare']","['ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'NORP', 'ORG']","based on the fact that the very unfair and unpopular individual mandate has been terminated as part of our tax cut bill, which essentially repeals (over time) obamacare, the democrats &amp, republicans will eventually come together and develop a great new healthcare plan!"
9.45437e+17,"i hope everyone is having a great christmas, then tomorrow it’s back to work in order to make america great again (which is happening faster than anyone anticipated)!",170034,26868,2017-12-25 23:33:00,2017-12-26 07:33:00,2017-12-26,07:33:00,7,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.669, 'pos': 0.331, 'compound': 0.908}",166,0.9079999999999999,"['a great Christmas', 'tomorrow']","['DATE', 'DATE']","i hope everyone is having a great christmas, then tomorrow it’s back to work in order to make america great again (which is happening faster than anyone anticipated)!"
9.45126e+17,people are proud to be saying merry christmas again. i am proud to have led the charge against the assault of our cherished and beautiful phrase. merry christmas!!!!!,197316,42780,2017-12-25 02:56:00,2017-12-25 10:56:00,2017-12-25,10:56:00,10,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.082, 'neu': 0.434, 'pos': 0.484, 'compound': 0.9612}",166,0.9612,"['Merry', 'Christmas']","['PERSON', 'DATE']",people are proud to be saying merry christmas again. i am proud to have led the charge against the assault of our cherished and beautiful phrase. merry christmas!!!!!
9.4503e+17,"the tax cut/reform bill, including massive alaska drilling and the repeal of the highly unpopular individual mandate, brought it all together as to what an incredible year we had. don’t let the fake news convince you otherwise...and our insider polls are strong!",94399,18061,2017-12-24 20:35:00,2017-12-25 04:35:00,2017-12-25,04:35:00,4,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.065, 'neu': 0.818, 'pos': 0.117, 'compound': 0.3595}",262,0.3595,"['The Tax Cut/Reform Bill', 'Massive Alaska']","['ORG', 'ORG']","the tax cut/reform bill, including massive alaska drilling and the repeal of the highly unpopular individual mandate, brought it all together as to what an incredible year we had. don’t let the fake news convince you otherwise...and our insider polls are strong!"
9.44928e+17,"the fake news refuses to talk about how big and how strong our base is. they show fake polls just like they report fake news. despite only negative reporting, we are doing well - nobody is going to beat us. make america great again!",117694,25602,2017-12-24 13:48:00,2017-12-24 21:48:00,2017-12-24,21:48:00,21,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.154, 'neu': 0.58, 'pos': 0.266, 'compound': 0.7733}",232,0.7733,"['The Fake News', 'Fake News']","['ORG', 'WORK_OF_ART']","the fake news refuses to talk about how big and how strong our base is. they show fake polls just like they report fake news. despite only negative reporting, we are doing well - nobody is going to beat us. make america great again!"
9.44907e+17,".@foxnews-fbi’s andrew mccabe, “in addition to his wife getting all of this money from m (clinton puppet), he was using, allegedly, his fbi official email account to promote her campaign. you obviously cannot do this. these were the people who were investigating hillary clinton.”",83598,23326,2017-12-24 12:25:00,2017-12-24 20:25:00,2017-12-24,20:25:00,20,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.942, 'pos': 0.058, 'compound': 0.3818}",280,0.3818,"['Andrew McCabe', 'Clinton Puppet', 'FBI', 'Hillary Clinton']","['PERSON', 'PERSON', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",".-fbi’s andrew mccabe, “in addition to his wife getting all of this money from m (clinton puppet), he was using, allegedly, his fbi official email account to promote her campaign. you obviously cannot do this. these were the people who were investigating hillary clinton.”"
9.44704e+17,"remember, the republicans are 5-0 in congressional races this year. in senate, i said roy m would lose in alabama and supported big luther strange - and roy lost. virginia candidate was not a “trumper,” and he lost.  good republican candidates will win big!",71771,12955,2017-12-23 22:57:00,2017-12-24 06:57:00,2017-12-24,06:57:00,6,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.183, 'neu': 0.642, 'pos': 0.175, 'compound': 0.2942}",257,0.2942,"['Republicans', '5', 'Congressional', 'this year', 'Senate', 'Roy M', 'Alabama', 'Roy', 'Virginia', 'Republican']","['NORP', 'CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'DATE', 'ORG', 'PERSON', 'GPE', 'PERSON', 'GPE', 'NORP']","remember, the republicans are 5-0 in congressional races this year. in senate, i said roy m would lose in alabama and supported big luther strange - and roy lost. virginia candidate was not a “trumper,” and he lost.  good republican candidates will win big!"
9.447e+17,"the stock market is setting record after record and unemployment is at a 17 year low. so many things accomplished by the trump administration, perhaps more than any other president in first year. sadly, will never be reported correctly by the fake news media!",85863,17736,2017-12-23 22:44:00,2017-12-24 06:44:00,2017-12-24,06:44:00,6,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.214, 'neu': 0.726, 'pos': 0.06, 'compound': -0.7922}",259,-0.7922,"['17 year', 'the Trump Administration', 'first year', 'the Fake News Media']","['DATE', 'ORG', 'DATE', 'ORG']","the stock market is setting record after record and unemployment is at a 17 year low. so many things accomplished by the trump administration, perhaps more than any other president in first year. sadly, will never be reported correctly by the fake news media!"
9.44667e+17,"wow, “fbi lawyer james baker reassigned,” according to @foxnews.",58511,13341,2017-12-23 20:32:00,2017-12-24 04:32:00,2017-12-24,04:32:00,4,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.678, 'pos': 0.322, 'compound': 0.5859}",64,0.5859,"['FBI', 'James Baker']","['ORG', 'PERSON']","wow, “fbi lawyer james baker reassigned,” according to ."
9.44666e+17,fbi deputy director andrew mccabe is racing the clock to retire with full benefits. 90 days to go?!!!,61879,17323,2017-12-23 20:30:00,2017-12-24 04:30:00,2017-12-24,04:30:00,4,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.83, 'pos': 0.17, 'compound': 0.5386}",101,0.5386,"['FBI', 'Andrew McCabe', '90 days']","['ORG', 'PERSON', 'DATE']",fbi deputy director andrew mccabe is racing the clock to retire with full benefits. 90 days to go?!!!
9.44666e+17,"how can fbi deputy director andrew mccabe, the man in charge, along with leakin’ james comey, of the phony hillary clinton investigation (including her 33,000 illegally deleted emails) be given $700,000 for wife’s campaign by clinton puppets during investigation?",102458,28589,2017-12-23 20:27:00,2017-12-24 04:27:00,2017-12-24,04:27:00,4,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",263,0.0,"['FBI', 'Andrew McCabe', 'James Comey', 'Phony', 'Hillary Clinton', '33,000', '700,000', 'Clinton Puppets']","['ORG', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'CARDINAL', 'MONEY', 'PERSON']","how can fbi deputy director andrew mccabe, the man in charge, along with leakin’ james comey, of the phony hillary clinton investigation (including her 33,000 illegally deleted emails) be given $700,000 for wife’s campaign by clinton puppets during investigation?"
9.4433e+17,"remember, the most hated part of obamacare is the individual mandate, which is being terminated under our just signed tax cut bill.",101486,19795,2017-12-22 22:11:00,2017-12-23 06:11:00,2017-12-23,06:11:00,6,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.248, 'neu': 0.752, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.7645}",131,-0.7645,['ObamaCare'],['ORG'],"remember, the most hated part of obamacare is the individual mandate, which is being terminated under our just signed tax cut bill."
9.44276e+17,"congressman ron desantis is a brilliant young leader, yale and then harvard law, who would make a great governor of florida. he loves our country and is a true fighter!",61684,12852,2017-12-22 18:40:00,2017-12-23 02:40:00,2017-12-23,02:40:00,2,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.553, 'pos': 0.447, 'compound': 0.9569}",168,0.9569,"['Ron DeSantis', 'Yale', 'Harvard Law', 'Florida', 'FIGHTER']","['PERSON', 'ORG', 'PERSON', 'GPE', 'ORG']","congressman ron desantis is a brilliant young leader, yale and then harvard law, who would make a great governor of florida. he loves our country and is a true fighter!"
9.44248e+17,"95% of americans will pay less or, at worst, the same amount of taxes (mostly far less). the dems only want to raise your taxes!",87235,16668,2017-12-22 16:46:00,2017-12-23 00:46:00,2017-12-23,00:46:00,0,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.192, 'neu': 0.763, 'pos': 0.045, 'compound': -0.6403}",128,-0.6403,"['95%', 'Americans', 'Dems']","['PERCENT', 'NORP', 'NORP']","95% of americans will pay less or, at worst, the same amount of taxes (mostly far less). the dems only want to raise your taxes!"
9.44223e+17,will be signing the biggest ever tax cut and reform bill in 30 minutes in oval office. will also be signing a much needed 4 billion dollar missile defense bill.,87261,14977,2017-12-22 15:07:00,2017-12-22 23:07:00,2017-12-22,23:07:00,23,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.071, 'neu': 0.878, 'pos': 0.051, 'compound': -0.1531}",160,-0.1531,"['Tax Cut and Reform Bill', '30 minutes', 'Oval Office', '4 billion dollar']","['LAW', 'TIME', 'ORG', 'MONEY']",will be signing the biggest ever tax cut and reform bill in 30 minutes in oval office. will also be signing a much needed 4 billion dollar missile defense bill.
9.44222e+17,"with all my administration has done on legislative approvals (broke harry truman’s record), regulation cutting, judicial appointments, building military, va, tax cuts &amp, reform, record economy/stock market and so much more, i am sure great credit will be given by mainstream news?",77825,15569,2017-12-22 15:04:00,2017-12-22 23:04:00,2017-12-22,23:04:00,23,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.089, 'neu': 0.72, 'pos': 0.191, 'compound': 0.7277}",283,0.7277,"['Legislative Approvals', 'Harry Truman’s Record', 'Regulation Cutting', 'Judicial Appointments', 'Building Military', 'VA', 'TAX CUTS &amp', 'REFORM', 'Record Economy/Stock Market']","['ORG', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'ORG', 'GPE', 'GPE', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG']","with all my administration has done on legislative approvals (broke harry truman’s record), regulation cutting, judicial appointments, building military, va, tax cuts &amp, reform, record economy/stock market and so much more, i am sure great credit will be given by mainstream news?"
9.4421e+17,"“the president has accomplished some absolutely historic things during this past year.” thank you charlie kirk of turning points usa. sadly, the fake mainstream media will never talk about our accomplishments in their end of year reviews. we are compiling a long &amp, beautiful list.",72521,14661,2017-12-22 14:17:00,2017-12-22 22:17:00,2017-12-22,22:17:00,22,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.109, 'neu': 0.72, 'pos': 0.172, 'compound': 0.5267}",284,0.5267,"['this past year', 'Charlie Kirk', 'Turning Points USA', 'the Fake Mainstream Media', 'NEVER', 'their end of year']","['DATE', 'PERSON', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'DATE']","“the president has accomplished some absolutely historic things during this past year.” thank you charlie kirk of turning points usa. sadly, the fake mainstream media will never talk about our accomplishments in their end of year reviews. we are compiling a long &amp, beautiful list."
9.44192e+17,"at some point, and for the good of the country, i predict we will start working with the democrats in a bipartisan fashion. infrastructure would be a perfect place to start. after having foolishly spent $7 trillion in the middle east, it is time to start rebuilding our country!",103336,21639,2017-12-22 13:05:00,2017-12-22 21:05:00,2017-12-22,21:05:00,21,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.053, 'neu': 0.816, 'pos': 0.131, 'compound': 0.6239}",278,0.6239,"['Democrats', '$7 trillion', 'the Middle East']","['NORP', 'MONEY', 'LOC']","at some point, and for the good of the country, i predict we will start working with the democrats in a bipartisan fashion. infrastructure would be a perfect place to start. after having foolishly spent $7 trillion in the middle east, it is time to start rebuilding our country!"
9.44188e+17,so true! ,40072,7938,2017-12-22 12:50:00,2017-12-22 20:50:00,2017-12-22,20:50:00,20,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.228, 'pos': 0.772, 'compound': 0.5244}",9,0.5244,[],[],so true! 
9.44188e+17,"our big and very popular tax cut and reform bill has taken on an unexpected new source of “love” - that is big companies and corporations showering their workers with bonuses. this is a phenomenon that nobody even thought of, and now it is the rage. merry christmas!",80470,17409,2017-12-22 12:47:00,2017-12-22 20:47:00,2017-12-22,20:47:00,20,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.104, 'neu': 0.714, 'pos': 0.183, 'compound': 0.6727}",266,0.6727,"['Tax Cut and Reform Bill', 'Merry Christmas']","['LAW', 'PERSON']","our big and very popular tax cut and reform bill has taken on an unexpected new source of “love” - that is big companies and corporations showering their workers with bonuses. this is a phenomenon that nobody even thought of, and now it is the rage. merry christmas!"
9.43908e+17,"thank you to everyone who joined me at the @whitehouse yesterday. together, we are making america great again!  ",58014,10998,2017-12-21 18:16:00,2017-12-22 02:16:00,2017-12-22,02:16:00,2,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.657, 'pos': 0.343, 'compound': 0.854}",112,0.8540000000000001,"['@WhiteHouse', 'yesterday']","['ORG', 'DATE']","thank you to everyone who joined me at the  yesterday. together, we are making america great again!  "
9.43857e+17,"house democrats want a shutdown for the holidays in order to distract from the very popular, just passed, tax cuts. house republicans, don’t let this happen. pass the c.r. today and keep our government open!",74744,16128,2017-12-21 14:52:00,2017-12-21 22:52:00,2017-12-21,22:52:00,22,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.108, 'neu': 0.713, 'pos': 0.179, 'compound': 0.4376}",207,0.4376,"['House', 'Democrats', 'Tax Cuts', 'House', 'Republicans']","['ORG', 'NORP', 'PERSON', 'ORG', 'NORP']","house democrats want a shutdown for the holidays in order to distract from the very popular, just passed, tax cuts. house republicans, don’t let this happen. pass the c.r. today and keep our government open!"
9.43843e+17,home sales hit best numbers in 10 years! make america great again,72315,14122,2017-12-21 13:56:00,2017-12-21 21:56:00,2017-12-21,21:56:00,21,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.499, 'pos': 0.501, 'compound': 0.9013}",65,0.9013,['10 years'],['DATE'],home sales hit best numbers in 10 years! make america great again
9.43825e+17,was @foxandfriends just named the most influential show in news? you deserve it - three great people! the many fake news hate shows should study your formula for success!,77943,15020,2017-12-21 12:45:00,2017-12-21 20:45:00,2017-12-21,20:45:00,20,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.164, 'neu': 0.556, 'pos': 0.28, 'compound': 0.6982}",170,0.6982,['three'],['CARDINAL'],was  just named the most influential show in news? you deserve it - three great people! the many fake news hate shows should study your formula for success!
9.43819e+17,"the massive tax cuts, which the fake news media is desperate to write badly about so as to please their democrat bosses, will soon be kicking in and will speak for themselves. companies are already making big payments to workers. dems want to raise taxes, hate these big cuts!",94344,19980,2017-12-21 12:24:00,2017-12-21 20:24:00,2017-12-21,20:24:00,20,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.274, 'neu': 0.664, 'pos': 0.063, 'compound': -0.919}",276,-0.919,"['the Fake News Media', 'Democrat']","['ORG', 'NORP']","the massive tax cuts, which the fake news media is desperate to write badly about so as to please their democrat bosses, will soon be kicking in and will speak for themselves. companies are already making big payments to workers. dems want to raise taxes, hate these big cuts!"
9.43598e+17,we are making america great again! ,85379,18953,2017-12-20 21:44:00,2017-12-21 05:44:00,2017-12-21,05:44:00,5,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.532, 'pos': 0.468, 'compound': 0.6588}",35,0.6588,[],[],we are making america great again! 
9.43544e+17,we are delivering historic tax relief for the american people!#taxcutsandjobsact ,70131,16264,2017-12-20 18:09:00,2017-12-21 02:09:00,2017-12-21,02:09:00,2,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.686, 'pos': 0.314, 'compound': 0.628}",81,0.628,['American'],['NORP'],we are delivering historic tax relief for the american people!#taxcutsandjobsact 
9.43534e+17,"together, we are making america great again! ",57732,12015,2017-12-20 17:30:00,2017-12-21 01:30:00,2017-12-21,01:30:00,1,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.539, 'pos': 0.461, 'compound': 0.729}",45,0.7290000000000001,[],[],"together, we are making america great again! "
9.43521e+17,"i would like to congratulate @senatemajldr on having done a fantastic job both strategically &amp, politically on the passing in the senate of the massive tax cut &amp, reform bill. i could have not asked for a better or more talented partner. our team will go onto many more victories!",74913,14090,2017-12-20 16:39:00,2017-12-21 00:39:00,2017-12-21,00:39:00,0,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.09, 'neu': 0.685, 'pos': 0.226, 'compound': 0.8379}",286,0.8379,"['strategically &amp', 'Senate', 'the MASSIVE TAX CUT &amp', 'Reform Bill']","['ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'PERSON']","i would like to congratulate  on having done a fantastic job both strategically &amp, politically on the passing in the senate of the massive tax cut &amp, reform bill. i could have not asked for a better or more talented partner. our team will go onto many more victories!"
9.43489e+17,"the tax cuts are so large and so meaningful, and yet the fake news is working overtime to follow the lead of their friends, the defeated dems, and only demean. this is truly a case where the results will speak for themselves, starting very soon. jobs, jobs, jobs!",66856,14161,2017-12-20 14:32:00,2017-12-20 22:32:00,2017-12-20,22:32:00,22,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.143, 'neu': 0.699, 'pos': 0.158, 'compound': 0.2223}",263,0.2223,"['the Fake News', 'Dems', 'Jobs']","['ORG', 'ORG', 'NORP']","the tax cuts are so large and so meaningful, and yet the fake news is working overtime to follow the lead of their friends, the defeated dems, and only demean. this is truly a case where the results will speak for themselves, starting very soon. jobs, jobs, jobs!"
9.43363e+17,"the united states senate just passed the biggest in history tax cut and reform bill. terrible individual mandate (obamacare)repealed. goes to the house tomorrow morning for final vote. if approved, there will be a news conference at the white house at approximately 1:00 p.m.",118874,24870,2017-12-20 06:09:00,2017-12-20 14:09:00,2017-12-20,14:09:00,14,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.104, 'neu': 0.783, 'pos': 0.112, 'compound': 0.1027}",275,0.1027,"['Senate', 'Tax Cut and Reform Bill', 'House', 'tomorrow', 'The White House', 'approximately 1:00 P.M.']","['ORG', 'LAW', 'ORG', 'DATE', 'FAC', 'TIME']","the united states senate just passed the biggest in history tax cut and reform bill. terrible individual mandate (obamacare)repealed. goes to the house tomorrow morning for final vote. if approved, there will be a news conference at the white house at approximately 1:00 p.m."
9.43214e+17,"congratulations to paul ryan, kevin mccarthy, kevin brady, steve scalise, cathy mcmorris rodgers and all great house republicans who voted in favor of cutting your taxes!",108974,19499,2017-12-19 20:18:00,2017-12-20 04:18:00,2017-12-20,04:18:00,4,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.043, 'neu': 0.638, 'pos': 0.319, 'compound': 0.8883}",170,0.8883,"['Paul Ryan', 'Kevin McCarthy', 'Kevin Brady', 'Steve Scalise', 'Cathy McMorris Rodgers', 'House', 'Republicans']","['PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'ORG', 'NORP']","congratulations to paul ryan, kevin mccarthy, kevin brady, steve scalise, cathy mcmorris rodgers and all great house republicans who voted in favor of cutting your taxes!"
9.43136e+17,a  story in the @washingtonpost that i was close to “rescinding” the nomination of justice gorsuch prior to confirmation is fake news. i never even wavered and am very proud of him and the job he is doing as a justice of the u.s. supreme court. the unnamed sources don’t exist!,81173,19622,2017-12-19 15:07:00,2017-12-19 23:07:00,2017-12-19,23:07:00,23,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.064, 'neu': 0.701, 'pos': 0.235, 'compound': 0.8821}",277,0.8821,"['@washingtonpost', 'Justice Gorsuch', 'the U.S. Supreme Court']","['ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG']",a  story in the  that i was close to “rescinding” the nomination of justice gorsuch prior to confirmation is fake news. i never even wavered and am very proud of him and the job he is doing as a justice of the u.s. supreme court. the unnamed sources don’t exist!
9.43079e+17,"stocks and the economy have a long way to go after the tax cut bill is totally understood and appreciated in scope and size. immediate expensing will have a big impact. biggest tax cuts and reform ever passed. enjoy, and create many beautiful jobs!",59049,11224,2017-12-19 11:23:00,2017-12-19 19:23:00,2017-12-19,19:23:00,19,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.081, 'neu': 0.675, 'pos': 0.245, 'compound': 0.8675}",248,0.8675,"['the Tax Cut Bill', 'Biggest Tax Cuts and Reform EVER', 'JOBS']","['LAW', 'LAW', 'ORG']","stocks and the economy have a long way to go after the tax cut bill is totally understood and appreciated in scope and size. immediate expensing will have a big impact. biggest tax cuts and reform ever passed. enjoy, and create many beautiful jobs!"
9.43074e+17,dow rises 5000 points on the year for the first time ever - make america great again!,96316,19077,2017-12-19 11:04:00,2017-12-19 19:04:00,2017-12-19,19:04:00,19,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.745, 'pos': 0.255, 'compound': 0.729}",85,0.7290000000000001,"['DOW', '5000', 'THE YEAR FOR THE FIRST TIME EVER']","['ORG', 'CARDINAL', 'EVENT']",dow rises 5000 points on the year for the first time ever - make america great again!
9.42921e+17,"together, our task is to strengthen our families, to build up our communities, to serve our citizens, and to celebrate american greatness as a shining example to the world.... ",56477,13138,2017-12-19 00:54:00,2017-12-19 08:54:00,2017-12-19,08:54:00,8,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.812, 'pos': 0.188, 'compound': 0.7184}",176,0.7184,['AMERICAN'],['ORG'],"together, our task is to strengthen our families, to build up our communities, to serve our citizens, and to celebrate american greatness as a shining example to the world.... "
9.42905e+17,"with the strategy that i announced today, we are declaring that america is in the game and america is determined to win!our four pillars of national security strategy: ",51506,12330,2017-12-18 23:49:00,2017-12-19 07:49:00,2017-12-19,07:49:00,7,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.792, 'pos': 0.208, 'compound': 0.762}",168,0.762,"['today', 'AMERICA', 'AMERICA']","['DATE', 'GPE', 'GPE']","with the strategy that i announced today, we are declaring that america is in the game and america is determined to win!our four pillars of national security strategy: "
9.42884e+17,70 record closes for the dow so far this year! we have never had 70 dow records in a one year period. wow!,82981,17094,2017-12-18 22:25:00,2017-12-19 06:25:00,2017-12-19,06:25:00,6,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.827, 'pos': 0.173, 'compound': 0.658}",106,0.6579999999999999,"['70', 'NEVER', '70', 'Dow Records', 'one year']","['CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'DATE']",70 record closes for the dow so far this year! we have never had 70 dow records in a one year period. wow!
9.42882e+17,thank you maria b! ,33592,6779,2017-12-18 22:20:00,2017-12-19 06:20:00,2017-12-19,06:20:00,6,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.518, 'pos': 0.482, 'compound': 0.4199}",19,0.4199,['Maria B'],['PERSON'],thank you maria b! 
9.42882e+17,so true ivanka! ,36603,6750,2017-12-18 22:18:00,2017-12-19 06:18:00,2017-12-19,06:18:00,6,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.371, 'pos': 0.629, 'compound': 0.5244}",16,0.5244,[],[],so true ivanka! 
9.42857e+17,"as the world watches, we are days away from passing historic tax cuts for american families and businesses. it will be the biggest tax cut and tax reform in the history of our country! ",40985,7814,2017-12-18 20:40:00,2017-12-19 04:40:00,2017-12-19,04:40:00,4,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.159, 'neu': 0.841, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.7234}",185,-0.7234,"['days', 'American']","['DATE', 'NORP']","as the world watches, we are days away from passing historic tax cuts for american families and businesses. it will be the biggest tax cut and tax reform in the history of our country! "
9.42854e+17,"when the american people speak, all of us should listen. just over one year ago, you spoke loud and clear. on november 8, 2016, you voted to make america great again! ",41122,8025,2017-12-18 20:28:00,2017-12-19 04:28:00,2017-12-19,04:28:00,4,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.79, 'pos': 0.21, 'compound': 0.8283}",167,0.8283,"['American', 'US', 'one year ago', 'November 8, 2016']","['NORP', 'GPE', 'DATE', 'DATE']","when the american people speak, all of us should listen. just over one year ago, you spoke loud and clear. on november 8, 2016, you voted to make america great again! "
9.42852e+17,"over the past 11 months, i have travelled tens of thousands of miles, to visit 13 countries. i have met with more than 100 world leaders and everywhere i traveled, it was my highest privilege and greatest honor to represent the american people! ",54593,10269,2017-12-18 20:19:00,2017-12-19 04:19:00,2017-12-19,04:19:00,4,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.784, 'pos': 0.216, 'compound': 0.8805}",245,0.8805,"['the past 11 months', 'tens of thousands of miles', '13', 'more than 100', 'AMERICAN']","['DATE', 'CARDINAL', 'CARDINAL', 'CARDINAL', 'NORP']","over the past 11 months, i have travelled tens of thousands of miles, to visit 13 countries. i have met with more than 100 world leaders and everywhere i traveled, it was my highest privilege and greatest honor to represent the american people! "
9.42841e+17,our deepest sympathies and most heartfelt prayers are with the victims of the train derailment in washington state. we are closely monitoring the situation and coordinating with local authorities... ,36209,6855,2017-12-18 19:35:00,2017-12-19 03:35:00,2017-12-19,03:35:00,3,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.07, 'neu': 0.816, 'pos': 0.115, 'compound': 0.3597}",199,0.3597,['Washington State'],['GPE'],our deepest sympathies and most heartfelt prayers are with the victims of the train derailment in washington state. we are closely monitoring the situation and coordinating with local authorities... 
9.4283e+17,"my thoughts and prayers are with everyone involved in the train accident in dupont, washington. thank you to all of our wonderful first responders who are on the scene. we are currently monitoring here at the white house.",72643,12206,2017-12-18 18:51:00,2017-12-19 02:51:00,2017-12-19,02:51:00,2,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.07, 'neu': 0.79, 'pos': 0.14, 'compound': 0.4767}",221,0.4767,"['DuPont', 'Washington', 'First Responders', 'the White House']","['GPE', 'GPE', 'ORG', 'FAC']","my thoughts and prayers are with everyone involved in the train accident in dupont, washington. thank you to all of our wonderful first responders who are on the scene. we are currently monitoring here at the white house."
9.42827e+17,"the train accident that just occurred in dupont, wa shows more than ever why our soon to be submitted infrastructure plan must be approved quickly. seven trillion dollars spent in the middle east while our roads, bridges, tunnels, railways (and more) crumble! not for long!",90206,18082,2017-12-18 18:41:00,2017-12-19 02:41:00,2017-12-19,02:41:00,2,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.074, 'neu': 0.869, 'pos': 0.057, 'compound': -0.2225}",273,-0.2225,"['DuPont', 'WA', 'Seven trillion dollars', 'the Middle East']","['ORG', 'ORG', 'MONEY', 'LOC']","the train accident that just occurred in dupont, wa shows more than ever why our soon to be submitted infrastructure plan must be approved quickly. seven trillion dollars spent in the middle east while our roads, bridges, tunnels, railways (and more) crumble! not for long!"
9.42722e+17,ivanka trump will be interviewed on @foxandfriends.,37098,4817,2017-12-18 11:42:00,2017-12-18 19:42:00,2017-12-18,19:42:00,19,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",51,0.0,['Ivanka Trump'],['PERSON'],ivanka trump will be interviewed on .
9.42717e+17,"remember, republicans are 5-0 in congressional races this year. the media refuses to mention this. i said gillespie and moore would lose (for very different reasons), and they did. i also predicted  “i” would win. republicans will do well in 2018, very well! @foxandfriends",73888,14792,2017-12-18 11:23:00,2017-12-18 19:23:00,2017-12-18,19:23:00,19,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.055, 'neu': 0.776, 'pos': 0.169, 'compound': 0.68}",273,0.68,"['Republicans', '5', 'this year', 'Gillespie', 'Moore', 'Republicans', '2018']","['NORP', 'CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'GPE', 'PERSON', 'NORP', 'DATE']","remember, republicans are 5-0 in congressional races this year. the media refuses to mention this. i said gillespie and moore would lose (for very different reasons), and they did. i also predicted  “i” would win. republicans will do well in 2018, very well! "
9.42552e+17,"more than a century after conquering flight, the #wrightbrothers continue to motivate &amp, inspire americans, who never tire of exploration &amp, innovation. this great american spirit can be found in the design of every new supersonic jet and next generation:  ",51146,10241,2017-12-18 00:26:00,2017-12-18 08:26:00,2017-12-18,08:26:00,8,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.033, 'neu': 0.649, 'pos': 0.318, 'compound': 0.9382}",263,0.9382,"['More than a century', 'WrightBrothers', 'motivate &amp', 'Americans']","['DATE', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'NORP']","more than a century after conquering flight, the #wrightbrothers continue to motivate &amp, inspire americans, who never tire of exploration &amp, innovation. this great american spirit can be found in the design of every new supersonic jet and next generation:  "
