id,cleaned_text,favorites,retweets,date,tweet_datetime,date_part,time_part,hour,year,month,sentiment_score,tweet_length,compound,entity,entity_type,datetime_5mins_after,price_5mins_after,eod_price,5mins_price_diff_abs,5mins_price_diff_perc,eod_price_diff_abs,eod_price_diff_perc,5mins_price_diff_perc_magnitude,eod_price_diff_perc_magnitude
9.3534e+17,thank you rand! ,42793,9125,2017-11-28 02:50:00,2017-11-28 10:50:00,2017-11-28,10:50:00,10,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.417, 'pos': 0.583, 'compound': 0.4199}",16,0.4199,['Rand'],['ORG'],2017-11-28 10:55:00,261.085,262.87,-0.015000000000043201,-5.7449253159874376e-05,1.7699999999999818,0.006779011872845583,5.7449253159874376e-05,0.006779011872845583
8.99798e+17,"join me live from fort myer in arlington, virginia. ",36009,4891,2017-08-22 01:00:00,2017-08-22 09:00:00,2017-08-22,09:00:00,9,2017,8,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.804, 'pos': 0.196, 'compound': 0.296}",54,0.29600000000000004,"['Fort Myer', 'Arlington', 'Virginia', '➡']","['GPE', 'GPE', 'GPE', 'ORG']",2017-08-22 09:05:00,243.67,245.44,0.0,0.0,1.7700000000000102,0.007263922518159848,0.0,0.007263922518159848
8.9397e+17,thank you nicole! ,43367,8275,2017-05-08 23:01:00,2017-05-09 07:01:00,2017-05-09,07:01:00,7,2017,5,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.417, 'pos': 0.583, 'compound': 0.4199}",18,0.4199,['Nicole'],['PERSON'],2017-05-09 07:06:00,239.92,239.44,0.044999999999987494,0.00018759770713908284,-0.4350000000000023,-0.0018134445023449807,0.00018759770713908284,0.0018134445023449807
8.81977e+17,thank you to shawn steel for the nice words on .,50956,7465,2017-03-07 20:44:00,2017-03-08 04:44:00,2017-03-08,04:44:00,4,2017,3,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.629, 'pos': 0.371, 'compound': 0.6486}",56,0.6486,['Shawn Steel'],['PERSON'],2017-03-08 04:49:00,236.91333333333333,236.56,0.03333333333333144,0.00014071822582460082,-0.3199999999999932,-0.0013508949679162158,0.00014071822582460082,0.0013508949679162158
8.77846e+17,great night in iowa - special people. thank you!,56446,8039,2017-06-22 11:11:00,2017-06-22 19:11:00,2017-06-22,19:11:00,19,2017,6,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.343, 'pos': 0.657, 'compound': 0.8622}",48,0.8622,"['night', 'Iowa']","['TIME', 'GPE']",2017-06-22 19:16:00,242.905,242.84,0.025000000000005684,0.00010293148880107742,-0.03999999999999204,-0.00016469038208165367,0.00010293148880107742,0.00016469038208165367
8.78725e+17,make america great again!,134210,36346,2017-06-24 21:23:00,2017-06-25 05:23:00,2017-06-25,05:23:00,5,2017,6,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.406, 'pos': 0.594, 'compound': 0.6588}",25,0.6588,[],[],2017-06-25 05:28:00,243.32123809523807,243.4042857142857,0.00047619047614944066,1.9570482700355267e-06,0.08352380952376848,0.00034326626659364354,1.9570482700355267e-06,0.00034326626659364354
8.74084e+17,"my daughter, ivanka, will be on  tomorrow morning. enjoy!",50169,6877,2017-12-06 02:02:00,2017-12-06 10:02:00,2017-12-06,10:02:00,10,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.72, 'pos': 0.28, 'compound': 0.5411}",71,0.5411,['Ivanka'],['PERSON'],2017-12-06 10:07:00,263.309,263.24,-0.16599999999999682,-0.0006300408008349817,-0.23500000000001364,-0.0008919252300977839,0.0006300408008349817,0.0008919252300977839
8.62999e+17,the fake media is working overtime today!,65939,15809,2017-12-05 11:53:00,2017-12-05 19:53:00,2017-12-05,19:53:00,19,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.361, 'neu': 0.639, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5255}",41,-0.5255,['today'],['DATE'],2017-12-05 19:58:00,263.355,263.19,-0.01833333333331666,-6.960967954228468e-05,-0.18333333333333712,-0.0006960967954234943,6.960967954228468e-05,0.0006960967954234943
8.60089e+17,congratulations to  on its unbelievable ratings hike.,31683,5238,2017-04-05 11:07:00,2017-04-05 19:07:00,2017-04-05,19:07:00,19,2017,4,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.513, 'pos': 0.487, 'compound': 0.6908}",67,0.6908,[],[],2017-04-05 19:12:00,234.546,234.78,-0.02400000000000091,-0.00010231487402481523,0.21000000000000796,0.0008952551477171333,0.00010231487402481523,0.0008952551477171333
8.52985e+17,weekly address-  ,28250,5616,2017-04-14 20:41:00,2017-04-15 04:41:00,2017-04-15,04:41:00,4,2017,4,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",17,0.0,['Weekly'],['DATE'],2017-04-15 04:46:00,232.50590416666665,232.50400000000002,-1.0416666640367112e-05,-4.480172755619787e-08,-0.0019145833332743223,-8.234557545365624e-06,4.480172755619787e-08,8.234557545365624e-06
8.32375e+17,'trump signs bill undoing obama coal mining rule' ,79427,15157,2017-02-16 23:44:00,2017-02-17 07:44:00,2017-02-17,07:44:00,7,2017,2,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",50,0.0,['Obama'],['ORG'],2017-02-17 07:49:00,234.25,235.09,0.030000000000001137,0.00012808470668602655,0.8700000000000045,0.0037144564938946484,0.00012808470668602655,0.0037144564938946484
1.0651e+18,america first!,157446,34373,2018-11-21 04:40:00,2018-11-21 12:40:00,2018-11-21,12:40:00,12,2018,11,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",14,0.0,[],[],2018-11-21 12:45:00,266.6629,265.02,0.16289999999997917,0.0006112570356472014,-1.4800000000000182,-0.005553470919324646,0.0006112570356472014,0.005553470919324646
1.05848e+18,"jobs, jobs, jobs! #maga ",50814,12836,2018-02-11 22:14:00,2018-02-12 06:14:00,2018-02-12,06:14:00,6,2018,2,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",24,0.0,"['JOBS', 'JOBS', 'JOBS', '#']","['ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'CARDINAL']",2018-02-12 06:19:00,264.6825,265.34,0.012499999999988631,4.722862432458772e-05,0.6699999999999591,0.0025314542638000493,4.722862432458772e-05,0.0025314542638000493
1.04106e+18,thank you ! ,30020,5917,2018-09-15 20:26:00,2018-09-16 04:26:00,2018-09-16,04:26:00,4,2018,9,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.417, 'pos': 0.583, 'compound': 0.4199}",28,0.4199,[],[],2018-09-16 04:31:00,290.6593511904762,290.5542857142857,-0.0005654761905020678,-1.9454907886406804e-06,-0.1056309523809773,-0.0003634176793015341,1.9454907886406804e-06,0.0003634176793015341
1.04043e+18,gina is great! ,35481,7208,2018-09-14 02:37:00,2018-09-14 10:37:00,2018-09-14,10:37:00,10,2018,9,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.313, 'pos': 0.687, 'compound': 0.6588}",15,0.6588,['Gina'],['PERSON'],2018-09-14 10:42:00,290.98,290.88,-0.009999999999990905,-3.436544211138151e-05,-0.11000000000001364,-0.00037801986322558726,3.436544211138151e-05,0.00037801986322558726
1.03789e+18,make america great again! ,57264,13708,2018-07-09 02:38:00,2018-07-09 10:38:00,2018-07-09,10:38:00,10,2018,7,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.406, 'pos': 0.594, 'compound': 0.6588}",26,0.6588,[],[],2018-07-09 10:43:00,276.95,277.9,0.029999999999972715,0.00010833453705031314,0.9799999999999613,0.003538928210313308,0.00010833453705031314,0.003538928210313308
1.03491e+18,#stopthebias ,90355,31460,2018-08-29 20:55:00,2018-08-30 04:55:00,2018-08-30,04:55:00,4,2018,8,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",13,0.0,[],[],2018-08-30 05:00:00,290.9166666666667,290.3,0.016666666666708352,5.729345708734394e-05,-0.5999999999999659,-0.002062564455139106,5.729345708734394e-05,0.002062564455139106
1.01991e+18,really big jobs meeting today at the white house! 3 p.m.,52570,8804,2018-07-19 11:37:00,2018-07-19 19:37:00,2018-07-19,19:37:00,19,2018,7,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",56,0.0,"['today', 'the White House', '3']","['DATE', 'FAC', 'CARDINAL']",2018-07-19 19:42:00,280.18,280.0,-0.014999999999986358,-5.3534145862654074e-05,-0.19499999999999318,-0.0006959438962151115,5.3534145862654074e-05,0.0006959438962151115
9.66119e+17,"so true, thank you! ",82845,17050,2018-02-21 01:14:00,2018-02-21 09:14:00,2018-02-21,09:14:00,9,2018,2,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.245, 'pos': 0.755, 'compound': 0.7322}",20,0.7322,[],[],2018-02-21 09:19:00,271.56,270.05,0.040000000000020464,0.00014731879787868469,-1.4699999999999704,-0.005413965822038784,0.00014731879787868469,0.005413965822038784
1.01994e+18,“trump recognized russian meddling many times.” ,2539,809,2018-07-19 01:27:00,2018-07-19 09:27:00,2018-07-19,09:27:00,9,2018,7,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",48,0.0,['Russian Meddling MANY TIMES'],['ORG'],2018-07-19 09:32:00,280.39,280.0,0.11000000000001364,0.0003924646781790126,-0.2799999999999727,-0.0009990009990009019,0.0003924646781790126,0.0009990009990009019
9.48319e+17,"congratulations to senator orrin hatch on an absolutely incredible career. he has been a tremendous supporter, and i will never forget the (beyond kind) statements he has made about me as president. he is my friend and he will be greatly missed in the u.s. senate! ",53678,9691,2018-02-01 22:23:00,2018-02-02 06:23:00,2018-02-02,06:23:00,6,2018,2,"{'neg': 0.047, 'neu': 0.741, 'pos': 0.212, 'compound': 0.8255}",265,0.8255,"['Orrin Hatch', 'the U.S. Senate']","['PERSON', 'ORG']",2018-02-02 06:28:00,279.89,275.45,-0.08000000000004093,-0.0002857449012395647,-4.520000000000039,-0.016144586920027282,0.0002857449012395647,0.016144586920027282
9.4836e+17,"i will be announcing the most dishonest &amp, corrupt media awards of the year on monday at 5:00 o’clock. subjects will cover dishonesty &amp, bad reporting in various categories from the fake news media. stay tuned!",164894,39474,2018-03-01 01:05:00,2018-03-01 09:05:00,2018-03-01,09:05:00,9,2018,3,"{'neg': 0.262, 'neu': 0.658, 'pos': 0.079, 'compound': -0.8631}",216,-0.8631,"['THE MOST DISHONEST &amp', 'CORRUPT', 'THE YEAR on Monday', '5:00 o’clock', 'Dishonesty &amp', 'Bad Reporting', 'the Fake News Media']","['ORG', 'ORG', 'EVENT', 'TIME', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG']",2018-03-01 09:10:00,271.91,267.7,0.18000000000000682,0.0006624222573878732,-4.03000000000003,-0.0148308983181836,0.0006624222573878732,0.0148308983181836
9.48404e+17,"“president trump has something now he didn’t have a year ago, that is a set of accomplishments that nobody can deny. the accomplishments are there, look at his record, he has had a very significant first year.”  show,david asman &amp, ed rollins",82534,16495,2018-03-01 04:03:00,2018-03-01 12:03:00,2018-03-01,12:03:00,12,2018,3,"{'neg': 0.056, 'neu': 0.894, 'pos': 0.049, 'compound': -0.079}",254,-0.079,"['Trump', 'a year ago', 'first', 'David Asman &amp', 'Ed Rollins']","['PERSON', 'DATE', 'ORDINAL', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",2018-03-01 12:08:00,271.08,267.7,-0.040000000000020464,-0.00014753614635593267,-3.420000000000016,-0.012614340513425849,0.00014753614635593267,0.012614340513425849
9.48738e+17,"“some 40 u.s. companies have responded to president trump’s tax cut and reform victory in congress last year by handing out bonuses up to $2,000, increases in 401k matches and spending on charity, a much higher number than previously known.” ",57755,13178,2018-04-01 02:07:00,2018-04-01 10:07:00,2018-04-01,10:07:00,10,2018,4,"{'neg': 0.047, 'neu': 0.781, 'pos': 0.172, 'compound': 0.6808}",242,0.6808,"['Some 40', 'U.S.', 'Trump', 'Congress', 'last year', 'up to $2,000', '401k']","['CARDINAL', 'GPE', 'PERSON', 'ORG', 'DATE', 'MONEY', 'NORP']",2018-04-01 10:12:00,262.784575,262.72700000000003,-0.0004895833333193877,-1.8630561599673145e-06,-0.05806458333330511,-0.00022095846057831,1.8630561599673145e-06,0.00022095846057831
9.48739e+17,"stock market had another good day but, now that the tax cut bill has passed, we have tremendous upward potential. dow just short of 25,000, a number that few thought would be possible this soon into my administration. also, unemployment went down to 4.1%. only getting better!",90710,15696,2018-04-01 02:11:00,2018-04-01 10:11:00,2018-04-01,10:11:00,10,2018,4,"{'neg': 0.118, 'neu': 0.745, 'pos': 0.137, 'compound': -0.1386}",276,-0.1386,"['another good day', 'the Tax Cut Bill', '25,000', '4.1%']","['DATE', 'LAW', 'CARDINAL', 'PERCENT']",2018-04-01 10:16:00,262.7841833333333,262.72700000000003,-0.0004895833333762312,-1.863058936970369e-06,-0.05767291666666097,-0.00021946834275585772,1.863058936970369e-06,0.00021946834275585772
9.48872e+17,"many mostly democrat states refused to hand over data from the 2016 election to the commission on voter fraud. they fought hard that the commission not see their records or methods because they know that many people are voting illegally. system is rigged, must go to voter i.d.",93479,24611,2018-04-01 11:02:00,2018-04-01 19:02:00,2018-04-01,19:02:00,19,2018,4,"{'neg': 0.213, 'neu': 0.732, 'pos': 0.056, 'compound': -0.7906}",277,-0.7906,"['Democrat', '2016', 'the Commission On Voter Fraud', 'Commission', 'Voter I.D.']","['NORP', 'DATE', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG']",2018-04-01 19:07:00,262.7321895833333,262.72700000000003,-0.0004895833333762312,-1.8634276289081642e-06,-0.005679166666652691,-2.1615760493387515e-05,1.8634276289081642e-06,2.1615760493387515e-05
9.48875e+17,"as americans, you need identification, sometimes in a very strong and accurate form, for almost everything you do.....except when it comes to the most important thing, voting for the people that run your country. push hard for voter identification!",131113,31942,2018-04-01 11:11:00,2018-04-01 19:11:00,2018-04-01,19:11:00,19,2018,4,"{'neg': 0.033, 'neu': 0.826, 'pos': 0.141, 'compound': 0.6786}",248,0.6786,"['Americans', 'Voter Identification']","['NORP', 'ORG']",2018-04-01 19:16:00,262.73130833333335,262.72700000000003,-0.0004895833333193877,-1.8634338789653237e-06,-0.004797916666632318,-1.8261652014249612e-05,1.8634338789653237e-06,1.8261652014249612e-05
9.4888e+17,"with all of the failed “experts” weighing in, does anybody really believe that talks and dialogue would be going on between north and south korea right now if i wasn’t firm, strong and willing to commit our total “might” against the north. fools, but talks are a good thing!",79155,15366,2018-04-01 11:32:00,2018-04-01 19:32:00,2018-04-01,19:32:00,19,2018,4,"{'neg': 0.078, 'neu': 0.776, 'pos': 0.146, 'compound': 0.5635}",274,0.5635,"['North', 'South Korea', 'North']","['GPE', 'GPE', 'LOC']",2018-04-01 19:37:00,262.72925208333334,262.72700000000003,-0.0004895833333193877,-1.8634484630999153e-06,-0.0027416666666226774,-1.043531139348934e-05,1.8634484630999153e-06,1.043531139348934e-05
9.48881e+17,so beautiful....show this picture to the nfl players who still kneel! ,100807,26681,2018-04-01 11:37:00,2018-04-01 19:37:00,2018-04-01,19:37:00,19,2018,4,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",70,0.0,['NFL'],['ORG'],2018-04-01 19:42:00,262.7287625,262.72700000000003,-0.0004895833333193877,-1.8634519355465606e-06,-0.0022520833333032897,-8.571878903643993e-06,1.8634519355465606e-06,8.571878903643993e-06
9.49066e+17,"thank you to the great republican senators who showed up to our mtg on immigration reform. we must build the wall, stop illegal immigration, end chain migration &amp, cancel the visa lottery. the current system is unsafe &amp, unfair to the great people of our country - time for change!",116304,23628,2018-04-01 23:53:00,2018-04-02 07:53:00,2018-04-02,07:53:00,7,2018,4,"{'neg': 0.175, 'neu': 0.657, 'pos': 0.167, 'compound': 0.2714}",287,0.2714,"['Republican', 'WALL']","['NORP', 'ORG']",2018-04-02 07:58:00,262.4,257.47,-0.03000000000002956,-0.000114316198605455,-4.9599999999999795,-0.01890027816941653,0.000114316198605455,0.01890027816941653
9.49071e+17,making america great again! ,79061,17547,2018-05-01 00:11:00,2018-05-01 08:11:00,2018-05-01,08:11:00,8,2018,5,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.406, 'pos': 0.594, 'compound': 0.6588}",28,0.6588,[],[],2018-05-01 08:16:00,264.2,264.98,-0.009999999999990905,-3.7848680973433656e-05,0.7700000000000387,0.002914348434957188,3.7848680973433656e-05,0.002914348434957188
9.49127e+17,"i authorized zero access to white house (actually turned him down many times) for author of phony book! i never spoke to him for book. full of lies, misrepresentations and sources that don’t exist. look at this guy’s past and watch what happens to him and sloppy steve!",84431,18374,2018-05-01 03:52:00,2018-05-01 11:52:00,2018-05-01,11:52:00,11,2018,5,"{'neg': 0.07, 'neu': 0.93, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5242}",269,-0.5242,"['White House', 'Sloppy Steve']","['ORG', 'PERSON']",2018-05-01 11:57:00,262.84,264.98,-0.07000000000005002,-0.00026625080826157247,2.069999999999993,0.007873416758586561,0.00026625080826157247,0.007873416758586561
9.49129e+17,"the fake news media barely mentions the fact that the stock market just hit another new record and that business in the u.s. is booming...but the people know! can you imagine if “o” was president and had these numbers - would be biggest story on earth! dow now over 25,000.",109266,21941,2018-05-01 04:04:00,2018-05-01 12:04:00,2018-05-01,12:04:00,12,2018,5,"{'neg': 0.071, 'neu': 0.929, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5696}",273,-0.5696,"['U.S.', '25,000']","['GPE', 'CARDINAL']",2018-05-01 12:09:00,262.8252,264.98,0.06630000000001246,0.0002523225664288154,2.2211000000000354,0.008452996263875497,0.0002523225664288154,0.008452996263875497
9.49243e+17,"dow goes from 18,589 on november 9, 2016, to 25,075 today, for a new all-time record. jumped 1000 points in last 5 weeks, record fastest 1000 point move in history. this is all about the make america great again agenda! jobs, jobs, jobs. six trillion dollars in value created!",104714,21478,2018-05-01 11:35:00,2018-05-01 19:35:00,2018-05-01,19:35:00,19,2018,5,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.829, 'pos': 0.171, 'compound': 0.8436}",276,0.8436,"['18,589', 'November 9, 2016', '25,075', 'today', '1000', 'last 5 weeks', '1000', 'the Make America Great', 'Six trillion dollars']","['CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'CARDINAL', 'LOC', 'MONEY']",2018-05-01 19:40:00,265.25,264.98,0.01999999999998181,7.540625117815408e-05,-0.25,-0.0009425781397277834,7.540625117815408e-05,0.0009425781397277834
9.49496e+17,good idea rand! ,100976,23528,2018-06-01 04:19:00,2018-06-01 12:19:00,2018-06-01,12:19:00,12,2018,6,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.385, 'pos': 0.615, 'compound': 0.4926}",16,0.4926,['Rand'],['ORG'],2018-06-01 12:24:00,273.52,273.6,-0.08000000000004093,-0.000292397660818863,0.0,0.0,0.000292397660818863,0.0
9.49499e+17,"michael wolff is a total loser who made up stories in order to sell this really boring and untruthful book. he used sloppy steve bannon, who cried when he got fired and begged for his job. now sloppy steve has been dumped like a dog by almost everyone. too bad! ",73499,18306,2018-06-01 04:32:00,2018-06-01 12:32:00,2018-06-01,12:32:00,12,2018,6,"{'neg': 0.297, 'neu': 0.662, 'pos': 0.04, 'compound': -0.9425}",262,-0.9425,"['Michael Wolff', 'Steve Bannon', 'Sloppy Steve']","['PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON']",2018-06-01 12:37:00,273.7,273.6,0.11000000000001364,0.00040206147885527124,0.010000000000047748,3.6551043532467374e-05,0.00040206147885527124,3.6551043532467374e-05
9.49609e+17,"the african american unemployment rate fell to 6.8%, the lowest rate in 45 years. i am so happy about this news! and, in the washington post (of all places), headline states, “trumps first year jobs numbers were very, very good.”",122595,25626,2018-06-01 11:49:00,2018-06-01 19:49:00,2018-06-01,19:49:00,19,2018,6,"{'neg': 0.124, 'neu': 0.774, 'pos': 0.102, 'compound': 0.1364}",229,0.1364,"['African American', '6.8%', '45 years', 'the Washington Post', 'Trumps', 'first year']","['NORP', 'PERCENT', 'DATE', 'ORG', 'PERSON', 'DATE']",2018-06-01 19:54:00,273.9,273.6,0.01999999999998181,7.30246823425654e-05,-0.2799999999999727,-0.0010223455527967457,7.30246823425654e-05,0.0010223455527967457
9.50104e+17,"the fake news awards, those going to the most corrupt &amp, biased of the mainstream media, will be presented to the losers on wednesday, january 17th, rather than this coming monday. the interest in, and importance of, these awards is far greater than anyone could have anticipated!",126448,28946,2018-07-01 20:35:00,2018-07-02 04:35:00,2018-07-02,04:35:00,4,2018,7,"{'neg': 0.143, 'neu': 0.627, 'pos': 0.23, 'compound': 0.6628}",283,0.6628,"['the Mainstream Media', 'Wednesday, January 17th', 'this coming Monday']","['ORG', 'DATE', 'DATE']",2018-07-02 04:40:00,269.71,271.86,0.03666666666663332,0.0001359669723862203,2.1866666666666674,0.008108575807767424,0.0001359669723862203,0.008108575807767424
9.50105e+17,"the stock market has been creating tremendous benefits for our country in the form of not only record setting stock prices, but present and future jobs, jobs, jobs. seven trillion dollars of value created since our big election win!",84850,15850,2018-07-01 20:42:00,2018-07-02 04:42:00,2018-07-02,04:42:00,4,2018,7,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.701, 'pos': 0.299, 'compound': 0.9259}",232,0.9259,['Seven TRILLION dollars'],['MONEY'],2018-07-02 04:47:00,270.03,271.86,0.15999999999996817,0.0005928780523954799,1.990000000000009,0.007373920776670282,0.0005928780523954799,0.007373920776670282
9.50206e+17,"“his is turning out to be an enormously consequential presidency. so much so that, despite my own frustration over his missteps, there has never been a day when i wished hillary clinton were president. not one. indeed, as trump’s accomplishments accumulate, the mere thought of...",70013,13215,2018-08-01 03:23:00,2018-08-01 11:23:00,2018-08-01,11:23:00,11,2018,8,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.943, 'pos': 0.057, 'compound': 0.3724}",280,0.3724,"['a day', 'Hillary Clinton', 'Trump']","['DATE', 'PERSON', 'ORG']",2018-08-01 11:28:00,281.4251,280.86,-0.04490000000004102,-0.0001595196646180446,-0.6100000000000136,-0.0021671936618467814,0.0001595196646180446,0.0021671936618467814
9.50207e+17,"...clinton in the wh, doubling down on barack obama’s failed policies, washes away any doubts that america made the right choice. this was truly a change election — and the changes trump is bringing are far-reaching &amp, necessary.” thank you michael goodwin! ",70174,14702,2018-08-01 03:24:00,2018-08-01 11:24:00,2018-08-01,11:24:00,11,2018,8,"{'neg': 0.123, 'neu': 0.763, 'pos': 0.114, 'compound': -0.1007}",261,-0.1007,"['Clinton', 'Barack Obama', 'America', 'Michael Goodwin']","['PERSON', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'GPE', 'PERSON']",2018-08-01 11:29:00,281.42,280.86,-0.1099999999999568,-0.00039072212552820944,-0.6699999999999591,-0.0023798529463998834,0.00039072212552820944,0.0023798529463998834
9.50502e+17,we have been working every day to deliver for america’s farmers just as they work every day to deliver for us. #afbf18 ,49232,9116,2018-08-01 22:58:00,2018-08-02 06:58:00,2018-08-02,06:58:00,6,2018,8,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",119,0.0,"['DELIVER for America', 'every day', 'US']","['ORG', 'DATE', 'GPE']",2018-08-02 07:03:00,279.09,282.39,0.06999999999999318,0.000250878073256373,3.3700000000000045,0.012077987241058005,0.000250878073256373,0.012077987241058005
9.50502e+17,"in every decision we make, we are honoring america’s proud farming legacy. years of crushing taxes, crippling regs, &amp, corrupt politics left our communities hurting, our economy stagnant, &amp, millions of hardworking americans completely forgotten. but they are not forgotten anymore! ",69129,14128,2018-08-01 22:59:00,2018-08-02 06:59:00,2018-08-02,06:59:00,6,2018,8,"{'neg': 0.173, 'neu': 0.661, 'pos': 0.166, 'compound': -0.0905}",289,-0.0905,"['America', 'millions', 'Americans']","['GPE', 'CARDINAL', 'NORP']",2018-08-02 07:04:00,279.01,282.39,-0.01999999999998181,-7.167688062209014e-05,3.3600000000000136,0.012041715944522144,7.167688062209014e-05,0.012041715944522144
9.50507e+17,"we are fighting for our farmers, for our country, and for our great american flag. we want our flag respected - and we want our national anthem respected also! ",89774,17493,2018-08-01 23:19:00,2018-08-02 07:19:00,2018-08-02,07:19:00,7,2018,8,"{'neg': 0.065, 'neu': 0.573, 'pos': 0.362, 'compound': 0.8866}",160,0.8866,[],[],2018-08-02 07:24:00,279.19,282.39,-0.03000000000002956,-0.00010744216030380902,3.169999999999959,0.011353054938757821,0.00010744216030380902,0.011353054938757821
9.50824e+17,"it was my great honor to sign h.r. 267, the “martin luther king, jr. national historical park act,” which redesignates the martin luther king, junior, national historic site in the state of georgia as the martin luther king, jr. national historical park.  ",62081,13524,2018-09-01 20:17:00,2018-09-02 04:17:00,2018-09-02,04:17:00,4,2018,9,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.846, 'pos': 0.154, 'compound': 0.8074}",256,0.8074,"['H.R. 267', 'Martin Luther King', 'National Historical Park Act', 'Martin Luther King', 'Junior', 'the State of Georgia', 'Martin Luther King', 'National Historical Park']","['FAC', 'PERSON', 'LAW', 'PERSON', 'GPE', 'GPE', 'PERSON', 'FAC']",2018-09-02 04:22:00,290.6619875,290.832,0.0009062500000140972,3.117892481913064e-06,0.17091874999999845,0.0005880345220796513,3.117892481913064e-06,0.0005880345220796513
9.4514e+17,merry christmas!! ,128584,26247,2017-12-25 03:51:00,2017-12-25 11:51:00,2017-12-25,11:51:00,11,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.197, 'pos': 0.803, 'compound': 0.6229}",18,0.6229,[],[],2017-12-25 11:56:00,267.46208992506246,267.4560449625312,-6.244796003329611e-05,-2.3348335261357492e-07,-0.0061074104912677285,-2.2834671885650132e-05,2.3348335261357492e-07,2.2834671885650132e-05
9.47614e+17,"happy new year! we are making america great again, and much faster than anyone thought possible!",166739,32589,2017-12-31 23:43:00,2018-01-01 07:43:00,2018-01-01,07:43:00,7,2018,1,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.587, 'pos': 0.413, 'compound': 0.8968}",96,0.8968,['HAPPY NEW YEAR'],['EVENT'],2018-01-01 07:48:00,266.882425,266.887,3.125000000636646e-05,1.1709277471349292e-07,0.004606249999994816,1.7259474989233213e-05,1.1709277471349292e-07,1.7259474989233213e-05
9.47593e+17,"as our country rapidly grows stronger and smarter, i want to wish all of my friends, supporters, enemies, haters, and even the very dishonest fake news media, a happy and healthy new year. 2018 will be a great year for america!",169966,36017,2017-12-31 22:18:00,2018-01-01 06:18:00,2018-01-01,06:18:00,6,2018,1,"{'neg': 0.211, 'neu': 0.384, 'pos': 0.405, 'compound': 0.8915}",227,0.8915,"['Fake News Media', 'Healthy New Year', '2018', 'a great year', 'America']","['PERSON', 'EVENT', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'GPE']",2018-01-01 06:23:00,266.88189375,266.887,3.125000000636646e-05,1.1709300779616097e-07,0.005137499999989359,1.9250090477727233e-05,1.1709300779616097e-07,1.9250090477727233e-05
9.47588e+17,"iran, the number one state of sponsored terror with numerous violations of human rights occurring on an hourly basis, has now closed down the internet so that peaceful demonstrators cannot communicate. not good!",93121,25822,2017-12-31 22:00:00,2018-01-01 06:00:00,2018-01-01,06:00:00,6,2018,1,"{'neg': 0.162, 'neu': 0.668, 'pos': 0.17, 'compound': -0.3123}",211,-0.3123,"['Iran', 'One', 'hourly']","['GPE', 'CARDINAL', 'TIME']",2018-01-01 06:05:00,266.88178125,266.887,3.125000000636646e-05,1.1709305715496268e-07,0.005249999999989541,1.96716335979869e-05,1.1709305715496268e-07,1.96716335979869e-05
9.47328e+17,“trump rally: stocks put 2017 in the record books” ,55336,10928,2017-12-31 04:46:00,2017-12-31 12:46:00,2017-12-31,12:46:00,12,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",51,0.0,"['Trump Rally: Stocks', '2017']","['WORK_OF_ART', 'DATE']",2017-12-31 12:51:00,266.87531875,266.878,3.125000000636646e-05,1.1709589261376051e-07,0.002712499999972806,1.0163923476701851e-05,1.1709589261376051e-07,1.0163923476701851e-05
9.47236e+17,"jobs are kicking in and companies are coming back to the u.s. unnecessary regulations and high taxes are being dramatically cut, and it will only get better. much more to come!",106921,20115,2017-12-30 22:42:00,2017-12-31 06:42:00,2017-12-31,06:42:00,6,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.061, 'neu': 0.846, 'pos': 0.093, 'compound': 0.2714}",176,0.2714,['U.S.'],['GPE'],2017-12-31 06:47:00,266.87304375,266.878,3.125000000636646e-05,1.1709689081568883e-07,0.004987499999970169,1.8688663770264774e-05,1.1709689081568883e-07,1.8688663770264774e-05
9.47235e+17,"i use social media not because i like to, but because it is the only way to fight a very dishonest and unfair “press,” now often referred to as fake news media. phony and non-existent “sources” are being used more often than ever. many stories &amp, reports a pure fiction!",179632,42893,2017-12-30 22:36:00,2017-12-31 06:36:00,2017-12-31,06:36:00,6,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.344, 'neu': 0.656, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.9736}",273,-0.9736,"['Social Media', 'Fake News Media']","['ORG', 'ORG']",2017-12-31 06:41:00,266.87300625,266.878,3.125000000636646e-05,1.1709690726970936e-07,0.005024999999989177,1.88291826850927e-05,1.1709690726970936e-07,1.88291826850927e-05
9.47214e+17,"on taxes: “this is the biggest corporate rate cut ever, going back to the corporate income tax rate of roughly 80 years ago.this is a huge pro-growth stimulus for the economy. every year the obama wh overstated how the economy would grow. now real economics and jobs.”  report",66759,13561,2017-12-30 21:12:00,2017-12-31 05:12:00,2017-12-31,05:12:00,5,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.042, 'neu': 0.913, 'pos': 0.046, 'compound': 0.0516}",280,0.0516,"['roughly 80 years ago', 'the Obama WH']","['DATE', 'FAC']",2017-12-31 05:17:00,266.87248125,266.878,3.125000000636646e-05,1.170971376264821e-07,0.005549999999971078,2.079645163811805e-05,1.170971376264821e-07,2.079645163811805e-05
9.4695e+17,"many reports of peaceful protests by iranian citizens fed up with regime’s corruption &amp, its squandering of the nation’s wealth to fund terrorism abroad. iranian govt should respect their people’s rights, including right to express themselves. the world is watching! #iranprotests",119278,33702,2017-12-30 03:42:00,2017-12-30 11:42:00,2017-12-30,11:42:00,11,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.124, 'neu': 0.688, 'pos': 0.187, 'compound': 0.5093}",283,0.5093,"['Iranian', 'corruption &amp', 'Iranian', '#']","['NORP', 'ORG', 'NORP', 'CARDINAL']",2017-12-30 11:47:00,266.86591875,266.869,3.125000000636646e-05,1.1710001716261493e-07,0.003112500000042928,1.1663161707181208e-05,1.1710001716261493e-07,1.1663161707181208e-05
9.46532e+17,"in the east, it could be the coldest new year’s eve on record. perhaps we could use a little bit of that good old global warming that our country, but not other countries, was going to pay trillions of dollars to protect against. bundle up!",174817,51213,2017-12-29 00:01:00,2017-12-29 08:01:00,2017-12-29,08:01:00,8,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.033, 'neu': 0.824, 'pos': 0.143, 'compound': 0.6533}",240,0.6533,"['East', 'the COLDEST New Year', 'Global Warming']","['LOC', 'EVENT', 'ORG']",2017-12-29 08:06:00,268.74,266.86,0.07999999999998408,0.00029777413831602795,-1.8000000000000114,-0.006699918112112005,0.00029777413831602795,0.006699918112112005
9.4652e+17,"together, we are making america great again!  ",58339,12232,2017-12-28 23:14:00,2017-12-29 07:14:00,2017-12-29,07:14:00,7,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.539, 'pos': 0.461, 'compound': 0.729}",46,0.7290000000000001,[],[],2017-12-29 07:19:00,268.73,266.86,0.08000000000004093,0.00029778522240849034,-1.7899999999999636,-0.006662944351386427,0.00029778522240849034,0.006662944351386427
9.46211e+17,"“arrests of ms-13 members, associates up 83% under trump” ",71955,16355,2017-12-28 02:46:00,2017-12-28 10:46:00,2017-12-28,10:46:00,10,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",58,0.0,"['Arrests of MS-13 Members, Associates Up 83% Under Trump']",['WORK_OF_ART'],2017-12-28 10:51:00,267.575,267.87,-0.05500000000000682,-0.0002055076037813654,0.2400000000000091,0.0008967604528640627,0.0002055076037813654,0.0008967604528640627
9.46201e+17,"“on 1/20 - the day trump was inaugurated - an estimated 35,000 isis fighters held approx 17,500 square miles of territory in both iraq and syria. as of 12/21, the u.s. military est the remaining 1,000 or so fighters occupy roughly 1,900 square miles..”   ",58623,15449,2017-12-28 02:09:00,2017-12-28 10:09:00,2017-12-28,10:09:00,10,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.054, 'neu': 0.946, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.1027}",281,-0.1027,"['1/20 - the day', 'Trump', 'an estimated 35,000', '17,500 square miles', 'Iraq', 'Syria', '12/21', 'U.S.', '1,000 or so', 'roughly 1,900 square miles']","['DATE', 'PERSON', 'CARDINAL', 'QUANTITY', 'GPE', 'GPE', 'CARDINAL', 'GPE', 'CARDINAL', 'QUANTITY']",2017-12-28 10:14:00,267.608,267.87,0.038000000000010914,0.00014201891093923428,0.30000000000001137,0.0011212019284673595,0.00014201891093923428,0.0011212019284673595
9.46157e+17,"just left west palm beach fire &amp, rescue #2. met with great men and women as representatives of those who do so much for all of us. firefighters, paramedics, first responders - what amazing people they are!",93854,14495,2017-12-27 23:11:00,2017-12-28 07:11:00,2017-12-28,07:11:00,7,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.052, 'neu': 0.697, 'pos': 0.25, 'compound': 0.8777}",209,0.8777,"['West Palm Beach Fire &amp', '2', 'first']","['ORG', 'MONEY', 'ORDINAL']",2017-12-28 07:16:00,267.85,267.87,0.0,0.0,0.01999999999998181,7.466865783080758e-05,0.0,7.466865783080758e-05
9.46151e+17,"“on 1/20 - the day trump was inaugurated - an estimated 35,000 isis fighters held approx 17,500 square miles of territory in both iraq and syria. as of 12/21, the u.s. military estimates the remaining 1,000 or so fighters occupy roughly 1,900 square miles...” via  ",38520,12128,2017-12-27 10:49:00,2017-12-27 18:49:00,2017-12-27,18:49:00,18,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.054, 'neu': 0.946, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.1027}",280,-0.1027,"['1/20 - the day', 'Trump', 'an estimated 35,000', '17,500 square miles', 'Iraq', 'Syria', '12/21', 'U.S.', '1,000 or so', 'roughly 1,900 square miles']","['DATE', 'PERSON', 'CARDINAL', 'QUANTITY', 'GPE', 'GPE', 'CARDINAL', 'GPE', 'CARDINAL', 'QUANTITY']",2017-12-27 18:54:00,267.55,267.32,0.0,0.0,-0.2300000000000182,-0.0008596524014203632,0.0,0.0008596524014203632
9.45781e+17,"all signs are that business is looking really good for next year, only to be helped further by our tax cut bill. will be a great year for companies and jobs! stock market is poised for another year of success!",111975,20029,2017-12-26 22:17:00,2017-12-27 06:17:00,2017-12-27,06:17:00,6,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.042, 'neu': 0.674, 'pos': 0.284, 'compound': 0.9218}",209,0.9218,"['next year', 'a great year', 'Stock Market', 'another year', 'SUCCESS']","['DATE', 'DATE', 'PERSON', 'DATE', 'ORG']",2017-12-27 06:22:00,267.45,267.32,-0.025000000000034106,-9.346667912901805e-05,-0.15500000000002956,-0.0005794934105992319,9.346667912901805e-05,0.0005794934105992319
9.45437e+17,"i hope everyone is having a great christmas, then tomorrow it’s back to work in order to make america great again (which is happening faster than anyone anticipated)!",170034,26868,2017-12-25 23:33:00,2017-12-26 07:33:00,2017-12-26,07:33:00,7,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.669, 'pos': 0.331, 'compound': 0.908}",166,0.908,"['a great Christmas', 'tomorrow']","['DATE', 'DATE']",2017-12-26 07:38:00,266.95,267.19,-0.05000000000001137,-0.00018726591760303884,0.18999999999999773,0.0007116104868913773,0.00018726591760303884,0.0007116104868913773
9.45126e+17,people are proud to be saying merry christmas again. i am proud to have led the charge against the assault of our cherished and beautiful phrase. merry christmas!!!!!,197316,42780,2017-12-25 02:56:00,2017-12-25 10:56:00,2017-12-25,10:56:00,10,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.082, 'neu': 0.434, 'pos': 0.484, 'compound': 0.9612}",166,0.9612,"['Merry', 'Christmas']","['PERSON', 'DATE']",2017-12-25 11:01:00,267.46277685262277,267.4560449625312,-6.244796014698295e-05,-2.3348275338093613e-07,-0.006794338051690829,-2.540292352185473e-05,2.3348275338093613e-07,2.540292352185473e-05
9.4503e+17,"the tax cut/reform bill, including massive alaska drilling and the repeal of the highly unpopular individual mandate, brought it all together as to what an incredible year we had. don’t let the fake news convince you otherwise...and our insider polls are strong!",94399,18061,2017-12-24 20:35:00,2017-12-25 04:35:00,2017-12-25,04:35:00,4,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.065, 'neu': 0.818, 'pos': 0.117, 'compound': 0.3595}",262,0.3595,"['The Tax Cut/Reform Bill', 'Massive Alaska']","['ORG', 'ORG']",2017-12-25 04:40:00,267.4675353871773,267.4560449625312,-6.244796009013953e-05,-2.334785992605782e-07,-0.01155287260615978,-4.319354082388993e-05,2.334785992605782e-07,4.319354082388993e-05
9.44704e+17,"remember, the republicans are 5-0 in congressional races this year. in senate, i said roy m would lose in alabama and supported big luther strange - and roy lost. virginia candidate was not a “trumper,” and he lost.  good republican candidates will win big!",71771,12955,2017-12-23 22:57:00,2017-12-24 06:57:00,2017-12-24,06:57:00,6,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.183, 'neu': 0.642, 'pos': 0.175, 'compound': 0.2942}",257,0.2942,"['Republicans', '5', 'Congressional', 'this year', 'Senate', 'Roy M', 'Alabama', 'Roy', 'Virginia', 'Republican']","['NORP', 'CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'DATE', 'ORG', 'PERSON', 'GPE', 'PERSON', 'GPE', 'NORP']",2017-12-24 07:02:00,267.483746877602,267.4740299750208,-6.24479599764527e-05,-2.3346444831150713e-07,-0.009779350541180065,-3.656053263873383e-05,2.3346444831150713e-07,3.656053263873383e-05
9.447e+17,"the stock market is setting record after record and unemployment is at a 17 year low. so many things accomplished by the trump administration, perhaps more than any other president in first year. sadly, will never be reported correctly by the fake news media!",85863,17736,2017-12-23 22:44:00,2017-12-24 06:44:00,2017-12-24,06:44:00,6,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.214, 'neu': 0.726, 'pos': 0.06, 'compound': -0.7922}",259,-0.7922,"['17 year', 'the Trump Administration', 'first year', 'the Fake News Media']","['DATE', 'ORG', 'DATE', 'ORG']",2017-12-24 06:49:00,267.48390924229807,267.4740299750208,-6.244796003329611e-05,-2.3346430680941807e-07,-0.009941715237289372,-3.7167517644016855e-05,2.3346430680941807e-07,3.7167517644016855e-05
9.44667e+17,"wow, “fbi lawyer james baker reassigned,” according to .",58511,13341,2017-12-23 20:32:00,2017-12-24 04:32:00,2017-12-24,04:32:00,4,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.678, 'pos': 0.322, 'compound': 0.5859}",64,0.5859,"['FBI', 'James Baker']","['ORG', 'PERSON']",2017-12-24 04:37:00,267.485557868443,267.4740299750208,-6.244796003329611e-05,-2.3346286787090744e-07,-0.011590341382202496,-4.3330708276925425e-05,2.3346286787090744e-07,4.3330708276925425e-05
9.44666e+17,fbi deputy director andrew mccabe is racing the clock to retire with full benefits. 90 days to go?!!!,61879,17323,2017-12-23 20:30:00,2017-12-24 04:30:00,2017-12-24,04:30:00,4,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.83, 'pos': 0.17, 'compound': 0.5386}",101,0.5386,"['FBI', 'Andrew McCabe', '90 days']","['ORG', 'PERSON', 'DATE']",2017-12-24 04:35:00,267.485582847627,267.4740299750208,-6.244796003329611e-05,-2.3346284606894523e-07,-0.011615320566193077,-4.3424089368823813e-05,2.3346284606894523e-07,4.3424089368823813e-05
9.44666e+17,"how can fbi deputy director andrew mccabe, the man in charge, along with leakin’ james comey, of the phony hillary clinton investigation (including her 33,000 illegally deleted emails) be given $700,000 for wife’s campaign by clinton puppets during investigation?",102458,28589,2017-12-23 20:27:00,2017-12-24 04:27:00,2017-12-24,04:27:00,4,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",263,0.0,"['FBI', 'Andrew McCabe', 'James Comey', 'Phony', 'Hillary Clinton', '33,000', '700,000', 'Clinton Puppets']","['ORG', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'CARDINAL', 'MONEY', 'PERSON']",2017-12-24 04:32:00,267.485620316403,267.4740299750208,-6.244796003329611e-05,-2.334628133660095e-07,-0.011652789342235792,-4.3564160974182373e-05,2.334628133660095e-07,4.3564160974182373e-05
9.4433e+17,"remember, the most hated part of obamacare is the individual mandate, which is being terminated under our just signed tax cut bill.",101486,19795,2017-12-22 22:11:00,2017-12-23 06:11:00,2017-12-23,06:11:00,6,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.248, 'neu': 0.752, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.7645}",131,-0.7645,['ObamaCare'],['ORG'],2017-12-23 06:16:00,267.5023064113239,267.4920149875104,-6.244796009013953e-05,-2.3344825078161995e-07,-0.010353871773588708,-3.87057199446156e-05,2.3344825078161995e-07,3.87057199446156e-05
9.43598e+17,we are making america great again! ,85379,18953,2017-12-20 21:44:00,2017-12-21 05:44:00,2017-12-21,05:44:00,5,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.532, 'pos': 0.468, 'compound': 0.6588}",35,0.6588,[],[],2017-12-21 05:49:00,267.3,267.58,0.0015384615384164135,5.755594437624715e-06,0.28153846153838913,0.0010532737821159458,5.755594437624715e-06,0.0010532737821159458
9.43363e+17,"the united states senate just passed the biggest in history tax cut and reform bill. terrible individual mandate (obamacare)repealed. goes to the house tomorrow morning for final vote. if approved, there will be a news conference at the white house at approximately 1:00 p.m.",118874,24870,2017-12-20 06:09:00,2017-12-20 14:09:00,2017-12-20,14:09:00,14,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.104, 'neu': 0.783, 'pos': 0.112, 'compound': 0.1027}",275,0.1027,"['Senate', 'Tax Cut and Reform Bill', 'House', 'tomorrow', 'The White House', 'approximately 1:00 P.M.']","['ORG', 'LAW', 'ORG', 'DATE', 'FAC', 'TIME']",2017-12-20 14:14:00,267.345,267.03,0.015000000000043201,5.6110425317185506e-05,-0.30000000000001137,-0.0011222085063405207,5.6110425317185506e-05,0.0011222085063405207
9.43214e+17,"congratulations to paul ryan, kevin mccarthy, kevin brady, steve scalise, cathy mcmorris rodgers and all great house republicans who voted in favor of cutting your taxes!",108974,19499,2017-12-19 20:18:00,2017-12-20 04:18:00,2017-12-20,04:18:00,4,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.043, 'neu': 0.638, 'pos': 0.319, 'compound': 0.8883}",170,0.8883,"['Paul Ryan', 'Kevin McCarthy', 'Kevin Brady', 'Steve Scalise', 'Cathy McMorris Rodgers', 'House', 'Republicans']","['PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'ORG', 'NORP']",2017-12-20 04:23:00,268.05,267.03,0.03750000000002274,0.00013991884706878499,-0.9825000000000159,-0.0036658737932000036,0.00013991884706878499,0.0036658737932000036
9.43079e+17,"stocks and the economy have a long way to go after the tax cut bill is totally understood and appreciated in scope and size. immediate expensing will have a big impact. biggest tax cuts and reform ever passed. enjoy, and create many beautiful jobs!",59049,11224,2017-12-19 11:23:00,2017-12-19 19:23:00,2017-12-19,19:23:00,19,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.081, 'neu': 0.675, 'pos': 0.245, 'compound': 0.8675}",248,0.8675,"['the Tax Cut Bill', 'Biggest Tax Cuts and Reform EVER', 'JOBS']","['LAW', 'LAW', 'ORG']",2017-12-19 19:28:00,267.62,267.17,0.07666666666671063,0.00028655794076988387,-0.373333333333278,-0.0013954125811392972,0.00028655794076988387,0.0013954125811392972
9.43074e+17,dow rises 5000 points on the year for the first time ever - make america great again!,96316,19077,2017-12-19 11:04:00,2017-12-19 19:04:00,2017-12-19,19:04:00,19,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.745, 'pos': 0.255, 'compound': 0.729}",85,0.7290000000000001,"['DOW', '5000', 'THE YEAR FOR THE FIRST TIME EVER']","['ORG', 'CARDINAL', 'EVENT']",2017-12-19 19:09:00,267.59,267.17,0.009999999999990905,3.737200089689404e-05,-0.40999999999996817,-0.00153225203677393,3.737200089689404e-05,0.00153225203677393
9.42921e+17,"together, our task is to strengthen our families, to build up our communities, to serve our citizens, and to celebrate american greatness as a shining example to the world.... ",56477,13138,2017-12-19 00:54:00,2017-12-19 08:54:00,2017-12-19,08:54:00,8,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.812, 'pos': 0.188, 'compound': 0.7184}",176,0.7184,['AMERICAN'],['ORG'],2017-12-19 08:59:00,268.47,267.17,-0.029999999999972715,-0.00011173184357531738,-1.329999999999984,-0.004953445065176849,0.00011173184357531738,0.004953445065176849
9.42905e+17,"with the strategy that i announced today, we are declaring that america is in the game and america is determined to win!our four pillars of national security strategy: ",51506,12330,2017-12-18 23:49:00,2017-12-19 07:49:00,2017-12-19,07:49:00,7,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.792, 'pos': 0.208, 'compound': 0.762}",168,0.762,"['today', 'AMERICA', 'AMERICA']","['DATE', 'GPE', 'GPE']",2017-12-19 07:54:00,268.51,267.17,0.029999999999972715,0.00011174016686521422,-1.3100000000000023,-0.004879320619785467,0.00011174016686521422,0.004879320619785467
9.42884e+17,70 record closes for the dow so far this year! we have never had 70 dow records in a one year period. wow!,82981,17094,2017-12-18 22:25:00,2017-12-19 06:25:00,2017-12-19,06:25:00,6,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.827, 'pos': 0.173, 'compound': 0.658}",106,0.6579999999999999,"['70', 'NEVER', '70', 'Dow Records', 'one year']","['CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'DATE']",2017-12-19 06:30:00,268.41,267.17,0.020000000000038654,7.451842468064627e-05,-1.2199999999999704,-0.004545623905510527,7.451842468064627e-05,0.004545623905510527
9.42882e+17,thank you maria b! ,33592,6779,2017-12-18 22:20:00,2017-12-19 06:20:00,2017-12-19,06:20:00,6,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.518, 'pos': 0.482, 'compound': 0.4199}",19,0.4199,['Maria B'],['PERSON'],2017-12-19 06:25:00,268.39,267.17,0.029999999999972715,0.0001117901326575224,-1.1899999999999977,-0.004434341928752413,0.0001117901326575224,0.004434341928752413
9.42882e+17,so true ivanka! ,36603,6750,2017-12-18 22:18:00,2017-12-19 06:18:00,2017-12-19,06:18:00,6,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.371, 'pos': 0.629, 'compound': 0.5244}",16,0.5244,[],[],2017-12-19 06:23:00,268.37,267.17,0.0,0.0,-1.1999999999999886,-0.004471438685396984,0.0,0.004471438685396984
9.42857e+17,"as the world watches, we are days away from passing historic tax cuts for american families and businesses. it will be the biggest tax cut and tax reform in the history of our country! ",40985,7814,2017-12-18 20:40:00,2017-12-19 04:40:00,2017-12-19,04:40:00,4,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.159, 'neu': 0.841, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.7234}",185,-0.7234,"['days', 'American']","['DATE', 'NORP']",2017-12-19 04:45:00,268.47375,267.17,-0.06875000000002274,-0.00025601161827279754,-1.3725000000000023,-0.005110922852062531,0.00025601161827279754,0.005110922852062531
9.42854e+17,"when the american people speak, all of us should listen. just over one year ago, you spoke loud and clear. on november 8, 2016, you voted to make america great again! ",41122,8025,2017-12-18 20:28:00,2017-12-19 04:28:00,2017-12-19,04:28:00,4,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.79, 'pos': 0.21, 'compound': 0.8283}",167,0.8283,"['American', 'US', 'one year ago', 'November 8, 2016']","['NORP', 'GPE', 'DATE', 'DATE']",2017-12-19 04:33:00,268.57,267.17,0.0026086956521567117,9.713374507184557e-06,-1.3973913043478206,-0.005203130944382815,9.713374507184557e-06,0.005203130944382815
9.42852e+17,"over the past 11 months, i have travelled tens of thousands of miles, to visit 13 countries. i have met with more than 100 world leaders and everywhere i traveled, it was my highest privilege and greatest honor to represent the american people! ",54593,10269,2017-12-18 20:19:00,2017-12-19 04:19:00,2017-12-19,04:19:00,4,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.784, 'pos': 0.216, 'compound': 0.8805}",245,0.8805,"['the past 11 months', 'tens of thousands of miles', '13', 'more than 100', 'AMERICAN']","['DATE', 'CARDINAL', 'CARDINAL', 'CARDINAL', 'NORP']",2017-12-19 04:24:00,268.56217391304347,267.17,0.006521739130391779,2.4284497747857444e-05,-1.3856521739130585,-0.0051596462881955225,2.4284497747857444e-05,0.0051596462881955225
9.42722e+17,ivanka trump will be interviewed on .,37098,4817,2017-12-18 11:42:00,2017-12-18 19:42:00,2017-12-18,19:42:00,19,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",51,0.0,['Ivanka Trump'],['PERSON'],2017-12-18 19:47:00,268.28,268.2,0.03599999999994452,0.00013420617050127688,-0.04400000000003956,-0.00016402976394640535,0.00013420617050127688,0.00016402976394640535
9.42717e+17,"remember, republicans are 5-0 in congressional races this year. the media refuses to mention this. i said gillespie and moore would lose (for very different reasons), and they did. i also predicted  “i” would win. republicans will do well in 2018, very well! ",73888,14792,2017-12-18 11:23:00,2017-12-18 19:23:00,2017-12-18,19:23:00,19,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.055, 'neu': 0.776, 'pos': 0.169, 'compound': 0.68}",273,0.68,"['Republicans', '5', 'this year', 'Gillespie', 'Moore', 'Republicans', '2018']","['NORP', 'CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'GPE', 'PERSON', 'NORP', 'DATE']",2017-12-18 19:28:00,268.21,268.2,-0.010000000000047748,-3.7282827529817864e-05,-0.020000000000038654,-7.456565505942379e-05,3.7282827529817864e-05,7.456565505942379e-05
9.42552e+17,"more than a century after conquering flight, the #wrightbrothers continue to motivate &amp, inspire americans, who never tire of exploration &amp, innovation. this great american spirit can be found in the design of every new supersonic jet and next generation:  ",51146,10241,2017-12-18 00:26:00,2017-12-18 08:26:00,2017-12-18,08:26:00,8,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.033, 'neu': 0.649, 'pos': 0.318, 'compound': 0.9382}",263,0.9382,"['More than a century', 'WrightBrothers', 'motivate &amp', 'Americans']","['DATE', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'NORP']",2017-12-18 08:31:00,268.11,268.2,0.040000000000020464,0.00014921475733957723,0.12999999999999545,0.0004849479613533609,0.00014921475733957723,0.0004849479613533609
9.42503e+17,wonderful weekend at camp david. a very special place. a lot of very important work done. heading back to the  now. ,54110,8562,2017-12-17 21:13:00,2017-12-18 05:13:00,2017-12-18,05:13:00,5,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.659, 'pos': 0.341, 'compound': 0.831}",127,0.831,['Camp David'],['FAC'],2017-12-18 05:18:00,267.93,268.2,0.01999999999998181,7.465193535135609e-05,0.2899999999999636,0.0010824530625955118,7.465193535135609e-05,0.0010824530625955118
9.4213e+17,weekly address ,43997,10167,2017-12-16 20:31:00,2017-12-17 04:31:00,2017-12-17,04:31:00,4,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",17,0.0,[],[],2017-12-17 04:36:00,267.10960714285716,267.39285714285717,0.001532738095249897,5.738269420217017e-06,0.28478273809525945,0.0010661704582681925,5.738269420217017e-06,0.0010661704582681925
9.42123e+17,"tax cuts will increase investment in the american economy and in u.s. workers, leading to higher growth, higher wages, and more jobs! ",59442,12037,2017-12-16 20:05:00,2017-12-17 04:05:00,2017-12-17,04:05:00,4,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.108, 'neu': 0.7, 'pos': 0.191, 'compound': 0.3091}",134,0.3091,"['American', 'U.S.']","['NORP', 'GPE']",2017-12-17 04:10:00,267.1016369047619,267.39285714285717,0.001532738095249897,5.738440649553211e-06,0.29275297619051344,0.0010960421640563635,5.738440649553211e-06,0.0010960421640563635
9.41869e+17,"great job kevin, we are all proud of you! ",54860,10894,2017-12-16 03:12:00,2017-12-16 11:12:00,2017-12-16,11:12:00,11,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.483, 'pos': 0.517, 'compound': 0.8172}",42,0.8172,['Kevin'],['PERSON'],2017-12-16 11:17:00,266.7911041666667,266.95142857142855,0.001532738095249897,5.745119972428392e-06,0.16185714285711583,0.0006066846690836657,5.745119972428392e-06,0.0006066846690836657
9.4182e+17,"dow, s&amp,p 500 and nasdaq close at record highs! #maga ",48684,10153,2017-12-16 00:00:00,2017-12-16 08:00:00,2017-12-16,08:00:00,8,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",57,0.0,"['DOW', 'S&amp', '500', 'NASDAQ', '#']","['ORG', 'ORG', 'CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'CARDINAL']",2017-12-16 08:05:00,266.7322470238095,266.95142857142855,0.001532738095249897,5.746387697998934e-06,0.22071428571427987,0.0008274798285054532,5.746387697998934e-06,0.0008274798285054532
9.4179e+17,"today, it was my tremendous honor to visit marine helicopter squadron one (hmx-1) at the marine corps air facility in quantico, virginia. i am honored to serve as your commander-in-chief. on behalf of an entire nation, thank you for your sacrifice and service. we love you! ",66015,14462,2017-12-15 21:58:00,2017-12-16 05:58:00,2017-12-16,05:58:00,5,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.736, 'pos': 0.264, 'compound': 0.9406}",274,0.9406,"['Today', 'Marine Helicopter Squadron One', 'the Marine Corps Air Facility', 'Quantico', 'Virginia']","['DATE', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'GPE', 'GPE']",2017-12-16 06:03:00,266.6948482142857,266.95142857142855,0.0015327380951930536,5.747193522478412e-06,0.25811309523805903,0.0009678273892136697,5.747193522478412e-06,0.0009678273892136697
9.41418e+17,“manufacturing optimism rose to another all-time high in the latest  outlook survey” ,32408,6893,2017-12-14 21:20:00,2017-12-15 05:20:00,2017-12-15,05:20:00,5,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.774, 'pos': 0.226, 'compound': 0.5423}",98,0.5423,"['Another All-Time High', 'the Latest @ShopFloorNAM Outlook Survey']","['FAC', 'LOC']",2017-12-15 05:25:00,264.75666666666666,266.51,0.031666666666637866,0.00011962099033577435,1.7849999999999682,0.006742846349985713,0.00011962099033577435,0.006742846349985713
9.41406e+17,"in 1960, there were approximately 20,000 pages in the code of federal regulations. today there are over 185,000 pages, as seen in the roosevelt room.today, we cut the red tape! it is time to set free our dreams and make america great again! ",74535,20389,2017-12-14 20:35:00,2017-12-15 04:35:00,2017-12-15,04:35:00,4,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.052, 'neu': 0.713, 'pos': 0.235, 'compound': 0.9011}",241,0.9011,"['1960', 'approximately 20,000', 'Today', '185,000', 'the Roosevelt Room', 'Today']","['DATE', 'CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'CARDINAL', 'FAC', 'DATE']",2017-12-15 04:40:00,264.755,266.51,0.024999999999977263,9.443584029002101e-05,1.7799999999999727,0.0067238318286555075,9.443584029002101e-05,0.0067238318286555075
9.41404e+17,"when americans are free to thrive, innovate, &amp, prosper, there is no challenge too great, no task too large, &amp, no goal beyond our reach. we are a nation of explorers, pioneers, innovators &amp, inventors. we are nation of people who work hard, dream big, &amp, who never, ever give up... ",58921,13232,2017-12-14 20:27:00,2017-12-15 04:27:00,2017-12-15,04:27:00,4,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.127, 'neu': 0.635, 'pos': 0.238, 'compound': 0.7906}",295,0.7906,['Americans'],['NORP'],2017-12-15 04:32:00,264.74,266.51,-0.05000000000001137,-0.00018882888326602728,1.7199999999999704,0.00649571358434975,0.00018882888326602728,0.00649571358434975
9.41401e+17,"today, we gathered in the roosevelt room for one single reason: to cut the red tape! for many decades, an ever-growing maze of regs, rules, and restrictions has cost our country trillions of dollars, millions of jobs, countless american factories, &amp, devastated entire industries. ",48388,9921,2017-12-14 20:13:00,2017-12-15 04:13:00,2017-12-15,04:13:00,4,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.145, 'neu': 0.855, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.7978}",284,-0.7978,"['Today', 'the Roosevelt Room', 'one', 'many decades', 'trillions of dollars', 'millions', 'American']","['DATE', 'FAC', 'CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'MONEY', 'CARDINAL', 'NORP']",2017-12-15 04:18:00,264.88,266.51,0.029999999999972715,0.00011327166320548504,1.6599999999999682,0.006267698697375752,0.00011327166320548504,0.006267698697375752
9.41095e+17,thank you omarosa for your service! i wish you continued success.,72683,10942,2017-12-13 23:58:00,2017-12-14 07:58:00,2017-12-14,07:58:00,7,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.432, 'pos': 0.568, 'compound': 0.8478}",65,0.8478,['Omarosa'],['ORG'],2017-12-14 08:03:00,267.11,265.66,-0.04333333333329392,-0.00016220397774047585,-1.4933333333332826,-0.005589798617522831,0.00016220397774047585,0.005589798617522831
9.40905e+17,"the reason i originally endorsed luther strange (and his numbers went up mightily), is that i said roy moore will not be able to win the general election.  i was right! roy worked hard but the deck was stacked against him!",63126,11712,2017-12-13 11:22:00,2017-12-13 19:22:00,2017-12-13,19:22:00,19,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.063, 'neu': 0.828, 'pos': 0.109, 'compound': 0.4374}",222,0.4374,"['Luther Strange', 'Roy Moore', 'Roy']","['PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON']",2017-12-13 19:27:00,267.15,266.75,0.009999999999990905,3.7433555439061565e-05,-0.38999999999998636,-0.0014599086621246776,3.7433555439061565e-05,0.0014599086621246776
9.40796e+17,"congratulations to doug jones on a hard fought victory. the write-in votes played a very big factor, but a win is a win. the people of alabama are great, and the republicans will have another shot at this seat in a very short period of time. it never ends!",103471,19326,2017-12-13 04:08:00,2017-12-13 12:08:00,2017-12-13,12:08:00,12,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.047, 'neu': 0.613, 'pos': 0.34, 'compound': 0.9668}",256,0.9668,"['Doug Jones', 'Alabama', 'Republicans']","['PERSON', 'GPE', 'NORP']",2017-12-13 12:13:00,267.17,266.75,-0.05000000000001137,-0.00018711174313304154,-0.4700000000000273,-0.0017588503854502927,0.00018711174313304154,0.0017588503854502927
9.40706e+17,wishing all of those celebrating #hanukkah around the world a happy and healthy eight nights in the company of those they love.  ,65750,13616,2017-12-12 22:13:00,2017-12-13 06:13:00,2017-12-13,06:13:00,6,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.497, 'pos': 0.503, 'compound': 0.9451}",129,0.9451,['eight nights'],['DATE'],2017-12-13 06:18:00,266.82,266.75,-0.052500000000009095,-0.000196723154315297,-0.12250000000000227,-0.00045902069340228864,0.000196723154315297,0.00045902069340228864
9.39968e+17,"very little discussion of all the purposely false and defamatory stories put out this week by the fake news media. they are out of control - correct reporting means nothing to them. major lies written, then forced to be withdrawn after they are exposed...a stain on america!",99253,23353,2017-10-12 21:18:00,2017-10-13 05:18:00,2017-10-13,05:18:00,5,2017,10,"{'neg': 0.176, 'neu': 0.824, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8478}",274,-0.8478,"['this week', 'the Fake News Media', 'America']","['DATE', 'ORG', 'GPE']",2017-10-13 05:23:00,254.70857142857145,254.95,-0.003928571428559735,-1.542355176349702e-05,0.23749999999998295,0.0009324238111595738,1.542355176349702e-05,0.0009324238111595738
9.3968e+17,no american should be separated from their loved ones because of preventable crime committed by those illegally in our country. our cities should be sanctuaries for americans – not for criminal aliens! ,104365,27338,2017-10-12 02:17:00,2017-10-12 10:17:00,2017-10-12,10:17:00,10,2017,10,"{'neg': 0.14, 'neu': 0.638, 'pos': 0.222, 'compound': 0.5216}",202,0.5216,"['American', 'Americans']","['NORP', 'NORP']",2017-10-12 10:22:00,254.84,254.64,0.03999999999999204,0.0001569858712715543,-0.160000000000025,-0.0006279434850864404,0.0001569858712715543,0.0006279434850864404
9.39643e+17,great army - navy game. army wins 14 to 13 and brings home the commander-in-chief’s trophy! congratulations!,78901,11838,2017-09-12 23:47:00,2017-09-13 07:47:00,2017-09-13,07:47:00,7,2017,9,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.514, 'pos': 0.486, 'compound': 0.9229}",108,0.9229,"['Great Army - Navy Game', 'Army', '14', '13', 'COMMANDER']","['ORG', 'ORG', 'CARDINAL', 'CARDINAL', 'ORG']",2017-09-13 07:52:00,249.82,250.17,0.0,0.0,0.3499999999999943,0.001401008726282901,0.0,0.001401008726282901
9.39641e+17,great army - navy game. army wins 14 to 13 and brings home the commander-in-chief’s trophy (last time was 1996). wow! congratulations!,7867,1657,2017-09-12 11:39:00,2017-09-12 19:39:00,2017-09-12,19:39:00,19,2017,9,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.514, 'pos': 0.486, 'compound': 0.9523}",134,0.9523,"['Great Army - Navy Game', 'Army', '14', '13', 'COMMANDER', '1996']","['ORG', 'ORG', 'CARDINAL', 'CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'DATE']",2017-09-12 19:44:00,250.125,250.05,0.0049999999999954525,1.999040460577104e-05,-0.06999999999999318,-0.0002798656644810218,1.999040460577104e-05,0.0002798656644810218
9.39634e+17,". of the washington post just admitted that his picture was a fake (fraud?) showing an almost empty arena last night for my speech in pensacola when, in fact, he knew the arena was packed (as shown also on t.v.). fake news, he should be fired.",73972,18321,2017-09-12 23:14:00,2017-09-13 07:14:00,2017-09-13,07:14:00,7,2017,9,"{'neg': 0.236, 'neu': 0.738, 'pos': 0.026, 'compound': -0.9076}",254,-0.9076,"['the Washington Post', 'last night', 'Pensacola', 'T.V.']","['ORG', 'TIME', 'PERSON', 'GPE']",2017-09-13 07:19:00,249.7,250.17,0.01999999999998181,8.010253123991432e-05,0.4899999999999807,0.0019625120153796086,8.010253123991432e-05,0.0019625120153796086
9.39616e+17,".  put out a phony photo of an empty arena hours before i arrived @ the venue, w/ thousands of people outside, on their way in. real photos now shown as i spoke. packed house, many people unable to get in. demand apology &amp, retraction from fake news wapo! ",64019,18675,2017-09-12 22:01:00,2017-09-13 06:01:00,2017-09-13,06:01:00,6,2017,9,"{'neg': 0.147, 'neu': 0.83, 'pos': 0.024, 'compound': -0.7371}",285,-0.7371,"['an empty arena hours', 'thousands', 'FAKE NEWS WaPo']","['TIME', 'CARDINAL', 'ORG']",2017-09-13 06:06:00,249.71571428571426,250.17,0.0023809523809461552,9.53474269540869e-06,0.45666666666667766,0.0018287636489842127,9.53474269540869e-06,0.0018287636489842127
9.39376e+17,"we believe that every american should stand for the national anthem, and we proudly pledge allegiance to one nation under god! ",58748,13187,2017-09-12 06:06:00,2017-09-12 14:06:00,2017-09-12,14:06:00,14,2017,9,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.739, 'pos': 0.261, 'compound': 0.7734}",127,0.7734,['American'],['NORP'],2017-09-12 14:11:00,249.78,250.05,-0.030000000000001137,-0.00012009126936472173,0.2400000000000091,0.0009607301549177738,0.00012009126936472173,0.0009607301549177738
9.39355e+17,"this is your land, this is your home, and it's your voice that matters the most. so speak up, be heard, and fight, fight, fight for the change you've been waiting for your entire life!merry christmas and thank you pensacola, florida! ",65377,16573,2017-09-12 04:46:00,2017-09-12 12:46:00,2017-09-12,12:46:00,12,2017,9,"{'neg': 0.172, 'neu': 0.739, 'pos': 0.089, 'compound': -0.6188}",234,-0.6188,['Florida'],['GPE'],2017-09-12 12:51:00,249.87,250.05,0.025000000000005684,0.00010006203846387033,0.2050000000000125,0.0008205087154036003,0.00010006203846387033,0.0008205087154036003
9.393e+17,just arrived at the pensacola bay center. join me live on  in 10 minutes! #maga ,34237,5407,2017-09-12 01:04:00,2017-09-12 09:04:00,2017-09-12,09:04:00,9,2017,9,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.858, 'pos': 0.142, 'compound': 0.3595}",88,0.3595,"['the Pensacola Bay Center', '10 minutes', '#']","['FAC', 'TIME', 'CARDINAL']",2017-09-12 09:09:00,249.59,250.05,0.030000000000001137,0.00012021157236737111,0.4900000000000091,0.001963455682000357,0.00012021157236737111,0.001963455682000357
9.39275e+17,"on my way to pensacola, florida. see everyone soon! #maga ",41796,6207,2017-08-12 23:25:00,2017-08-13 07:25:00,2017-08-13,07:25:00,7,2017,8,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",58,0.0,"['Pensacola', 'Florida', '#']","['GPE', 'GPE', 'CARDINAL']",2017-08-13 07:30:00,245.185,245.56,0.0024999999999977263,1.0196486290814908e-05,0.3774999999999977,0.0015396694299144422,1.0196486290814908e-05,0.0015396694299144422
9.39007e+17,i fulfilled my campaign promise - others didn’t! ,128801,44196,2017-08-12 05:41:00,2017-08-12 13:41:00,2017-08-12,13:41:00,13,2017,8,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.426, 'pos': 0.574, 'compound': 0.6588}",49,0.6588,[],[],2017-08-12 13:46:00,244.653,244.84,0.0024999999999977263,1.0218658862326979e-05,0.18950000000000955,0.0007745743417651284,1.0218658862326979e-05,0.0007745743417651284
9.39006e+17,"tonight,  melania and i were thrilled to welcome so many wonderful friends to the  – and wish them all a very #happyhanukkah ",41742,8012,2017-08-12 05:36:00,2017-08-12 13:36:00,2017-08-12,13:36:00,13,2017,8,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.501, 'pos': 0.499, 'compound': 0.9427}",143,0.9427,"['Tonight', '@FLOTUS Melania', '@WhiteHouse', 'HappyHanukkah']","['TIME', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG']",2017-08-12 13:41:00,244.6505,244.84,0.0024999999999977263,1.0218763284382975e-05,0.19200000000000728,0.000784801020241356,1.0218763284382975e-05,0.000784801020241356
9.38878e+17,"across the battlefields, oceans, and harrowing skies of europe and the pacific throughout the war, one great battle cry could be heard by america’s friends and foes alike:“remember pearl harbor.” ",53619,10670,2017-07-12 21:10:00,2017-07-13 05:10:00,2017-07-13,05:10:00,5,2017,7,"{'neg': 0.324, 'neu': 0.515, 'pos': 0.161, 'compound': -0.743}",196,-0.743,"['Europe', 'Pacific', 'one', 'America']","['LOC', 'LOC', 'CARDINAL', 'GPE']",2017-07-13 05:15:00,244.43,244.42,0.010000000000019327,4.0913182227392714e-05,0.0,0.0,4.0913182227392714e-05,0.0
9.38874e+17,"today, as we remember pearl harbor, it was an incredible honor to be joined with surviving veterans of the attack on 12/7/1941. they are heroes, and they are living witnesses to american history. all american hearts are filled with gratitude for their service and their sacrifice. ",52705,10118,2017-07-12 20:52:00,2017-07-13 04:52:00,2017-07-13,04:52:00,4,2017,7,"{'neg': 0.055, 'neu': 0.721, 'pos': 0.224, 'compound': 0.8636}",281,0.8636,"['Today', 'Veterans', 'American', 'American']","['DATE', 'NORP', 'NORP', 'NORP']",2017-07-13 04:57:00,244.33333333333331,244.42,-0.006666666666689025,-2.7284385146472232e-05,0.07999999999998408,0.00032741262175650356,2.7284385146472232e-05,0.00032741262175650356
9.38862e+17,"today, the u.s. flag flies at half-staff at the , in honor of national pearl harbor remembrance day.  ",46715,8315,2017-07-12 20:04:00,2017-07-13 04:04:00,2017-07-13,04:04:00,4,2017,7,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.842, 'pos': 0.158, 'compound': 0.4939}",113,0.4939,"['Today', 'U.S.', 'half', '@WhiteHouse', 'National Pearl Harbor Remembrance Day']","['DATE', 'GPE', 'CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'ORG']",2017-07-13 04:09:00,244.18444444444444,244.42,0.005491672370453671,2.2490359255409736e-05,0.24104722792600342,0.000987174468517793,2.2490359255409736e-05,0.000987174468517793
9.38517e+17,i have determined that it is time to officially recognize jerusalem as the capital of israel. i am also directing the state department to begin preparation to move the american embassy from tel aviv to jerusalem... ,113973,31278,2017-06-12 21:14:00,2017-06-13 05:14:00,2017-06-13,05:14:00,5,2017,6,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.932, 'pos': 0.068, 'compound': 0.34}",215,0.34,"['Jerusalem', 'Israel', 'the State Department', 'American', 'Tel Aviv', 'Jerusalem']","['GPE', 'GPE', 'ORG', 'NORP', 'GPE', 'GPE']",2017-06-13 05:19:00,243.78,244.55,-0.05000000000001137,-0.0002050609030882638,0.7199999999999989,0.002952877004470323,0.0002050609030882638,0.002952877004470323
9.38185e+17,"join me this friday in pensacola, florida at the pensacola bay center! tickets:  ",42799,9786,2017-05-12 23:13:00,2017-05-13 07:13:00,2017-05-13,07:13:00,7,2017,5,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.828, 'pos': 0.172, 'compound': 0.3595}",81,0.3595,"['this Friday', 'Pensacola', 'Florida', 'the Pensacola Bay Center']","['DATE', 'GPE', 'GPE', 'FAC']",2017-05-13 07:18:00,239.06475,239.16,0.0006250000000136424,2.6143613142023815e-06,0.0958750000000066,0.00040104302558991903,2.6143613142023815e-06,0.00040104302558991903
9.37642e+17,"democrats refusal to give even one vote for massive tax cuts is why we need republican roy moore to win in alabama. we need his vote on stopping crime, illegal immigration, border wall, military, pro life, v.a., judges 2nd amendment and more. no to jones, a pelosi/schumer puppet!",80564,20232,2017-04-12 11:17:00,2017-04-12 19:17:00,2017-04-12,19:17:00,19,2017,4,"{'neg': 0.234, 'neu': 0.701, 'pos': 0.065, 'compound': -0.8353}",280,-0.8353,"['Democrats', 'one', 'Tax Cuts', 'Republican', 'Roy Moore', 'Alabama', 'Border Wall', 'Pro Life', 'V.A.', 'Jones', 'Pelosi/Schumer Puppet']","['NORP', 'CARDINAL', 'PERSON', 'NORP', 'PERSON', 'GPE', 'PERSON', 'GPE', 'GPE', 'ORG', 'ORG']",2017-04-12 19:22:00,234.09,234.03,0.0,0.0,-0.060000000000002274,-0.0002563116749968058,0.0,0.0002563116749968058
9.37279e+17,i never asked comey to stop investigating flynn. just more fake news covering another comey lie!,77729,17398,2017-03-12 11:15:00,2017-03-12 19:15:00,2017-03-12,19:15:00,19,2017,3,"{'neg': 0.312, 'neu': 0.688, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.7082}",96,-0.7082,"['Comey', 'Flynn', 'Fake News', 'Comey']","['PERSON', 'PERSON', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",2017-03-12 19:20:00,237.52940476190483,237.52714285714282,-0.00028273809516576875,-1.1903273992467522e-06,-0.00254464285717404,-1.0712946596092499e-05,1.1903273992467522e-06,1.0712946596092499e-05
9.37145e+17,"congratulations to  news for suspending brian ross for his horrendously inaccurate and dishonest report on the russia, russia, russia witch hunt. more networks and “papers” should do the same with their fake news!",88788,20965,2017-03-12 02:22:00,2017-03-12 10:22:00,2017-03-12,10:22:00,10,2017,3,"{'neg': 0.275, 'neu': 0.639, 'pos': 0.086, 'compound': -0.8221}",217,-0.8221,"['@ABC News', 'Brian Ross', 'Russia', 'Russia', 'Russia', 'Witch Hunt']","['ORG', 'PERSON', 'GPE', 'GPE', 'GPE', 'PERSON']",2017-03-12 10:27:00,237.55954464285716,237.52714285714282,-0.0002827380952510339,-1.190176379433183e-06,-0.03268452380959275,-0.00013758438945647003,1.190176379433183e-06,0.00013758438945647003
9.37143e+17,"many people in our country are asking what the “justice” department is going to do about the fact that totally crooked hillary, after receiving a subpoena from the united states congress, deleted and “acid washed” 33,000 emails? no justice!",95324,25611,2017-03-12 02:13:00,2017-03-12 10:13:00,2017-03-12,10:13:00,10,2017,3,"{'neg': 0.05, 'neu': 0.801, 'pos': 0.149, 'compound': 0.6476}",240,0.6476,"['Crooked Hillary', 'the United States', '33,000']","['PERSON', 'GPE', 'CARDINAL']",2017-03-12 10:18:00,237.56005357142857,237.52714285714282,-0.0002827380952794556,-1.1901738298226199e-06,-0.033193452381027555,-0.00013972640760105215,1.1901738298226199e-06,0.00013972640760105215
9.37141e+17,"so general flynn lies to the fbi and his life is destroyed, while crooked hillary clinton, on that now famous fbi holiday “interrogation” with no swearing in and no recording, lies many times...and nothing happens to her? rigged system, or just a double standard?",120699,34268,2017-03-12 02:06:00,2017-03-12 10:06:00,2017-03-12,10:06:00,10,2017,3,"{'neg': 0.33, 'neu': 0.622, 'pos': 0.048, 'compound': -0.9311}",263,-0.9311,"['Flynn', 'FBI', 'Crooked Hillary Clinton', 'FBI']","['PERSON', 'ORG', 'PERSON', 'ORG']",2017-03-12 10:11:00,237.56044940476193,237.52714285714282,-0.0002827380952510339,-1.1901718465870415e-06,-0.033589285714356265,-0.00014139241536836712,1.1901718465870415e-06,0.00014139241536836712
9.37137e+17,great job first lady melania! ,67562,11335,2017-03-12 01:50:00,2017-03-12 09:50:00,2017-03-12,09:50:00,9,2017,3,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.477, 'pos': 0.523, 'compound': 0.6588}",30,0.6588,[],[],2017-03-12 09:55:00,237.56135416666663,237.52714285714282,-0.0002827380952794556,-1.1901673138950665e-06,-0.03449404761909136,-0.0001452004122741416,1.1901673138950665e-06,0.0001452004122741416
9.37066e+17,"62 years ago this week, a brave seamstress in montgomery, alabama uttered one word that changed history... ",82830,21271,2017-02-12 21:07:00,2017-02-13 05:07:00,2017-02-13,05:07:00,5,2017,2,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.815, 'pos': 0.185, 'compound': 0.5267}",107,0.5267,"['62 years ago this week', 'Montgomery', 'Alabama', 'one']","['DATE', 'GPE', 'GPE', 'CARDINAL']",2017-02-13 05:12:00,231.68533333333332,232.77,-0.006666666666689025,-2.8773831926389452e-05,1.078000000000003,0.004652728622481583,2.8773831926389452e-05,0.004652728622481583
9.36865e+17,we are one step closer to delivering massive tax cuts for working families across america. special thanks to  mitch mcconnell and chairman  for shepherding our bill through the senate. look forward to signing a final bill before christmas! ,59801,13417,2017-02-12 07:49:00,2017-02-12 15:49:00,2017-02-12,15:49:00,15,2017,2,"{'neg': 0.05, 'neu': 0.816, 'pos': 0.134, 'compound': 0.5707}",267,0.5707,"['one', 'America', '@SenateMajLdr Mitch McConnell', '@SenOrrinHatch', 'Senate', 'Christmas']","['CARDINAL', 'GPE', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'ORG', 'DATE']",2017-02-12 15:54:00,231.6431093935791,231.65554102259216,0.0002526753864628972,1.0907972300233367e-06,0.012684304399527946,5.4758020943245225e-05,1.0907972300233367e-06,5.4758020943245225e-05
9.35838e+17,"great, and we should boycott fake news cnn. dealing with them is a total waste of time! ",55790,12620,2017-11-29 11:49:00,2017-11-29 19:49:00,2017-11-29,19:49:00,19,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.345, 'neu': 0.488, 'pos': 0.167, 'compound': -0.5255}",88,-0.5255,"['Fake News', 'CNN']","['PERSON', 'ORG']",2017-11-29 19:54:00,262.6,262.71,0.026666666666699257,0.00010155892956900646,0.13666666666665606,0.0005204895140404816,0.00010155892956900646,0.0005204895140404816
9.36352e+17,our fifth 1k milestone of 2017!#dow24k #maga ,45434,10067,2017-11-30 21:50:00,2017-12-01 05:50:00,2017-12-01,05:50:00,5,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",45,0.0,"['FIFTH 1', '2017!#DOW24']","['DATE', 'CARDINAL']",2017-12-01 05:55:00,263.42,264.46,-0.3599999999999568,-0.00136477367503206,0.6800000000000068,0.002577905830616449,0.00136477367503206,0.002577905830616449
9.36339e+17,"today, it was my great honor to meet with the crown prince of bahrain at the . bahrain and the united states are important partners.during the crown prince’s visit, he is advancing $9 billion in commercial deals, including finalizing the purchase of f-16’s... ",39629,8121,2017-11-30 21:00:00,2017-12-01 05:00:00,2017-12-01,05:00:00,5,2017,12,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.766, 'pos': 0.234, 'compound': 0.8979}",271,0.8979,"['Today', 'the Crown Prince', 'Bahrain', 'Bahrain', 'the United States', 'the Crown Prince', '$9 BILLION', 'F-16']","['DATE', 'ORG', 'GPE', 'GPE', 'GPE', 'ORG', 'MONEY', 'PRODUCT']",2017-12-01 05:05:00,264.40333333333336,264.46,0.03333333333335986,0.00012608591494254212,0.08999999999997499,0.0003404319703444982,0.00012608591494254212,0.0003404319703444982
9.36058e+17,funny to hear the democrats talking about the national debt when president obama doubled it in only 8 years!,108861,28268,2017-11-30 02:23:00,2017-11-30 10:23:00,2017-11-30,10:23:00,10,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.115, 'neu': 0.738, 'pos': 0.147, 'compound': 0.1759}",108,0.1759,"['Democrats', 'the National Debt', 'only 8 years']","['NORP', 'ORG', 'DATE']",2017-11-30 10:28:00,264.09,265.01,0.009999999999990905,3.786731293543966e-05,0.9300000000000068,0.0035216601029991173,3.786731293543966e-05,0.0035216601029991173
9.36052e+17,"""“had the information (crooked hillary’s emails) been released there would have been harm to national security....""""charles mcculloughfmr intel comm inspector general ",49012,16491,2017-11-30 02:00:00,2017-11-30 10:00:00,2017-11-30,10:00:00,10,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.149, 'neu': 0.851, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.5423}",167,-0.5423,"['Crooked Hillary', 'National Security', 'Intel Comm Inspector']","['PERSON', 'ORG', 'ORG']",2017-11-30 10:05:00,264.03,265.01,0.08499999999997954,0.0003220367879671126,1.0649999999999977,0.004034931519824197,0.0003220367879671126,0.004034931519824197
9.3604e+17,the only people who don’t like the tax cut bill are the people that don’t understand it or the obstructionist democrats that know how really good it is and do not want the credit and success to go to the republicans!,66935,14280,2017-11-30 01:09:00,2017-11-30 09:09:00,2017-11-30,09:09:00,9,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.11, 'neu': 0.697, 'pos': 0.193, 'compound': 0.7335}",216,0.7335,"['the Tax Cut Bill', 'the Obstructionist Democrats', 'Republicans']","['LAW', 'NORP', 'NORP']",2017-11-30 09:14:00,263.65,265.01,0.049999999999954525,0.0001896813353564284,1.4099999999999682,0.005349013657056025,0.0001896813353564284,0.005349013657056025
9.36038e+17,the house of representatives seeks contempt citations(?) against the justicedepartment and the fbi for withholding key documents and an fbi witness which could shed light on surveillance of associates of donald trump. big stuff. deep state. give this information now! ,60916,18613,2017-11-30 01:03:00,2017-11-30 09:03:00,2017-11-30,09:03:00,9,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.093, 'neu': 0.907, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6239}",276,-0.6239,"['The House of Representatives', 'JusticeDepartment', 'FBI', 'FBI', 'Donald Trump', 'Deep State']","['ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'PERSON', 'PERSON']",2017-11-30 09:08:00,263.6,265.01,0.05000000000001137,0.0001897173211914679,1.4599999999999795,0.0055397457787895255,0.0001897173211914679,0.0055397457787895255
9.36038e+17,"._may, don’t focus on me, focus on the destructive radical islamic terrorism that is taking place within the united kingdom. we are doing just fine!",94846,29584,2017-11-30 01:02:00,2017-11-30 09:02:00,2017-11-30,09:02:00,9,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.258, 'neu': 0.609, 'pos': 0.133, 'compound': -0.7424}",156,-0.7424,"['Radical Islamic Terrorism', 'the United Kingdom']","['ORG', 'GPE']",2017-11-30 09:07:00,263.6,265.01,0.060000000000002274,0.0002276694239963659,1.4699999999999704,0.005577900887910641,0.0002276694239963659,0.005577900887910641
9.36032e+17,"now, we have a once in a lifetime opportunity to restore american prosperity – and reclaim america’s destiny.but in order to achieve this bright and glowing future, the senate must pass tax cuts – and bring main street roaring back to life! ",43721,9881,2017-11-30 00:40:00,2017-11-30 08:40:00,2017-11-30,08:40:00,8,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.063, 'neu': 0.734, 'pos': 0.203, 'compound': 0.7556}",241,0.7556,"['SENATE', 'MUST', 'Main Street']","['ORG', 'PRODUCT', 'FAC']",2017-11-30 08:45:00,263.51,265.01,0.029999999999972715,0.00011386063458316652,1.5299999999999727,0.00580689236374667,0.00011386063458316652,0.00580689236374667
9.36014e+17,"a vote to cut taxes is a vote to put america first. it is time to take care of our workers, to protect our communities, and to rebuild our great country!  ",40793,8887,2017-11-29 23:29:00,2017-11-30 07:29:00,2017-11-30,07:29:00,7,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.073, 'neu': 0.645, 'pos': 0.282, 'compound': 0.8439}",155,0.8439,['OUR WORKERS'],['ORG'],2017-11-30 07:34:00,263.4,265.01,-0.026666666666699257,-0.00010122994381750489,1.5833333333333144,0.006010527914156936,0.00010122994381750489,0.006010527914156936
9.36006e+17,"this week, the senate can join the house &amp, take a strong stand for the middle class families who are the backbone of america. together, we will give the american people a big, beautiful christmas present-a massive tax cut that lets americans keep more of their hard-earned money! ",46046,9672,2017-11-29 22:54:00,2017-11-30 06:54:00,2017-11-30,06:54:00,6,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.039, 'neu': 0.781, 'pos': 0.18, 'compound': 0.8221}",284,0.8221,"['This week', 'Senate', 'the House &amp', 'America', 'American', 'Christmas', 'Americans']","['DATE', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'GPE', 'NORP', 'DATE', 'NORP']",2017-11-30 06:59:00,263.5425,265.01,-0.007499999999993179,-2.8457598178687832e-05,1.4599999999999795,0.0055397457787895255,2.8457598178687832e-05,0.0055397457787895255
9.3587e+17,so now tha matt lauer is gone when will the fake news practitioners at nbc be terminating the contract of phil griffin? and will they terminate low ratings joe scarborough based on the “unsolved mystery” that took place in florida years ago? investigate!,11146,3421,2017-11-29 01:58:00,2017-11-29 09:58:00,2017-11-29,09:58:00,9,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.125, 'neu': 0.875, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.7052}",254,-0.7052,"['Matt Lauer', 'Fake News', 'NBC', 'Phil Griffin', 'Joe Scarborough', 'Florida', 'years ago']","['PERSON', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'PERSON', 'PERSON', 'GPE', 'DATE']",2017-11-29 10:03:00,263.41,262.71,-0.19999999999998863,-0.0007586965593110604,-0.9000000000000341,-0.003414134516900095,0.0007586965593110604,0.003414134516900095
9.35834e+17,"., we are in record territory in all things having to do with our economy! ",31460,6271,2017-11-29 11:32:00,2017-11-29 19:32:00,2017-11-29,19:32:00,19,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",89,0.0,[],[],2017-11-29 19:37:00,262.56333333333333,262.71,-0.03666666666669016,-0.00013962934755022908,0.1099999999999568,0.00041888804265025433,0.00013962934755022908,0.00041888804265025433
9.35714e+17,great day for tax cuts and the republican party. but the biggest winner will be our great country!,61062,10271,2017-11-29 03:35:00,2017-11-29 11:35:00,2017-11-29,11:35:00,11,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.073, 'neu': 0.431, 'pos': 0.497, 'compound': 0.9299}",98,0.9299,"['the Republican Party', 'Winner']","['ORG', 'GPE']",2017-11-29 11:40:00,262.72,262.71,0.03000000000002956,0.00011420305302839681,0.01999999999998181,7.613536868545362e-05,0.00011420305302839681,7.613536868545362e-05
9.35713e+17,great work ivanka! ,37324,5911,2017-11-29 03:30:00,2017-11-29 11:30:00,2017-11-29,11:30:00,11,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.313, 'pos': 0.687, 'compound': 0.6588}",19,0.6588,[],[],2017-11-29 11:35:00,262.69,262.71,0.0,0.0,0.01999999999998181,7.613536868545362e-05,0.0,7.613536868545362e-05
9.35712e+17,"just won the lawsuit on leadership of consumer financial protection bureau, cfpb. a big win for the consumer!",68321,12579,2017-11-29 03:28:00,2017-11-29 11:28:00,2017-11-29,11:28:00,11,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.08, 'neu': 0.591, 'pos': 0.329, 'compound': 0.784}",109,0.784,"['Consumer Financial Protection Bureau', 'CFPB']","['ORG', 'ORG']",2017-11-29 11:33:00,262.63,262.71,0.040000000000020464,0.00015232872538946824,0.12000000000000455,0.00045698617616818826,0.00015232872538946824,0.00045698617616818826
9.35701e+17,"charles mccullough, the respected fmr intel comm inspector general, said public was misled on crooked hillary emails. “emails endangered national security.” why aren’t our deep state authorities looking at this? rigged &amp, corrupt?  ",53533,15970,2017-11-29 02:45:00,2017-11-29 10:45:00,2017-11-29,10:45:00,10,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.073, 'neu': 0.839, 'pos': 0.088, 'compound': 0.1494}",261,0.1494,"['Charles McCullough', 'Intel Comm Inspector General', 'Crooked Hillary Emails', 'Emails endangered National Security', 'Rigged &amp', '@TuckerCarlson @seanhannity']","['PERSON', 'ORG', 'PERSON', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'ORG', 'ORG']",2017-11-29 10:50:00,263.09,262.71,-0.05000000000001137,-0.00019001292087866297,-0.4300000000000068,-0.001634111119556156,0.00019001292087866297,0.001634111119556156
9.35686e+17,"after north korea missile launch, it's more important than ever to fund our gov't &amp, military! dems shouldn't hold troop funding hostage for amnesty &amp, illegal immigration. i ran on stopping illegal immigration and won big. they can't now threaten a shutdown to get their demands.",80465,18470,2017-11-29 01:45:00,2017-11-29 09:45:00,2017-11-29,09:45:00,9,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.165, 'neu': 0.69, 'pos': 0.145, 'compound': -0.2767}",286,-0.2767,"['North Korea', 'amnesty &amp']","['GPE', 'ORG']",2017-11-29 09:50:00,263.24,262.71,-0.11000000000001364,-0.0004176950825897613,-0.6400000000000432,-0.0024302259350675644,0.0004176950825897613,0.0024302259350675644
9.35641e+17,"“the conference board said that consumer sentiment was at its highest level in nearly 17 years in november. the consumer confidence index rose from 126.2 in october to 129.5, notching its best reading since december 2000...” ",34359,7441,2017-11-28 22:44:00,2017-11-29 06:44:00,2017-11-29,06:44:00,6,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.819, 'pos': 0.181, 'compound': 0.8176}",225,0.8176,"['The Conference Board', 'nearly 17 years', 'November', '126.2', 'October', '129.5', 'December 2000']","['ORG', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'CARDINAL', 'DATE', 'CARDINAL', 'DATE']",2017-11-29 06:49:00,263.1342857142857,262.71,-0.008214285714302605,-3.1216111856893526e-05,-0.43250000000000455,-0.0016435961503748144,3.1216111856893526e-05,0.0016435961503748144
9.35637e+17,"dow, s&amp,p 500 and nasdaq all finished the day at new record highs! ",40212,8169,2017-11-28 22:30:00,2017-11-29 06:30:00,2017-11-29,06:30:00,6,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 1.0, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': 0.0}",70,0.0,"['500', 'Nasdaq', 'the day']","['CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'DATE']",2017-11-29 06:35:00,263.13,262.71,0.005714285714304879,2.171705929307397e-05,-0.41428571428571104,-0.00157448679874257,2.171705929307397e-05,0.00157448679874257
9.35632e+17,"remarks from the roosevelt room with  mitch mcconnell,  and secretary of defense, general james mattis. ",28951,6515,2017-11-28 22:12:00,2017-11-29 06:12:00,2017-11-29,06:12:00,6,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.914, 'pos': 0.086, 'compound': 0.128}",129,0.128,"['the Roosevelt Room', 'Mitch McConnell', 'Defense', 'James Mattis']","['FAC', 'PERSON', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",2017-11-29 06:17:00,263.0,262.71,-0.01999999999998181,-7.603984487864729e-05,-0.3100000000000023,-0.0011786175956201136,7.603984487864729e-05,0.0011786175956201136
9.3534e+17,new home sales reach a 10 year high. stock market has more record gains. hopefully republican senators will give us the much needed tax cuts to keep it all going! democrats want big tax increases.,65520,12752,2017-11-28 02:48:00,2017-11-28 10:48:00,2017-11-28,10:48:00,10,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.056, 'neu': 0.734, 'pos': 0.211, 'compound': 0.6291}",196,0.6291,"['10 year', 'Republican', 'Democrats', 'Tax Increases']","['DATE', 'NORP', 'NORP', 'ORG']",2017-11-28 10:53:00,261.12,262.87,0.03000000000002956,0.00011490290704366143,1.7800000000000296,0.006817572484583974,0.00011490290704366143,0.006817572484583974
9.34962e+17,"back in d.c., big week for tax cuts and many other things of great importance to our country.  senate republicans will hopefully come through for all of us. the tax cut bill is getting better and better. the end result will be great for all!",73560,13270,2017-11-27 01:47:00,2017-11-27 09:47:00,2017-11-27,09:47:00,9,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.071, 'neu': 0.609, 'pos': 0.321, 'compound': 0.945}",241,0.945,"['D.C.', 'week', 'Senate', 'Republicans', 'The Tax Cut Bill']","['GPE', 'DATE', 'ORG', 'NORP', 'PRODUCT']",2017-11-27 09:52:00,260.695,260.23,0.024999999999977263,9.590670196024576e-05,-0.4399999999999977,-0.0016879579545018518,9.590670196024576e-05,0.0016879579545018518
9.34897e+17,"since the first day i took office, all you hear is the phony democrat excuse for losing the election, russia, russia,russia.  despite this i have the economy booming and have possibly done more than any 10 month president. make america great again!",130147,26771,2017-11-26 21:29:00,2017-11-27 05:29:00,2017-11-27,05:29:00,5,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.056, 'neu': 0.804, 'pos': 0.14, 'compound': 0.5893}",248,0.5893,"['the first day', 'Democrat', 'Russia', 'Russia', 'Russia', 'more than any 10 month']","['DATE', 'NORP', 'GPE', 'GPE', 'GPE', 'DATE']",2017-11-27 05:34:00,260.495,260.23,0.007727272727265699,2.9664684367731345e-05,-0.25727272727272066,-0.0009876594913029871,2.9664684367731345e-05,0.0009876594913029871
9.34564e+17,"wow, even i didn’t realize we did so much. wish the fake news would report! thank you. ",56589,15531,2017-11-25 23:25:00,2017-11-26 07:25:00,2017-11-26,07:25:00,7,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.126, 'neu': 0.486, 'pos': 0.388, 'compound': 0.7558}",87,0.7558,['the Fake News'],['ORG'],2017-11-26 07:30:00,260.1763202485174,260.2822225360068,0.0007060152498752359,2.713610389489611e-06,0.10660830273928923,0.00040975516884417403,2.713610389489611e-06,0.00040975516884417403
9.34552e+17,". is much more important in the united states than cnn, but outside of the u.s., cnn international is still a major source of (fake) news, and they represent our nation to the world very poorly. the outside world does not see the truth from them!",94924,26371,2017-11-25 22:37:00,2017-11-26 06:37:00,2017-11-26,06:37:00,6,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.051, 'neu': 0.872, 'pos': 0.078, 'compound': 0.0761}",254,0.0761,"['the United States', 'CNN', 'U.S.', 'CNN International']","['GPE', 'ORG', 'GPE', 'ORG']",2017-11-26 06:42:00,260.16954250211813,260.2822225360068,0.0007060152499889227,2.7136810831091157e-06,0.11338604913868267,0.0004358171819106619,2.7136810831091157e-06,0.0004358171819106619
9.34542e+17,"check out the recent editorial in the wall street journal  about what a complete disaster the  has been under its leader from previous administration, who just quit!",37441,7879,2017-11-25 22:00:00,2017-11-26 06:00:00,2017-11-26,06:00:00,6,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.14, 'neu': 0.86, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.6588}",174,-0.6588,"['the Wall Street Journal @WSJ', '@CFPB']","['ORG', 'ORG']",2017-11-26 06:05:00,260.16431798926857,260.2822225360068,0.0007060152499320793,2.713735578066105e-06,0.11861056198819142,0.0004559075771135762,2.713735578066105e-06,0.0004559075771135762
9.34539e+17,"the consumer financial protection bureau, or cfpb, has been a total disaster as run by the previous administrations pick. financial institutions have been devastated and unable to properly serve the public. we will bring it back to life!",60320,11770,2017-11-25 21:48:00,2017-11-26 05:48:00,2017-11-26,05:48:00,5,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.193, 'neu': 0.807, 'pos': 0.0, 'compound': -0.8553}",237,-0.8553,"['The Consumer Financial Protection Bureau', 'CFPB', 'Administrations', 'Financial Institutions']","['ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'ORG']",2017-11-26 05:53:00,260.1626235526688,260.2822225360068,0.0007060152499320793,2.713753252647109e-06,0.12030499858798294,0.0004624235542493631,2.713753252647109e-06,0.0004624235542493631
9.3419e+17,"time magazine called to say that i was probably going to be named “man (person) of the year,” like last year, but i would have to agree to an interview and a major photo shoot. i said probably is no good and took a pass. thanks anyway!",139152,33870,2017-11-24 22:40:00,2017-11-25 06:40:00,2017-11-25,06:40:00,6,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.107, 'neu': 0.656, 'pos': 0.237, 'compound': 0.7959}",235,0.7959,"['Time Magazine', 'Man (Person) of the Year', 'last year']","['ORG', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'DATE']",2017-11-25 06:45:00,259.9666337192884,260.0788901440271,0.0007060152499320793,2.715799167096434e-06,0.11296243998867794,0.00043452786673368014,2.715799167096434e-06,0.00043452786673368014
9.34026e+17,"can you believe that the disrespect for our country, our flag, our anthem continues without penalty to the players. the commissioner has lost control of the hemorrhaging league. players are the boss! ",50359,11667,2017-11-24 11:48:00,2017-11-24 19:48:00,2017-11-24,19:48:00,19,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.146, 'neu': 0.787, 'pos': 0.067, 'compound': -0.4427}",200,-0.4427,['Anthem'],['GPE'],2017-11-24 19:53:00,259.87456933069757,259.8755577520475,0.0007060152499320793,2.716761281510959e-06,0.001694436599848359,6.520227075670049e-06,2.716761281510959e-06,6.520227075670049e-06
9.33922e+17,two great people! ,57070,11636,2017-11-24 04:54:00,2017-11-24 12:54:00,2017-11-24,12:54:00,12,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.313, 'pos': 0.687, 'compound': 0.6588}",18,0.6588,['Two'],['CARDINAL'],2017-11-24 12:59:00,260.335,259.8755577520475,-0.025000000000034106,-9.602089414669728e-05,-0.4844422479525292,-0.001860663112430977,9.602089414669728e-05,0.001860663112430977
9.33919e+17,a great guy (with great ratings)! ,54667,9261,2017-11-24 04:42:00,2017-11-24 12:42:00,2017-11-24,12:42:00,12,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.261, 'pos': 0.739, 'compound': 0.8588}",34,0.8588,[],[],2017-11-24 12:47:00,260.3425,259.8755577520475,-0.0675000000000523,-0.00025920663569007447,-0.5344422479525406,-0.0020523107712935008,0.00025920663569007447,0.0020523107712935008
9.33837e+17,"obamacare premiums are going up, up, up, just as i have been predicting for two years. obamacare is owned by the democrats, and it is a disaster. but do not worry. even though the dems want to obstruct, we will repeal &amp, replace right after tax cuts!",75706,14607,2017-11-23 23:18:00,2017-11-24 07:18:00,2017-11-24,07:18:00,7,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.129, 'neu': 0.799, 'pos': 0.072, 'compound': -0.5975}",253,-0.5975,"['ObamaCare', 'two years', 'ObamaCare', 'Democrats', 'Dems', 'Repeal &amp']","['ORG', 'DATE', 'ORG', 'NORP', 'NORP', 'ORG']",2017-11-24 07:23:00,260.33,259.8755577520475,-0.009999999999990905,-3.84113082891254e-05,-0.46444224795249056,-0.001783983436861376,3.84113082891254e-05,0.001783983436861376
9.33831e+17,"my great honor to join our incredible men and women of the , at the lake worth inlet station, in riviera beach, florida today!#happythanksgiving ",49085,8786,2017-11-23 22:54:00,2017-11-24 06:54:00,2017-11-24,06:54:00,6,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.631, 'pos': 0.369, 'compound': 0.8932}",150,0.8932,"['@USCG', 'the Lake Worth Inlet Station', 'Riviera Beach', 'Florida']","['ORG', 'FAC', 'GPE', 'GPE']",2017-11-24 06:59:00,260.3125,259.8755577520475,-0.007499999999993179,-2.8810694529783264e-05,-0.44444224795250875,-0.0017072919789202089,2.8810694529783264e-05,0.0017072919789202089
9.33663e+17,make america great again!,123428,28352,2017-11-23 11:44:00,2017-11-23 19:44:00,2017-11-23,19:44:00,19,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.406, 'pos': 0.594, 'compound': 0.6588}",25,0.6588,[],[],2017-11-23 19:49:00,259.78977083333336,259.79,0.00010416666668788821,4.009653964472087e-07,0.00033333333334439885,1.2830892684122625e-06,4.009653964472087e-07,1.2830892684122625e-06
9.33659e+17, make america great again!,7560,2917,2017-11-23 11:31:00,2017-11-23 19:31:00,2017-11-23,19:31:00,19,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.438, 'pos': 0.562, 'compound': 0.729}",40,0.7290000000000001,['@ThePlumLineGS MAKE'],['PERSON'],2017-11-23 19:36:00,259.78950000000003,259.79,0.00010416666668788821,4.009658144580922e-07,0.0006041666666760648,2.325601723419323e-06,4.009658144580922e-07,2.325601723419323e-06
9.33659e+17,"happy thanksgiving, your country is starting to do really well. jobs coming back, highest stock market ever, military getting really strong, we will build the wall, v.a. taking care of our vets, great supreme court justice, record cut in regs, lowest unemployment in 17 years....!",176020,34473,2017-11-23 11:28:00,2017-11-23 19:28:00,2017-11-23,19:28:00,19,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.122, 'neu': 0.512, 'pos': 0.366, 'compound': 0.9564}",280,0.9564,"['Stock Market EVER', 'WALL', 'V.A.', 'Vets', 'Supreme Court', '17 years']","['PERSON', 'ORG', 'GPE', 'LOC', 'ORG', 'DATE']",2017-11-23 19:33:00,259.7894375,259.79,0.00010416666668788821,4.0096591092226605e-07,0.0006666666666887977,2.566181829464891e-06,4.0096591092226605e-07,2.566181829464891e-06
9.33517e+17,....and it will get even better with tax cuts! ,42794,7889,2017-11-23 02:06:00,2017-11-23 10:06:00,2017-11-23,10:06:00,10,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.178, 'neu': 0.565, 'pos': 0.258, 'compound': 0.2481}",47,0.2481,[],[],2017-11-23 10:11:00,259.7777291666667,259.79,0.00010416666668788821,4.0098398269630886e-07,0.012375000000020009,4.7636897134693603e-05,4.0098398269630886e-07,4.7636897134693603e-05
9.33448e+17,i have long given the order to help argentina with the search and rescue mission of their missing submarine. 45 people aboard and not much time left. may god be with them and the people of argentina!,106996,20574,2017-11-22 21:32:00,2017-11-23 05:32:00,2017-11-23,05:32:00,5,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.052, 'neu': 0.726, 'pos': 0.222, 'compound': 0.7424}",199,0.7424,"['Argentina', '45', 'Argentina']","['GPE', 'CARDINAL', 'GPE']",2017-11-23 05:37:00,259.77202083333333,259.79,0.00010416666668788821,4.0099279408078774e-07,0.018083333333379414,6.961234903842025e-05,4.0099279408078774e-07,6.961234903842025e-05
9.33446e+17,51 million american to travel this weekend - highest number in twelve years (aaa). traffic and airports are running very smoothly!  ,53613,8549,2017-11-22 21:25:00,2017-11-23 05:25:00,2017-11-23,05:25:00,5,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.926, 'pos': 0.074, 'compound': 0.1511}",140,0.1511,"['51 Million', 'American', 'twelve years', 'AAA']","['CARDINAL', 'NORP', 'DATE', 'ORG']",2017-11-23 05:30:00,259.771875,259.79,0.00010416666668788821,4.009930191942233e-07,0.018229166666685614,7.017377834476574e-05,4.009930191942233e-07,7.017377834476574e-05
9.33302e+17,will be having meetings and working the phones from the winter white house in florida (mar-a-lago). stock market hit new record high yesterday - $5.5 trillion gain since e. many companies coming back to the u.s. military building up and getting very strong.,65713,12203,2017-11-22 11:51:00,2017-11-22 19:51:00,2017-11-22,19:51:00,19,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.851, 'pos': 0.149, 'compound': 0.7902}",257,0.7902,"['the Winter White House', 'Florida', 'yesterday', '$5.5 trillion', 'U.S.']","['ORG', 'GPE', 'DATE', 'MONEY', 'GPE']",2017-11-22 19:56:00,259.66,259.76,0.07000000000005002,0.0002696559959938751,0.17000000000001592,0.0006548788474132899,0.0002696559959938751,0.0006548788474132899
9.33291e+17,another crooked hillary fan! ,70,38,2017-11-22 11:08:00,2017-11-22 19:08:00,2017-11-22,19:08:00,19,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.0, 'neu': 0.536, 'pos': 0.464, 'compound': 0.3802}",29,0.3802,[],[],2017-11-22 19:13:00,259.61,259.76,-0.01999999999998181,-7.70327003812418e-05,0.12999999999999545,0.0005007125524785096,7.70327003812418e-05,0.0005007125524785096
9.33286e+17,the nfl is now thinking about a new idea - keeping teams in the locker room during the national anthem next season. that’s almost as bad as kneeling! when will the highly paid commissioner finally get tough and smart? this issue is killing your league!.....,101847,19737,2017-11-22 10:48:00,2017-11-22 18:48:00,2017-11-22,18:48:00,18,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.189, 'neu': 0.759, 'pos': 0.053, 'compound': -0.7909}",257,-0.7909,"['NFL', 'next season']","['ORG', 'DATE']",2017-11-22 18:53:00,259.65,259.76,0.012000000000000455,4.6218196103807824e-05,0.1220000000000141,0.0004698849937220827,4.6218196103807824e-05,0.0004698849937220827
9.33282e+17,"...lavar, you could have spent the next 5 to 10 years during thanksgiving with your son in china, but no nba contract to support you. but remember lavar, shoplifting is not a little thing. it’s a really big deal, especially in china. ungrateful fool!",135381,30028,2017-11-22 10:33:00,2017-11-22 18:33:00,2017-11-22,18:33:00,18,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.219, 'neu': 0.713, 'pos': 0.068, 'compound': -0.8311}",250,-0.8311,"['LaVar', 'the next 5 to 10 years', 'Thanksgiving', 'China', 'NBA', 'LaVar', 'China']","['ORG', 'DATE', 'DATE', 'GPE', 'ORG', 'ORG', 'GPE']",2017-11-22 18:38:00,259.61833333333334,259.76,0.008333333333325754,3.2099431198049975e-05,0.14999999999997726,0.0005777897615653375,3.2099431198049975e-05,0.0005777897615653375
9.3328e+17,"it wasn’t the white house, it wasn’t the state department, it wasn’t father lavar’s so-called people on the ground in china that got his son out of a long term prison sentence - it was me. too bad! lavar is just a poor man’s version of don king, but without the hair. just think..",105092,25202,2017-11-22 10:25:00,2017-11-22 18:25:00,2017-11-22,18:25:00,18,2017,11,"{'neg': 0.123, 'neu': 0.856, 'pos': 0.021, 'compound': -0.68}",280,-0.68,"['the White House', 'n’t the State Department', 'LaVar', 'China', 'LaVar', 'Don King']","['ORG', 'ORG', 'PERSON', 'GPE', 'PERSON', 'PERSON']",2017-11-22 18:30:00,259.76,259.76,0.15999999999996817,0.0006163328197225275,0.15999999999996817,0.0006163328197225275,0.0006163328197225275,0.0006163328197225275
